Hello, hello, hello, hello, hello, yes, we're starting.
hola hola hola hola hola sí ya empezamos
family, let's start, have a good afternoon
familia empezamos que pasa buenas tardes
Good afternoon, well, it looks a little bit like
buenísimas tardes bueno se ve un poco
dark if I put it a little dark I don't know
oscuro si lo puesto un poco oscuro no sé
because
por qué
It looks a little dark and I know a little
se ve un poco oscuro y sé un poco
unfocused
desenfocado
I was just playing that outside of
precisamente estaba tocando eso fuera de
camera but it seems that it is not
cámara pero parece ser que no sea
because let's see the same thing, it's not dirty either.
porque a ver lo mismo tampoco sucio la
camera to see but let's see if I have for
cámara a ver pero a ver si tengo por
here something
aquí algo
has visited to clean the camera
ha visitado para limpiar la cámara
moment it seems it looks like a little
momento parece se ve como un poco
blurry if not anymore
borroso si ya no
it seems to look a little blurry
parece que se ve un poco borroso
let's see a rag
a ver un trapo
I need something to clean the
necesito algo con lo que limpiar la
camera hunger
cámara hambre
Let's see, here I have a shirt, let's see
a ver aquí tengo una camisa a ver
and cleans empty and so cleans empty and
y limpia vacías y así limpia vacías y
Eduardo, thank you very much to Eduardo.
eduardo muchísimas gracias a eduardo te
I want a lot, well, let's see. Let's go.
quiero muchísimo bueno a ver vamos a
start with the mess, don't let's see now, we see
empezar con el lío no a ver ahora se ve
It might look the same but it's okay
mejor se ve igual pero no pasa nada
could turn on the light bulb to know
podría encender el foco saber
could you make the background it would look perfect
podrías hacer el fondo se vería perfecto
what happens is that
lo que pasa que
We don't feel like it, the truth is, it's not going to get involved.
no nos apetece la verdad no va a meterse
the truth
la verdad
no sometimes it will be true to extend a little
no a veces será verdad extender un poco
I don't care if it's a little worse but
me da igual que sea un poco peor pero
with a more intimate light it is worth it
con una con una luz más íntima vale con
a more intimate light and atmosphere
una luz más íntima y con un ambiente
here more intimate branding many
aquí más íntimo brando muchísimas
Thank you, handsome, welcome
gracias guapísimo bienvenido
the thing thank you very much to see you know
la cosa muchísimas gracias a ver sabéis
why I'm not going to put the focus because
por qué no voy a poner el foco porque
I'm going to watch the Dallas video and the video
voy a ver el vídeo de dallas y el vídeo
It lasts two hours, it lasted an hour I think
dura dos horas duró una hora creo
so we go here for
entonces nosotros vamos vamos aquí por
at least two hours minimum then
lo menos dos horas como mínimo entonces
two hours with the fire in the face
dos horas con el fuego en la cara la
It's true that it's going to be, you know, two hours.
verdad que va a estar tú sabes dos horas
In the fire the caraba statute looks ugly
en el fuego la caraba estatut se ve feo
I don't care, I'm showered with complaints
me da igual me da lluvia de las quejas
Of the kids I already know what I do
de la chavalería yo ya de las que haga
I'll pass the kids on to the forum
la chavalería me lo paso por el foro de
the balls so clearly I saw it and I went
las pelotas así de claro lo viese y voy
to make a shitty border and I'm going to make
a hacer un borde de y voy a hacer
a piece of [ __ ] edge in fact I'm going to before
un borde de de hecho voy a antes
to start with the Dallas video
de comenzar con el vídeo de dallas
I'm going to show you some studies because yesterday in
voy a poneros unos estudios pues ayer en
the ones I have in total
los que tengo total
totally right
totalmente la razón
[Music]
[Música]
and
e
I think he put it yesterday spoiler to see in
creo que lo puso ayer spoiler a ver en
the theater spoiler I want to tell you this is
el teatre spoiler quiero deciros esto es
what I was going to say I'm not going to sweat
lo que iba a decir no voy a sudar
You have very bad words for her
tienes muy malas palabras para la
kids lately already soul but to
chavalería últimamente ya alma pero a
see the one who takes it personally with the
ver el que se dé por aludido con las
words will surely be for something
palabras será por algo seguramente habrá
many people from the youth who do not know
mucha gente de la chavalería que no se
take it as alluded to by the words but
dé por aludido por las palabras pero
Look, I'm here 24 hours a day.
mira si yo estoy aquí 24 horas
working I think I work 25 hours
trabajando creo que trabajo 25 horas
I think I work 25 hours a day, okay?
creo que trabajo 25 horas al día vale
trying to please everyone and
intentando complacer a todo el mundo y
that it has and that it has content all
que tenga y que tenga contenido todo
kind of people are worth what they can't
tipo de personas vale lo que no puede
being is apart from the complaints all the
ser es aparte de que las quejas todo el
day the chat of course for members
día el chat por supuesto para miembros
when it is more of youtubers when it is
cuando esté más de youtubers cuando es
the topic of the kids is full of brats
tema de los chavales se llena de niñato
the chat and it has to always be alone
el chat y tiene que ser siempre solo
member that there is no one who does it anymore
miembro eso ya lo no hay nadie que lo
can deny no or that is there is someone who is there
pueda negar no o sea hay alguien que hay
someone who can deny that it is impossible
alguien que pueda negar que es imposible
when they are green U2 songs to the PSE or
cuando sean temas de u2 verdes al pse o
From YouTube you have to put the chat only
de youtube hay que poner el chat sólo
member
miembro
Is there anyone who can deny it?
hay alguien que lo pueda negar hay
someone who wants to discuss them
alguien que los quiera discutir
girl theme terios brats okay I'm going to
tema de niña terios niñatos vale voy a
keep doing it and I will continue
seguir haciéndolo y voy a seguir
doing it because I like the content
haciéndolo porque me gusta el contenido
of the youtubers too but in my
de los youtubers también pero que en mi
content ends up leaning more towards me
contenido acabe inclinándose más yo
spend more time on other types of targets
dedique más tiempo a otro tipo de target
that he supports me more because with logic it is worth it and
que me apoye más pues con lógica vale y
I'm going to explain why
os voy a explicar el porqué
before coming
antes de venir
before reaching the lordship
antes de llegar a la señoría
before Mrs. Eri arrived at this already
antes de llegar la señor eri a esto ya
This comes from years ago, this comes from years ago
viene de años esto ya viene de años
How many times have we discussed here in
cuántas veces hemos discutido aquí en
the live the theme that all the
los directos el tema de que todos los
strangers from all walks of life
extraños desde todos los estratos se
filled with comments from many
llenaban de comentarios de muchos
fillings starts at minute 8 which almost
rellenos empieza en el minuto 8 que casi
not talking about the video I just came here to
no habla del vídeo sólo vengo aquí para
find out about the click of the video of the topic
enterarme del clic del vídeo del tema
of the title how many for how many years
del título cuantos durante cuántos años
we have had that controversy
hemos tenido esa polémica
tell me
decidme
for how many years have we been here
durante cuántos años hemos tenido aquí
the discussion of the extracts that this
la discusión de los extractos que esto
It's not a video channel this is a
no es un canal de vídeo que esto es un
channel of live extracts and that I
canal de extractos de directo y que yo
I put in the title something that is the
pongo en el título una cosa que es la
more striking but they are narrower than me
más llamativa pero son estrechos de mi
straight
directo
how many
cuantos
how many years since you started direct
cuántos años desde que iniciaste directo
on youtube exactly starts every
en youtube exactamente empieza todos los
videos start at minute 8 start at minute 8
vídeos empieza en el minuto 8 empieza el
minute 9 that there is an [ __ ]
minuto 9 que haya un
that there is an [ __ ]
que haya un
filling up my videos or several
llenándome los vídeos o varios
[ __ ] filling my videos with
llenándome los vídeos de
comments start at minute 10
comentarios de empieza en el minuto 10
starts at minute 8 that makes my
empieza en el minuto 8 eso hace que mis
videos are harmed because because they are
vídeos se perjudiquen porque porque se
They position less because they have less
posicionan menos porque tienen menos
audience retention whoever wants to see
retención de audiencia el que quiera ver
How do I make the extracts?
los extractos como los hago
that I see it and that I don't see it
que lo vea y el que no que no lo veo
They are throwing beef to ghosn a sail because
están tirando beef a ghosn a vela porque
He told private things about the problem
contó cosas privadas sobre el problema
from Dallas with area and Juan are a lie
de dallas con área y juan son mentira
now we're going to see it
ahora lo vamos a ver
Now now we are going to watch the whole video and
ahora ahora vamos a ver todo el vídeo y
I want to make it clear
lo quiero dejar claro
everyone and even the [ __ ] is uploaded
todos y hasta la sea subo los
excerpts from the live shows are not that
extractos de los directos no es que
I want the theme of the video
quiero es que el tema del vídeo
I just want to see you watch video
solamente quiero verte ver vídeo
now I take and add
ahora cojo y añado
I add to part of the extracts of the
añado a parte de los extractos de los
direct and I add the format of the
directos y añado el formato de las
quick news 2-minute videos
noticias rápidas vídeos de 2 minutos
where I tell you the news and even how
donde te cuento la noticia y hasta como
with your honor look at the comments
con la señoría mira en los comentarios
now look at the comments now which ones
ahora mira los comentarios ahora cuáles
are
son
videos that don't even last five minutes
vídeos que no duran ni cinco minutos
They entertain no one, it's a shame about the
entretienen a nadie es una pena lo del
new format
nuevo formato
the format is very ugly
feísimo el formato
churra was seriously doing
churra en serio estaba haciendo
precisely what he criticized so much about
precisamente lo que tanto criticaba de
other channels an unedited video and
otros canales un vídeo sin edición y
above now without even a picture just
encima ahora sin ni siquiera imagen sólo
four crappy photos this is not the one
cuatro fotos cutres este no es el
quality standard I expected from you
estándar de calidad que esperaba de ti
You're going to get screwed, okay the day that
os vais a tomar por culo vale el día que
I have the diagram, you put class to the CEO
yo tenga el diagrama metéis clase al ceo
I will do it on YouTube because there are topics that
de youtube lo haré porque haya temas que
I'm interested in things like today's and that I
me interesen como el de hoy y que me
entertain the day I am four
entretenga el día que yo tenga cuatro
hours to dedicate to YouTube and have
horas para dedicarle a youtube y tenga
four themes of the lordship or two of the
cuatro temas de la señoría o dos de la
kids I'm going to [ __ ] I saw myself with the
chavalería me voy a me vi con la
Your Honor, okay, your Honor, give it to him now.
señoría vale la señoría le dan la ya
everyone likes the video if they like it
todo a todos le dan like si el vídeo el
scope gives you light again if you take the
ámbito le vuelve a dar light si coges el
You summarize it again directly
directo lo vuelves a resumir de
next time they see him again
siguiente lo vuelven a ver le vuelve a
mandalay if the video for an hour sees
mandalay si el vídeo durante una hora ve
in the hour-long video if the
en el vídeo de una hora entera si el
video lasts two minutes, three people watch it
vídeo dura dos minutos se lo ven tres
Sometimes they don't complain about anything
veces no ponen queja de nada
If you don't want to see something, then don't see it.
que no quiere ver algo pues no lo vea
some have the members icon
algunos tienen el icono de miembros
totally but what I think is that this
totalmente pero que a mí es que este
This is not supporting you or the one who doesn't
este esto no es apoyarte o el que no
Whoever supports me will go to another channel.
apoye el que me apoye se va a otro canal
Okay
vale
the one who supports me, the one who doesn't like me
el que me apoye el que no le gusta
support moving to another channel
apoyar que se vaya a otro canal
Do you understand me? With this I do not mean
me entendéis con esto no quiero decir
that he goes as a salc or I'm going to follow him
que vaya de salcé o lo voy a seguir
doing now when I have time
haciendo ahora que cuando tenga tiempo
to choose whether to dedicate myself to this or
para elegir si dedicarme a esto a
dedicate myself to something else and surely
dedicarme a lo otro pues y seguramente
Well, my content is more directed to
pues mi contenido va más dirigido a
change target
cambiar de target
but I'm not lying or anything
pero no estoy mintiendo o sea
literally
literalmente
how many years have we been together
cuántos años llevamos
talking and debating here in the
hablando y debatiendo aquí en los
direct from the topic of a is that many
directos del tema de a es que muchos
fillers is that eight minutes talking about
rellenos es que ocho minutos hablando de
filler and two minutes talking about the topic
relleno y dos minutos hablando del tema
from the video and now I upload a format
del vídeo y ahora subo un formato
also news
también de noticias
which is not to leave the extracts
que no es dejar el de los extractos
and there they also spread hatred for throwing at
y ahí también estiran odio por tirar a
the kids I like lying around
los chavales que me gusta tirados de
this hand then the subject brats this
esta mano entonces el tema niñatos esto
is what it brings
es lo que trae
the girl theme everything that comes after the
el tema niña todo lo que trae luego el
online theme the online theme
tema del online el tema del online
don't visit them because this video was from
no las visitas porque este vídeo era de
This video was over 24 hours ago and this
este vídeo hacía más de 24 horas y este
video an hour ago okay but look at
vídeo hacía una hora vale pero mirad en
5,000 visits in 5,000 visits
5.000 visitas en 5.000 visitas
thanks to Alicia, gorgeous in five thousand
gracias a alicia guapísima en cinco mil
visits the lady has already given
visitas la señor hería ya ha dado
2300 light
2300 light
and
e
In five thousand visits the lordship has already
en cinco mil visitas la señoría ya ha
Given 2300 people complain about everything no
dado 2300 la gente se queja por todo no
There is nothing that suits them and they cry for
hay nada que les venga bien y lloran por
everything, nobody, I don't care, I grew up, that's it
todo nadie me da igual crecí que ya está
to throw to throw for the people who
que tirar para tirar para la gente que
He supported me more in the end, this is a gesture
me apoye más al final esto es un gesto
mutual of
mutuo de
mutual facts
hechos mutuos
5000 but I'll explain it later
5000 pero que luego lo estoy explicando
because then I don't want what he does is
porque luego no quiero lo que hace es
that you only do directly for Mr. Wounded
que sólo haces directo para señor hería
They only make videos of the Lordship
es que sólo hacen vídeos de la señoría
Here is the explanation for that
aquí está la explicación para que
you see what I see is
ustedes vean lo que yo veo es
so that you can see what I see
para que ustedes vean lo que yo veo
5200 visits the lordship is already giving you
5200 visitas la señoría ya te está dando
2300 light or 50 percent
2300 light o sea un 50 por ciento
in 20 thousand 1200 life victory many
en 20 mil 1200 life victoria muchas
thanks in 20 thousand 1200 life
gracias en 20 mil 1200 life
There is something that doesn't add up, right?
hay algo que no cuadra verdad hasta que
What I'm saying is that this doesn't mean that
lo digo es que esto no quiere decir que
I'm going to stop making videos for the
yo vaya a dejar de hacer vídeos para la
animal kid I'll just do it
chavalería animal simplemente haré lo
that I like to do what I like
que a mí me gusta hacer lo que me
interested in playing and you already know
interese tocar y ya sabes
but you understand that I am here
pero que entendáis que yo estoy aquí
working 25 hours a day
trabajando 25 horas al día
25 hours a day and what if suddenly a
25 horas al día y que si de repente un
I have little time to dedicate to it every day
día tengo poco tiempo para dedicarle a
youtube then obviously I will pay attention to
youtube pues evidentemente haré caso a
the demand not to the content that is more
la demanda no al contenido que sea más
supported
apoyado
you understand me, look at you, look at me
me entendéis fíjate tú fíjate tú ves yo
pleasing every novelty that happens
complaciendo todo novedad que pasa le
The extracts seem very long because of the
parece muy largo los extractos por le
I will also add content that is
voy a añadir también contenidos que sean
quick videos with the salsa singer and that's it
vídeos rápidos con el salsero y punto
There are also complaints about going out to drink
hay también hay quejas por ir a tomar
for ass to me to me what you give me
por culo a mí a mí lo que me das de
think is that the girl content had
pensar es que el contenido de niña tenía
Well, it brings the interior and that's even what it is
pues trae el interior y hasta es lo que
It makes me think and it has already been demonstrated in
me da de pensar y ya se ha demostrado en
the chat I be with 5,000 or 6,000
el chat yo sea con 5.000 o 6.000
people on television to the CEO
personas en teles al ceo
with five or six thousand people the cha
con cinco mil o seis mil personas el cha
You can have it open, dude, it's okay.
se puede tener abierto tío no pasa nada
but it is to make a salsa video
pero es es hacer un vídeo de salsa de
youtube and you have to put it in mode
youtube y hay que ponerlo en modo
member god does not fail
miembro dios no falla
Well, let's see first of all before
bueno a ver en primer lugar antes que
nothing second
nada segundo
first of all
antes que nada
the topic of cards and this this
el tema de las tarjetas y este este
video if I saw it yesterday from Dallas the one that
vídeo si lo vi ayer de dallas el que le
has made to area Juan counting would give it
ha hecho a área juan contando lo daría
maybe not
igual no
[Music]
[Música]
I didn't see it, okay, I didn't see that one because
no lo vi vale ese no lo vi porque
It is effective and I get up
resulta efectivo y me levanto
that today I wake up and see that at seven
que hoy me levanto y veo que a las siete
In the morning, Dallas bar uploaded a video
de la mañana subió bar dallas un vídeo
of an hour that I think is a live show
de una hora que creo que es un directo
I said, well, let's see.
he dicho bueno lo vemos
we see it live we go to it
lo vemos en directo nosotros lo vamos
commenting on why because I don't have
comentando por qué porque no tengo
no editor available today and apart
ningún editor disponible hoy y aparte
It doesn't even make me record a video for him.
tampoco me pone a graba un vídeo para el
main channel of this I wanted to have
canal principal de esto quería haber
recorded a video there about the subject
grabado allí un vídeo sobre lo del tema
of Carlota Corredera and others parked
de carlota corredera y demás aparcada
main but had no editors no
principal pero no tenía editores no
the subject of uncle cards
el tema de las tarjetas tío
the subject of cards there are people who
el tema de las tarjetas hay gente que se
has put into question the issue of
ha puesto a poner en duda el tema de
late or that if it can be unsafe your
tarde o que si puede ser inseguro tus
bank card data and others
datos de las tarjetas bancarias y demás
Here, halfway, I'm going to put the
aquí así media mente yo voy a poner la
hand in the fire and I'm sure I won't
mano en el fuego y seguro que no me
I think that in that sense there will have been
quemo en que en ese sentido habrá tenido
all kinds of care are worth it and turn out to be
todo tipo de cuidado vale y resulta ser
that the payment is made through a
que la el pago se hace a través de una
payment platform, meaning that the data
plataforma de pago o sea que los datos
they are not going to be happy later
no van directamente a estar feliz tarde
From Colombia, sorry for asking something
desde colombia perdón por preguntar algo
Off topic, but what do you think of Alex?
fuera de temas pero qué opinas de álex
the boss who left me like a log
el capo que me quede como una patana el
Naval is the boss, he sees me as a kick
naval es el capo me ve como una patada
in the turnip that we have already talked about many times
en el nabo que ya hemos hablado muchas
sometimes no good let's watch this video
veces no bueno vamos a ver este vídeo
because I stopped following water and air and no
porque deje de seguir agua y ar y no
I will talk more about this topic and don't tell him
hablaré más de este tema y no le digan
nothing
nada
I have seen this
he visto esto
I don't want anyone to say anything to him
no quiero que nadie le vaya a decir nada
to any of the people involved in
a ninguna de las personas implicadas en
this direct
este directo
I have decided to summarize it because nothing else
he decidido resumirlo porque nada más
At the end of the live stream there were already people
terminar el directo ya habían personas
taking the click out of context and re
sacando el clic de contexto y re
uploading it I didn't like it in the end
subiéndolo no me ha gustado al final
answer this because it is a topic that
responder a esto porque es un tema que
I would have preferred to leave it in oblivion
hubiese preferido dejarlo en el olvido
Thanks to Marisol, gorgeous.
gracias a marisol guapísima
but I found out about this the hard way
pero me enteré de esto de la peor manera
I'm so tired welcome many
estoy tan cansada bienvenida muchas
thanks to you she is tired and I was able to
gracias a ti está cansada y me pudo la
rage now it's done and there is no
rabia ahora ya está hecho y no hay
backtracking so better have the info
vuelta atrás así que mejor tener la info
I didn't find out all of this about the whole thing
entera no todo me entere esto de la
best way worst way that it is
mejor manera de la peor manera de que se
alters
altera
let's see
vamos a ver
then it is tempered with that
entonces es templado con eso
I am a member of all your channels, a kiss
soy miembro de todos tus canales un beso
lordship
señoría
two people
dos personas
with a roof was reacting to people
con techo estaba reaccionando a gente
lying, criticizing, being Osh
mintiendo criticando estar de osh
After my unfiltered Dallas video
después de mi vídeo en dallas sin filtro
that I recommend you see and I found
que os recomiendo verlo y me encontré
with this surprise
con esta sorpresa
to all this the give it if I am not
a todo esto la da si es que no la estoy
seeing me but to all this you give it and
viendo conmigo pero a todo esto la das y
in this way
de esta guisa
the day like this - I support basket now
la da de esta guisa - basket apoyo ahora
The day is here, come see the roll that's there
la da está aquí pasa ve el rollo que hay
behind let me go back for a
detrás déjame ir para atrás de un
wait this this is pissing me off
momento esto esto me está cabreando
now
ahora
that
qué
but can't
pero no puede
Let's see, dude, I'm telling you very seriously.
vamos a ver tipo te lo digo muy en serio
okay it's very simple it's very simple here no
vale es muy simple es muy simple aquí no
It's a matter of no one helping me, it's that
es cuestión de que nadie me ayude es que
They themselves are the ones who earn the most
ellos mismos son los que más ganan de
agreement they themselves are the ones who most
acuerdo ellos mismos son los que más
money the creators earn are those who
dinero ganan los creadores son los que
They make more money from that plan to help me
más dinero ganan ese plan de ayudarme
because if not the creators themselves are
porque si no los mismos creadores son
those who earn the most money within being
los que más dinero ganan dentro de estar
From Osh they earn more inside by far
de osh con diferencia ganan más dentro
to be among those who win on Twitch
de estar desde los que ganan en twitch
in percentage
en porcentaje
Javi, I believe you, just like wings are
javi yo te creo al igual las alas son
Seriously towards Maria, thank you very much.
serios hacia maría muchísimas gracias
Good time we saw the Ansa Vela video
buena vez el vídeo ansa vela lo vimos
I think it was the last video we saw
fue creo que el último vídeo que vimos
on my secondary channel it actually opens
en mi canal secundario de hecho abre
you know I think that with you know the
sabes yo creo que con sabe la
journalist quoted many thanks to me
periodista citó muchísimas gracias yo
I think that with the knowledge that it is not being done
creo que con sabe la no se está
referring with no disrespect
refiriendo con ninguna falta de respeto
you know what Dallas is a little bit like
sabe para que se el dallas está un poco
[Music]
[Música]
burned quite burned with the subject is
quemado bastante quemado con el tema es
late or and I think I should rest a bit
tarde o y creo que debería descansar un
I think I should rest a little because
poco creo que debería descansar porque
in the end the issue is late or late
al fin al cabo el tema de tarde o se va
to fix it will work and all the
a arreglar va a funcionar y todo el
roll but not from one day to the next this
rollo pero no de un día para otro esto
It's going to be a long time, so a little rest
va para largo entonces un descansito
disconnect take things more slowly
desconectar tomarse las cosas con más
calm down because it's starting to get very
calma porque está empezando a estar muy
irritated to begin with is very irritated
irritado para empezar está muy irritado
but for example this form of this type
pero por ejemplo esta forma de esta tipa
I don't know that I don't know how much she knows
no sé que no sé cuánto con sabe la no
He is telling them nothing more than that.
les está diciendo nada más los está
giving my opinion in the end to know
opinando al final saber
pages refer to me worth not in quantity
pagés me refiere vale no en cantidad
because logically this network is
porque lógicamente esta red está
starting what the [ __ ] are you telling me
empezando que me estás diciendo de
help me for the love of art
que me ayuden a mí por amor al arte de
what the [ __ ] are you talking about
qué estás hablando
Well here they refer to the topic this
bueno aquí hacen referencia al tema esto
the Videla billions
lo billones videla
Here it refers to the fact that it would not be
aquí hace referencia que no sería
help him for the love of art
ayudarle por amor al arte
man to see for the love of art not because
hombre a ver por amor al arte no porque
It is assumed that they here the problem is
se supone que ellos aquí el problema es
What I see wrong here is not the same and
el aquí lo que yo veo mal no es igual y
would have liked to participate in being of or
harían querido participar en estar de o
No, I don't believe at all that Dallas
no yo no creo para nada que dallas le
have stopped following because they don't
haya dejado de seguir porque no
participate in being of you worth in fact
participen en estar de os vale de hecho
I have not participated either until now
yo tampoco he participado hasta el
moment that does not mean that I have it
momento que no quiere decir que le tenga
the mountain gate and that it will not be so
la puerta serrana y que no vaya a serlo
It's just not the time
simplemente que no es el momento
It's not the time, I have nothing to upload.
no es el momento no tengo nada que subir
I have nothing to contribute nor do I have anything
no tengo nada que aportar ni tengo nada
that at least even if it is to pass
que por lo menos aunque sea para aprobar
and with me dallas we have created ourselves
y conmigo dallas nos hemos creado de
The fact is that we did not create ourselves
hecho es que no que nos hayamos creado
It's just that I don't love the night
es que yo es que no amo la noche
I was just talking to him about
precisamente estuve hablando con él de
another thing
otra cosa
and his attitude has not changed
y es que no ha cambiado su actitud
with me not a single iota
conmigo ni un solo ápice
You don't understand me even a bit
me entendéis ni un solo ápice
The issue is not that
el tema no es que
has stopped following you or is
les haya dejado de seguir o que esté
pissed off at them for
con ellos por
don't participate it's late because I don't
qué no participen es tarde porque yo no
I have participated and I already say it with me in
he participado y ya lo digo conmigo en
Nice PNV has given us a go, it would be good if
niza pnv ha dado vamos estaría bueno que
you get angry because I can't upload a
te enfades porque yo no pueda subir un
video to your new platform no
vídeo a la plataforma tuya nueva no
The ugly thing here is not responding to being
aquí lo feo es no responder a ser
ghosting okay now I'm going to extend it to you
ghosting vale ahora os voy a extender
plus my opinion on the Westin
más mi opinión sobre lo del westin
boxing 256 casting fantasize nothing missing
boxing 256 casting fantasear nada faltar
less to finish is another thing true
menos a terminar es otra cosa verdad
missing would be something else is not what the
faltar sería otra cosa no es lo que las
annoying that I didn't answer him
molestas que no le contesté
then we can debate today is good or
luego ya podemos debatir hoy está bien o
bad for them to participate or not to participate is
mal que participe o no participen es
late or hey because he's going to promote you
tarde o oye porque te va a promocionar
for the love of art and now he says that
por amor al arte y ahora da la dice que
There is no moral art here because they go
no está acá moral arte porque ellos van
to win and that is another debate apart
a ganar y eso es otro debate aparte el
the two of them got angry until they reached the forest or it
mosqueo de los dos hasta el bosque o lo
that what he has done they owe him
que lo que ha hecho que le deben de
continue that I do not answer you now well
seguir que no le conteste ahora bien yo
personally javi oliveira based on
personalmente javi oliveira en base a
other experiences I've had
otras experiencias que he tenido al
past
pasado
If someone doesn't answer me, I don't give it to him.
a mí si alguien no me responde no le
would give so much importance
daría tanta importancia
I simply treat people as
simplemente yo trato a las personas al
the same level that those people treat me
mismo nivel que esas personas me traten
This has happened to me in the past and
a mí yo en el pasado esto me ha pasado y
You know I'm not going to mention
ustedes lo sabéis no voy a mencionar a
Nobody because I don't want to mention anyone
nadie porque no quiero mencionar a nadie
but you know that I arrive a
pero ustedes sabéis que yo llego un
moment when I thought I had
momento en el que yo me creía que había
some people who were very good friends of mine and
unas personas que eran muy amigas mía y
I thought that we were friends
yo me creía que yo que éramos amigos
but then when the time comes
pero luego a la hora de la verdad
anything that I wrote to her did not
cualquier cosa que la escribía no le
I was telling something that they did this to me
contaba algo tenía que me hacían esto
even not answering me for weeks
mismo no contestarme durante semanas
Okay, so it's not bad at all.
vale entonces no es nada malo no
answer each one has his own thing you have
contestar cada uno tiene su rollo tienes
a mess and he's busy with his things, okay
un lío y está liado con sus cosas vale
each one went out with their things what happens
cada uno salía con sus cosas lo que pasa
is that you have to realize when
es que te tienes que dar cuenta cuando
A person is either a friend of yours or he or she is not.
una persona es amiga tuya o no lo es me
understand but get angry and let him continue.
entiende pero enfadarte déjale seguir yo
I wouldn't stop following unless I
no dejaría de seguir a no ser que me
do something ugly
haga algo feo
for the simple fact that I don't
por el simple hecho de que no me
I answered, well, what I would do would be me.
conteste pues yo lo que haría sería yo
I treat you at the same level as you treat me
te trato al mismo nivel que tú a mí
You understand me, what I do here is
me entendéis es que yo aquí lo que yo
I think Dallas has believed that Juan
creo es que dallas se ha creído que juan
and Ari were friends of his for the simple reason
y ari eran amigos suyos por el simple
the fact that they have apologized
hecho de que se hayan pedido disculpa de
that they have made a stop right to see
que hayan hecho un pare derecho a ver
friends friends not the person with whom
amigos amigos no la persona con la que
I have spent time enjoying that is more than
me he pasado disfruto eso está más que
forgotten worth
olvidado vale
and today I put a person with a
y a día de hoy pongo una persona con un
cordial treatment, you follow me, I follow you
trato cordial tú me sigues yo te sigo
when we do a live show alone and such
cuando solos hacemos un directo y tal
but now about talking and all that nonsense
pero ya de hablar y de todo el rollo ese
well no
pues no
It has been seen that it is not worth it
se ha visto que no vale
If I said I don't accept free pressure
si yo dijera no admito gratis presiones
the whole issue of debating the topic of
todo el tema de debatir el tema de
to debate about
debatir de
the topic of debate he
el tema de debatir él
whether it is free or not is free to see
el si es gratis o no es gratis a ver al
end
final
participating in being a bear does not
el participar en estar de oso no
Depending on the creator, it can be done
según que creador puede ser hacerle un
please give the hours in a favor to
favor a dar las horas en un favor a
dallas as much as not so you're going to
dallas por mucho que no así que tú vas a
charge because you are going to upload a video here
cobrar porque vas a subir un vídeo aquí
and then you're not going to do it for free no
y entonces no lo vas a hacer gratis no
you're going to do it for the love of art because
lo vas a hacer por amor al arte porque
You're going to get paid for that video, okay?
tú vas a cobrar por ese vídeo vale si
Juan Bas or both to charge for the video
juan bas o ambas a cobrar por el vídeo
of rise
de suba
now it will be windy we will all see it
ahora hará aire lo vamos a ver todos nos
Don't worry, I'm going to watch the whole video.
preocupéis voy a ver el vídeo entero voy
Let's see Twitter, I'll see everything from there.
a ver el twitter de ahí voy a verlo todo
but I'm going to see it in order
pero voy a verlo en orden
Let's see if Juan Guarnizo is really
a ver realmente si juan guarnizo
will participate in being in Osh would be for
participará en estar de osh sería por
do Dallas a favor because because
hacerle el favor a dallas porque porque
I think he plays
yo creo que juega
It is late or it is a solution for the
es tarde o es una solución para los
YouTube problems for us people
problemas de youtube nos gente que gente
that has problems with youtube with the
que tiene problemas con youtube con la
monetization with certain videos that
monetización con ciertos vídeos que
They have controversial content and they do not
tienen un contenido polémico y no les
monetize not then people channels of
monetizan no entonces gente canales de
controversial channels of criticism that you
polémicas canales de críticas que te
They have a video and you can upload it there.
tienen un vídeo y lo puedas subir ahí no
It's late or you have it there as a channel
es tarde o lo tienes ahí como un canal
secondary as we have already said it is not
secundario ya lo hemos dicho no es
replace your YouTube channel or
sustituir tu canal de youtube ni
YouTube competition is a complement
competencia de youtube es un complemento
you understand me more, listen really
más me entendéis oye de verdad
studying in my opinion leave me with
estudiando en mi opinión dejarme ya con
that I continue watching the video no
que siga viendo el vídeo no
Keep watching the video Javi, there's more.
sigue viendo el vídeo javi que hay más
Well, let's see, I'm giving my opinion and
bueno a ver estoy dando mi opinión y
I will continue watching no no
seguiré viendo no no
I can
puedo
It is that later he explains it well
es que más adelante lo explica bueno
Dallas will explain his version and I will explain
dallas explicará su versión y explicaré
mine I can't or I don't
la mía no puedo o no
I'm not going to be the real thread
no voy a ser el hilo de verdad
the thread of what you are going to lose is going to disappear.
ya se va a ir el hilo de lo que os
I was explaining
estaba explicando
I've already lost track of what I was doing
ya se me ha ido el hilo de lo que estaba
explaining
explicando
sincerely
sinceramente
I am giving my opinion
estoy dando mi opinión
I can see
puedo ver
I ask your permission
os pido permiso
another listen first to the one from Dallas
otra escucha primero la de dallas
You lack information, what information do I need?
te falta información que información me
missing to give if surely this of it
falta a dar si seguramente esto de lo
that they are going to talk here I know from
que vayan a hablar aquí lo sepa desde
weeks ago before you that
hace semanas antes que ustedes que de
The truth is that it really pisses me off.
verdad me toca en los
I hadn't lost track of what
no había perdido el hilo de lo que
I was explaining sincerely
estaba explicando sinceramente
sincerely
sinceramente
Of course the video lasts a
pues claro sea que el vídeo dura una
hour and that I would have to see the whole thing
hora y que lo tendría que ver entero
Jorge, thank you very much, but I'm putting
jorge muchas gracias pero estoy poniendo
in context what I think is not
en contexto lo que yo pienso no
What I think is that playing yes yes
lo que yo pienso es que jugar sí sí
participate in this art or not
participar en este arte o pues no lo
I would do it completely free for the love of
haría completamente gratis por amor al
art would surely take one
arte seguramente se llevaría una
financial compensation for the video that
compensación económica por el vídeo que
would go up but Juan really didn't like it
subiera pero realmente a juan no le
interested
interesa
because it doesn't have a content
porque porque no tiene un contenido
controversial because it has no problems in
polémico porque no tiene problemas en
youtube because it has no problems in your
youtube porque no tiene problemas en tu
and because it doesn't have monetized videos and
y porque no tiene vídeos de monetizado y
a million things no
un millón de cosas no
Are you going to let me finish or what?
me dejáis que termine o qué
Here is what is wrong on Juan's part
aquí lo que están mal por parte de juan
do not answer
no contestar
I should have answered Dallas
tenía que haber contestado a dallas
from the first moment instead of
desde el primer momento en vez de
having said yes, yes, well, later on
haberle dicho sí sí pues ya más adelante
which should have pleased him since
lo cual tenía que haberle contenta desde
the first moment of the look seems to me
el primer momento da la mirada me parece
very good idea your platform
muy buena idea tu plataforma
I hope it is very successful and I will mention it.
ojalá tenga mucho éxito y la mencionaré
in my live
en mi directo
but I'm not going to participate because I
pero yo no voy a participar porque a mí
I'm not interested, I have two channels, I'll go.
no me interesa yo tengo dos canales voy
to start uploading content on Facebook
a empezar a subir contenido en facebook
and I have tweets
y tengo tweets
I just don't know
es que no sé
and for things like that exactly cat
y por cosas así exactamente cat
Seriously, he's seeing this and he uploaded it.
en serio que esté viendo esto el subió
since the video started reacting
desde que empezaba a reaccionar el vídeo
check out our chat
míranos el chat
I know there is an hour of video I'm going to watch it
yo sé que hay una hora de vídeo la voy a
see the whole thing I connected at 4
ver entera me he conectado a las 4
afternoons and I have asked for food instead of
tardes y me he pedido de comer en vez de
instead of eating my wife's cooking
en vez de comer la comida de mi mujer
to watch the entire hour of video
para ver la hora entera de vídeo
is that you are missing data or when of the
es que te faltan datos eo cuando de los
data I will answer those data
datos contestaré a esos datos
and we are with him and we are with the chat
y estamos con él y estamos con el chat
of imaginary member that we were
de miembro imaginario que estuviéramos
open
abiertos
Dallas is getting a little toxic
dallas está volviendo un poco tóxico
Dallas wasn't looking a bit good
dallas no se estaba viendo un poco
Toxic Dalla has the personality that
tóxico dalla tiene la personalidad que
have but it is not toxic dallas are very
tenga pero no es tóxico dallas están muy
burned by the project that is
quemada por el proyecto que está
doing
haciendo
and I should disconnect a little on days
y debería desconectar un poco los días
to return with a different mentality
para volver con otra mentalidad
spot
punto
but what data am I missing?
pero qué datos me faltan
Yes, I surely have more data than
si seguramente yo tenga más datos que
you
ustedes
Here is the problem that I see, the problem
aquí el problema que le veo el problema
that I see him
que le veo
is
es
that Juan should have told him about
que juan tenía que haberle dicho del
first moment gallant I'm not interested in the
primer momento galán no me interesa la
platform is a very good idea it will come
plataforma es muy buena idea va a venir
very good to other youtubers who have
muy bien a otros youtuber que tengan
problem for the content but I
problema para el contenido pero yo
I don't have any problem exactly
precisamente no tengo problema
so in a way the fact that
entonces en cierto modo el hecho de que
Juan says hey for supporting him for giving him a
juan diga oye por apoyarle por darle un
a little bit of promo
poquito de promo
I'm going to take a video that I have of
voy a un vídeo que tenga de
monetized that surely does not have
monetizado que seguramente no tenga
monetized and I'm going to upload it sooner or later
monetizado y lo voy a subir tarde o
Well no, he hasn't done it because because
pues no no lo ha hecho porque porque
probably don't have any video of
seguramente no tenga ningún vídeo de
monetized
monetizado
surely if you have a video of
seguramente si tiene un vídeo de
monetized does not matter if it is
monetizado le da igual que esté de
monetize prefers to have it than monetize
monetizar lo prefiere tener de monetizar
but having it on your YouTube channel I
pero tenerlo en su canal de youtube yo
I have a video of a monetized game
tengo un video de monetizado un game
over I don't know if it was Jairo's or which one it was
over no sé si era el de jairo o cuál era
One of the ones you don't see I have it
uno de los que no ves lo tengo yo de
monetized
monetizados
but I'm not going to delete it from my channel
pero no lo voy a borrar de mi canal de
youtube to upload in is late or
youtube para subir en es tarde o
I prefer to have it because on my channel
prefiero tenerlo porque en mi canal de
I want to have YouTube there, but here
youtube quiero tenerlo ahí pero aquí
Here then the problem that I see is
aquí luego el problema que yo veo es
having done this Goettingen and not
haberle hecho el goettingen este y no
I should have answered that I might tell you the same.
haberle contestado que igual os digo
I'll tell you one thing, I don't
igual os digo una cosa yo no me
[Music]
[Música]
I wouldn't have I wouldn't have
yo no me hubiera yo no me hubiera
offended because you didn't answer me if I
ofendido porque no me conteste si me
They ghost Victor Hernandez a lot.
hacen ghosting víctor hernández muchas
thank you
gracias
the issue of them not answering you, well
el tema este de que no te contesten pues
I would have been offended a couple of times ago
yo me hubiera ofendido hace un par de
years looked thank you very much
años lucía muchas gracias
Let's see, I don't want to mention anyone.
a ver es que no quiero mencionar a nadie
but it happened to me
pero a mí me pasó
It happened to me with people who I
a mí me pasó con personas que yo me
They thought she was a very good friend of mine
creían que era muy amiga mía
and they weren't my friends, they just loved me
y no eran amiga mía solamente me querían
for dad interests are worth when I gave myself
para papá intereses vale cuando yo me di
realize that such then I stopped
cuenta de que tal pues yo dejé de
answer them at the same level
contestarles al mismo nivel
I don't know if I'm explaining myself why
no sé si me estoy explicando por qué
lie bordering on the boy and
mentir rayando mucho con el chavo y de
TRUE
verdad
I don't know if I don't know if I'm explaining myself
no sé si no sé si me explicando
Juan doesn't benefit as much from the size
juan no se beneficia tanto por el tamaño
that has
que tiene
clear the fact that Juan went up
claro el hecho de que juan subieron
videos late or would it be because of making the
videos tarde o sería por hacerle el
favor that would not be for the love of art
favor que no sería por amor al arte
because some money would be taken that way
porque algo de dinero se llevaría así
But Juan probably doesn't give a damn.
pero seguramente le se la suda a juan no
you are interested
le interesa
but tell him I'm not interested
pero díselo no me interesa
I'm not interested
no me interesa
I have fifth exclusivity
tengo exclusividad quinta de
exclusivity interests me, it doesn't interest me
exclusividad me interesa no me interesa
maybe tomorrow many
a lo mejor el día de mañana muchas
Thanks to the best tomorrow I will
gracias a lo mejor el día de mañana me
to monetize a video I want to upload a
den monetiza un vídeo quiero subir un
video on youtube is not possible and it
vídeo en youtube no se puede y lo
I use something like this
utilizo yo que sea algo así
but tell him that I, for example, that
pero díselo es que yo yo por ejemplo que
I have more of a relationship with Dallas
yo tengo más relación con dallas
I told him in his diet that I told you
yo se lo dije en su dieta la que yo te
I support what I can retweet hands
apoyo lo que pueda las manos retuitear
made videos talking about afternoon or
hecho hacer vídeos hablando de tarde o
Promoting them is fine, but I can't
promocionarlas vale pero que yo no puedo
upload video right now because it is not
subir vídeo ahora mismo porque es que no
It suits me well because I have nothing to
me viene bien es que no tengo nada que
I can't think of what to upload, no
subir no se me ocurren a que subir no
I have problems with monetization if
tengo problemas con la monetización si
I have some old monetized videos
tengo algún vídeo de monetizado antiguo
I'm not interested in removing it from my channel to
no me interesa quitarlo de mi canal para
put it there right now that I don't have
ponerlo ahí yo ahora mismo que no tenga
that you don't want us to go up and that you don't
que subir no nos quieres y que no lo
is going to be
vaya a ser
for example I spoke with him it is good that
por ejemplo hablé con él es bueno que
let's do something, let's do a little chat
hagamos una cosa hacemos como una charla
an interview and they edited it for me
una entrevista y las hubo editada a mi
channel and upload the entire thing to the stadium to
canal y la subo entera al estadio para
move people later or whatever is in
mover gente más tarde o lo que esté en
my hand
mi mano
to lend a hand sincerely I
por echarle una mano sinceramente yo
Right now, knocking on wood, I don't
ahora mismo tocando madera pues no me
It's good, I have it
viene bien tengo
5 channels I'm uploading to
5 canales a los que estoy subiendo
I have no problems with monetization of videos
vídeos no tengo problemas monetización
I'm not going to upload a video about SEO salt.
no voy a subir un vídeo de sal seo de
7 months ago there because it is monetized
hace 7 meses ahí porque se monetiza
now it's worth it
ahora vale
and that's it and with me I don't know it's not that we
y ya está y conmigo no sé no es que nos
has angered is that he has not changed nor
haya enfadado es que no ha cambiado ni
one and I know him when he feels like it
una y yo conozco a él cuando le sienta
something is wrong, it hasn't changed one bit
mal algo no no ha cambiado ni un ápice
his attitude towards me
su actitud conmigo
I mean, if you're angry with me, well no, well no.
o sea enfada conmigo pues no pues no
upload a video, understand me
sube un vídeo me entiende
Here the problem is late
aquí el problema es tarde
This is free, I'm talking about you winning
esto gratis estoy hablando de que ganes
your more money from the next than you
tu más dinero del próximamente del que
you're winning the platforms what the [ __ ]
estás ganando las plataformas qué
you are saying but here
estás diciendo pero acá
Hawas is not interested, this is for waters
hawas no le interesa esto es para aguas
he's not going to make more money, I don't know.
no va a ganar más dinero no lo sé
This is pissing me off. This is really pissing me off.
esto me está cabreando esto sí que me
I don't know, I don't want to get off either.
está que no sé tampoco me quiero bajar
This is because I don't know the monetization either.
esto porque tampoco sé la monetización
in the afternoon or how it goes or how much they cost
de tarde o cómo va ni cuánto valen
getting pissed off because as I think it is
cabreando porque como yo creo que es
moment
momento
He is a person with whom that is a lie
es una persona con la que eso es mentira
Okay, I say again, that's purely
vale vuelvo a decir eso es puramente
lie is purely lie is given in
mentira es puramente mentira se da en
be of the highest percentage to the
estar de os más porcentaje a los
creators of those who give on YouTube or in
creadores de los que dan en youtube o en
big manga tweets of subscribing diversity
tweets big manga de suscribir diversidad
It's fake, okay.
es falso vale
we started countries [ __ ] false that
empezamos países mente falso que
There is a gang that after months a
hay una pandilla que después de meses un
kiss, Azkoyen is really disgusting
besito que azkoyen está dando mucho asco
but
pero
I wanted to say hello and try to
quería darte un saludo y tratar de
Let's cheer you up and celebrate the seven months
animarte celebremos los siete meses
together thanks to successes there are not too many
juntos gracias éxitos no hay demasiados
Ghosting Michelle Yellow was other people
ghosting michelle yellow era otra gente
too much team
demasiado team
so agustn a fat person read and
así agustín una persona gorda ley y
then a person close to this person
luego una persona cercana a esta persona
She was the one in charge of speaking
era la que se encargaba de hablar
with me talking to him about doing it
conmigo de habla con de hacerle el
dirty work not to mention socializing
trabajo sucio no hablar de relacionarse
with the entities with the people of
con las entidades con las gentes de
down but good it is when you give it
abajo pero bueno está cuando te das
realize that someone is making you loot
cuenta de que alguien te hace botines
because maybe it doesn't have the same
porque a lo mejor no tiene el mismo
level that you thought was friendship or
nivel que tú te creías que de amistad o
be it to me, to me, to my Juan and Ari
sea a mí a mí a mi juan y ari
as much from them to me as I to them to
tanto de ellos a mí como yo a ellos a lo
It's better not to answer each other in a month
mejor no nos contestamos en un mes a un
message
mensaje
A couple of months ago I wrote to you
hace un par de meses le escribí a haría
some whatsapp and there he answered me
unos whatsapp y allí me contestó le
He kept talking and didn't answer my questions.
seguía hablando y no me contestó las
conversations what happens is that
conversaciones lo que pasa que se
suddenly lower down two or three years ago
amparan para abajo de repente hace dos o
three weeks ago he sent me a waza, oh yeah
tres semanas me mandó un waza ay si
Sabino will continue as a friend because already
sabino seguirán cuánto amigo porque ya
friend calls me friend I don't know what to do
me llama amigo amigo no sé qué hacer
When I didn't answer him, I answered the
cuanto no le contesté le contesté a los
two or three days
dos o tres días
but I don't see her continuing because I will be
pero yo no la veo de seguir pues yo seré
I will give the people the same as the
yo le daré a la gente lo mismo que la
people give me
gente me dé a mí
You understand me and that's it, there are times when you
me entendéis y ya está hay veces que te
They may or may not sit well
pueden sentar mal o no
God willing, illuminates the importance that
dios quiera ilumina la importancia que
they would simply make me box
me hicieran boxing simplemente lo
I would have done the same or
hubiera hecho yo lo mismo o lo
we would have strained at the same level, that's it
hubiéramos tensar al mismo nivel ya está
Well, you are not my friend what I wanted
pues no eres mi amigo lo que yo quería
who was my friend and they even know the plan
que era mi amigo y hasta saben plan
But you know that I send you all my support
pero sabes que te mando todo mi apoyo
but counting them was a lot
pero es que contarlas fueron muchas
times swimming there is me too
veces nadando ya hay a mí también
places but I know it too
lugares pero es que yo también se lo
I make people so I could teach my
hago a gente así yo pudiera enseñar mi
WhatsApp screen that obviously
pantalla de whatsapp que evidentemente
I can't but come on this is pointless
no puedo pero vamos esto es sin sentido
Mr. mobile and I look at it and the mobile
señor móvil y lo miro y el móvil lo
I have silenced here for a good day
tengo aquí silenciado por día de bien
when one and I go in to see if good
cuando uno y me meto a ver si bueno
because I tell you the VAT or Alan of how many
porque os diga el iva o alan de cuántas
Sometimes they don't write me anything
veces no me escriben algo
If I don't context it and I write it later
si no lo contexto y el escribo yo luego
suddenly a week for something else
de repente a la semana por otra cosa
different the cinabe answered him that it is
diferente el cinabe le contestaba que es
that a lot of people talk to me
que a mí me habla muchísima gente al
end of the day
cabo del día
lots and lots of people
muchísima muchísima gente
then there are people who have
entonces hay gente que tiene
preferences for example I have the
preferencias por ejemplo yo le tengo las
active guasa notifications
notificaciones en guasa activas
only to my family, to my two best
solamente a mi familia a mis dos mejores
friends and from youtube to give it salty and
amigas y de youtube a darla salada y
forward and to Ivan I believe like the others
alante y al iván creo como los demás
It is normal that I understand that it does not matter
es normal que yo entiendo que dar igual
and this is that this is that this
y es que esto está que es que esto
Only people who understand it will understand it
solamente lo entenderá la gente que el
space for us, you don't have this
espacio para nosotros esto ustedes no lo
you will understand
vais a entender
Auro, for example, has never given me gout.
auro por ejemplo nunca me ha hecho got
zinc and it will be more complicated even though everyone
zinc y estará más liado aunque todos
they
ellos
Now for example I send him an audio
ahora por ejemplo yo le mando un audio
right now pig is not left loose and
ahora mismo cerdo no se quedó suelto y
He will surely answer me within two hours.
me lo contesta seguro a las dos horas
but the bottle
pero la botella
but what does that mean by the
pero qué quiere decir eso por la
importance or the degree of closeness that
importancia o el grado de cercanía que
you have with a person
tienes con una persona
and that's it
y ya está
It has been great and virtual thanks to a
era ha sido grande y virtual gracias un
dress of
vestido de
six months let's go guys I'm going to [ __ ]
seis meses vamos a chicos voy a putear
wait a moment with the multiplications, okay?
un momentito a las multiplicaciones vale
I'm not going to show them for a moment
no voy a mostrarlas un momentito de las
notifications
notificaciones
and I'm going to read them little by little
y las voy a ir leyendo poco a poco
because
porque
Dallas is very tired of the lack of
dallas está muy cansado la falta de
sleep makes things not get lost
sueño hace que las cosas no se pierden
Clearly that's all when you rest
con claridad eso es todo cuando descanse
you will see things differently but
verá las cosas diferentes sino
From affection a harvest should be taken
del cariño debería tomarse una cosecha
very burned gotor theme change burn or me
muy quemada gotor tema change arde o yo
I read Yadi makes me ghost in for installing or
leí yadi me hace ghost in por instalar o
face twisting with laughter heart
cara revolviéndose de la risa corazón
red let's see if I understand because I have
rojo a ver lo entiendo porque yo tengo
much fewer followers and it overwhelms me
muchos menos seguidores y me agobia
I'm not able to answer everything
contestar todo no soy capaz
how normal and ordinary is going to get us
qué normal y corriente nos va a sacar lo
better he thought he was more of a friend
mejor el se ha creído que era más amigo
Juan's ideology of what it was and
de juan ideario de lo que era y
simply because of what it looks like it has been
simplemente por lo que se ve que ha sido
It is Juan and Ar and in the past they are from the
es juan y ar y en el pasado son de las
typical people who have messed with
típicas personas que se han metido con
he
él
Today they have changed their attitude towards
hoy por hoy han cambiado su actitud con
many people
mucha gente
I also apologized publicly to her
la pedí disculpas públicamente además a
I know that they have it in good condition
mí me consta que lo tienen en buena
on top of looting and that Juan thinks very
encima saquear y que juan piensan muy
well from dallas but they don't consider it a
bien de dallas pero no lo consideran un
friend considers him a companion in
amigo lo considera un compañero en
colleague not a friend
colega no un amigo
and even with this and I want I want
y hasta con esto y quiero quiero
really react to this and then the
realmente reaccionar esto y luego las
I put with sounds it seems good worth in
pongo con sonidos parece bien vale en
absolute
absoluto
what doesn't work
lo que no funciona
Thank you very much, subscribe, let's go
gracias muchas gracias suscríbete vamos
Let's also see why if this continues
a ver también porque si esto continúa
As I think it will continue I am going to
como creo que va a continuar me voy a
piss off but average series pisses off but
cabrear pero serie media cabrea pero
Seriously, but seriously, let's listen to this
serio pero serio vamos a escuchar esta
[ __ ] [ __ ] let's see
a ver
literally
literalmente
I literally can't believe it
literalmente no me lo puedo creer
a problem I've never done
un problema que yo nunca he hecho
public you are telling me that the others
público me estás diciendo que los otros
two have started telling others
dos se han puesto a contarle a otros
influences behind things to me
influencias por detrás las cosas me
you're [ __ ] joking right?
estás vacilando verdad
a problem that I have never made a [ __ ] of
un problema que yo nunca he hecho
public mind that simply hurt me
mente público que sencillamente me dolió
Personally, I think the others can be
a mí personalmente los otros se pueden a
tell other influencers about it behind their backs
contarlo por detrás a otros influencers
I'm not going to keep listening to this because
no voy a seguir escuchando esto porque
If this is true, it's going to piss me off.
esto si es verdad me va a cabrear
That is to say that it is believed that it is believed I think that
o sea que se cree que se cree creo que
It is believed that confirm I believe that it is
se cree que confirmar me creo que se
She thinks Gonzalez is talking to her about the
cree que gonzález la está hablando del
topic because he has told it to everyone else
tema porque se lo ha contado a ar igual
people know nothing, the century is known
personas se sabe nada se sabe el siglo
has said he has not said it directly
ha dicho no lo ha dicho directamente
but let's see people take it for granted
pero vamos a ver la gente la da por
I had all three and it's true.
hecho a ver yo tenía los tres y verdad
That's what we saw
es que eso lo vimos
I think putting in the tri exactly
creo que poner en el tri exactamente
expect exactly what you are looking for
espera lo que busca exactamente
is that believed
se cree eso
indeed look
efectivamente mira
let's see the conclusion people give
a ver la gente la conclusión la gente da
for doing this for this
por hecho esto por esto
truth
vera
If any creator I have a month with
si algún creador con el que tengo de mes
open wants to get this out
abiertos quiere entrar esto fuera
October does not want to enter either that I
octubre no quiere entrar también que me
notify me directly by or by
avise a mí directamente por o por
private and someone tells him to vegetate and
privados y alguien le dice vegetar y
Ari Juan was invited but never
ari juan fueron invitado pero nunca
They said nothing indeed
dijeron nada efectivamente
Okay, so people have taken it for granted.
vale o sea la gente lo ha dado por hecho
white and in a bottle I don't know what
de blanco y en botella no sé a qué
we are not talking about stupidity
estupidez no estamos hablando no
but there is this tweet
pero está este tuit
the live show he did saying, I'll see for myself
el directo que hizo diciendo yo tú verás
what I have stopped following because they have
lo que he dejado de seguir porque han
done this and done this and apart from that
hecho esto y este hecho y aparte que
everyone has seen in public
todo el mundo ha visto en público a
who has stopped following us like
quien ha dejado de seguirnos en plan
The candle bag is based on that
bolsa vela se basa en eso
and it's going to piss me off a lot
y me va a cabrear mucho
the
las
I help you for the love of art only
te ayudo por amor al arte solamente
then we get angry about that no
entonces quedamos enfadados por eso no
I understand it because it's like I don't know what
lo entiendo porque es como no sé qué
you wait, I don't know what you expect from two
esperas ya no sé qué esperas de dos
people we don't have in your colleagues
personas que no tenemos en tus colegas
not even that they are two people in
ni siquiera que son dos personas en
the
los
terms of the two
términos de los dos
it looks great
estupendo parece
think
pensar
to think that they are actually going to loan
para pensar que efectivamente van loan
It's like I expect that
es como si yo espero que
disrespecting Dallas to what
faltando el respeto a dallas a lo que
is saying with knowing is simply
está diciendo con saber es simplemente
that Ari One is two people with whom
eso que ari one son dos personas con las
that are on good terms points
que están en buenos términos puntos
point that
punto que
follows very few people and one realizes
sigue a muy poquita gente y uno se da
ounce candle account is not that it is
cuenta de la onza vela no es que esté
talking about the topic because it has been
hablando del tema porque se lo haya
said Juan Mari Gonzalez is speaking
dicho juan mari gonzález está hablando
of the topic because everyone was
del tema porque todo el mundo estaba
talking about the topic on all channels
hablando del tema sean todos los canales
of salt or they told Alexa turn off t
de sal se o lo dijeron alexa apaga t
11 thank you very much
11 muchísimas gracias
people have put two and two together for the
la gente ha sumado dos más dos por las
words he said in the video
palabras que él dijo en el vídeo
former
anterior
a load of rubbish
una chorrada
to discuss these absurdities
a discutir estos absurdos estarlo
obstruct because 500 people me
obstruir por que 500 personas me
They sent that tweet, I hadn't seen it.
mandaron ese tweet yo no lo había visto
the dallas twitter saying effectively
el twitter dallas diciendo efectivamente
as if to say that Ari hadn't said
como diciendo que ari no había dicho
nothing like it no
nada igual no
unfollows them and everyone notices
los deja de seguir y todo el mundo se da
Note that I don't understand how the hell either
cuenta que no tampoco entiendo cómo
is that the moment you stop following
es que en el momento que dejas de seguir
someone everyone notices
a alguien todo el mundo se da cuenta
I also tell them it seems that they have the
también los digo parece que tienen a la
alert some kind of alert set okay
alerta algún tipo de alerta puesta vale
and even before releasing the video,
e incluso antes de que sacar el vídeo la
people were theorizing about banier and
gente estaba teorizando sobre banier y
Of course people were noticing
claro la gente se estaba dando cuenta de
that had given like this and took out a video
que había dado así y saca un vídeo sacó
a video saying and on top of that I have
un vídeo diciendo y encima que los he
unfollowed I don't know how much then
dejado de seguir no sé cuánto entonces
I don't know how to add two plus two either, that is.
yo no sé sumar dos más dos tampoco o sea
that he almost said it could tell us
que casi que lo dijo podría decirnos
and
y
Look first all that is false I have already
mira primero todo eso es falso ya he
said a lot of times is not the plan
dicho un montón de veces no es el plan
of help in an alarming way, that's worth it
de ayuda de forma alarte vale eso lo
first of all is only the very first of
primero de todo es solo primerísimo de
They all earn more stamps than I do.
todo ganan más sellos de lo que gano yo
By far more stamps will arrive than
con diferencia llegarán más sellos de lo
that other platforms do that
que hagan otras plataformas que al
At first things obviously don't work out
principio obviamente las cosas no se
earns the same as other people in
gana igual de lo que gana otra gente en
YouTube or normal tweets because the same
youtube o en tweets normal porque igual
that you when you started on YouTube
que tú cuando empezaste en youtube
when you started twitch you weren't there
cuando empezaste twitch no estabas
earning so much you had to dedicate
ganando tanto tuviste que dedicarle
time and effort and then earn more
tiempo y esfuerzo y para luego ganar más
money is not logical how you are going to earn more
dinero no es lógico cómo vas a ganar más
on a platform that has just come out
en una plataforma que acaba de salir
you will have to dedicate time and effort
tendrás que dedicarle tiempo y ganas
to then start to go up but if I am
para luego empezar a subir pero si estoy
talking about that you earn more within
hablando de que ganas más dentro de
be from what you gain from others
estar desde lo que ganas de otras
platforms in percentages colleagues that
plataformas en porcentajes colegas que
talk later
hablamos
Dallas is affected, I hope they can
a dallas ee lo ve tocado ojalá puedan
I think they will fix themselves
arreglarse yo creo que sí que se van a
fix I trust that if I will do it
arreglar yo confío en que si yo haré lo
possible when you are in the most things
posible cuando esté en las cosas más
older faces as much as possible to mediate
caras mayores lo posible por mediar
Let's see that Dallas is very busy right now
a ver que dallas ahora mismo está muy
irritated I would say
irritado yo diría
and he is taking a lot of account
y está echando mucha mucha cuenta
is also paying a lot of attention to the
también está haciendo mucho caso a la
people
gente
and we are probably not going to art and how it is
y seguramente no vamos al arte y cómo se
dare to compare it to merchandising
atreve a compararlo con el merchandising
that merchandising only wins one
que el merchandising solo gana una
person what the [ __ ] are you telling me and
persona que me estás contando y
This has really pissed me off because it is
esto sí que me ha porque sí que
It is confirmed to see two buoys and one
está confirmado mira dos boyas y una
thing and this look point anger is what
cosa y esto busque punto cabreo es qué
point that I think I have right now what
punto que creo que tenga ahora mismo qué
spot
punto
Dallas has been through the worst and is now
dallas ha pasado las peores y ahora está
exhausted not to understand it would be cruel is
exhausto no entenderlo sería cruel es
of course they are talking about something
claro que están hablando de algo
totally public it is up to you to offer the
totalmente público le toca ofrecer las
sorry and that's it, give him a break
disculpas y ya está denle un respiro a
What do you mean by offering an apology?
qué te refieres con ofrece la disculpa
apologize
disculparse
I don't think I said anything either.
tampoco considero que haya dicho nada
bad to
malo a
Juana I will do
juana haré
he's just complaining that he doesn't
él está simplemente quejándose de que no
they have answered it and such
lo hayan contestado y tal
the issue of whether he wins again
lo del tema de otra vez de que si gana
more will pay less on a platform that
más pagará menos en una plataforma que
they don't want to do it
no quieren hacerlo
but
pero
I'm not interested
no me interesa
right now I didn't do a single one
ahora mismo no hice ni un solo
comment on this is not a single one
comentario sobre esto es ni un solo
comment is more is more they came to me
comentario es más es más me vinieron a
ask for bits they came to me
preguntar por bits me vinieron a
ask for bits why there was
preguntar por bits que porque había
stopped following juanmi ari and
dejado de seguir a juanmi ari y
I literally skipped that and said don't do it
literalmente salté eso y dije no hagas
questions about things like that boom and the
preguntas sobre cosas así pum y los
jump you have it in the live shows
salten lo tenéis en los directos
previous I don't know when it was but
anteriores no sé en qué momento fue pero
you have the previous live videos
tenéis los directos anteriores
I think he really believes that
creo que realmente se cree que
[Music]
[Música]
what a great candle
que gonza vela
He is talking about the topic because he is
está hablando del tema porque se lo
they had told no one
habían contado a nadie
I haven't made a single comment but
no he hecho ni un solo comentario pero
not one
ni uno
and this girl knows it and I also think that
y esta tipa lo sabe y además creo que
is talking about it
está hablando de ello
whatever you have whatever you have this very
lo que tengáis lo que tengáis esto muy
into account is that you keep this very much in mind
en cuenta es que tengáis esto muy en
account
cuenta
Me when I made my video venting
yo cuando hice mi vídeo desahogándome
I didn't give names on the subject.
por el tema no di nombres no di nombres
of nothing, not even names of the
de nada ni siquiera nombres de los
scammers I did not give names of
estafadores no di nombres de
absolutely no one and when I referred to
absolutamente nadie y cuando me referí a
YouTubers who had ignored me
youtubers que me habían ignorado
according to percent one thing before
de acuerdo a por ciento una cosa antes
that he said it when he was referring to
de que lo diga cuando se refería a
YouTube that I had ignored
youtube el que lo habían ignorado yo
I think it refers to more
creo que se refiere a más
important that people are talking
importante que la gente estamos hablando
of yes of Ariguani
de sí de ariguaní
but it refers to more sure I am
pero se refiere a más seguro estoy
totally safe
totalmente seguro
I have no proof but no doubts either.
no tengo pruebas pero tampoco dudas no
no but it refers more
no pero se refiere más
It refers to more than just water or area
se refiere a más no sólo agua ni área
I talked about many people saying that a tag gives you
hablé de muchos dicen que un tag te
I have no contact with this one that more than
cuento sin contacto con está que más de
100 I think I said or 90 how many did I say
100 creo que dije o 90 cuántos dije yo
that I had contacted I don't know how to ask for
que había contactado no sé pedir que
I had contacted many, do you remember?
había contactado muchos os acordáis
true confirm in fact I know of another
verdad confirmar de hecho yo sé de otra
which he also stopped following because of
a la que dejó de seguir también por lo
same
mismo
I don't know if he will say it but there are other people
no sé si lo dirá él pero hay otra gente
at the head of following the people he has
a la cabeza de seguir la gente él ha
said nothing Diogenes thank you very much
dicho nada diógenes muchas gracias
where please those who have seen the
donde por favor los que hayáis visto el
video okay never give names
vídeo vale nunca di nombres
never worth it never gave names and this girl
jamás vale nunca di nombres y esta tipa
specifically later on he says things
específicamente más adelante dice cosas
that I consider would deserve some
que considero sí merecerían unas
apologies like reading private messages and
disculpas como leer mensajes privados y
say that I will hate the coach
decir que haré odia al dt
Well
bueno
Now I see it, I say people are counting
ahora lo veo yo digo gente está contando
specifically the story of juanar and
específicamente la historia de juanar y
specifically
específicamente
How can you really have it, I tell you
cómo puedes tener de verdad os lo digo
very seriously how could you have had the
muy en serio como podéis haber tenido la
little shame about a problem that I don't even know about
poca vergüenza de un problema que yo ni
I wasn't even going to say anything about it
siquiera iba a decir nada al respecto
literal but nothing about it because no
literal pero nada al respecto porque no
I was going to say nothing at all
iba a decir nada de nada sencillamente
unfollow them and that's it, I didn't say anything
les deja de seguir y punto no dije nada
What bothered me was that I didn't say anything at all.
lo que me molestó no dije nada de nada 0
0 and specifically this chick speaks
0 y específicamente esta tipa habla
specifically from Juani Har
concretamente de juani haré
very good very good do you want me to continue
muy bien muy bien queréis que siga
walking around telling [ __ ] behind the back
andando contando por detrás
when I literally go to the magnificent and I go
cuando literalmente al magníficas y voy
to say anything is worth it even if it is going to
a decir nada vale ni siquiera si va a
say nothing is that more do not even them
decir nada es que más ni siquiera les
I said nothing, I just unfollowed them and
dije nada sólo les deje de seguir y
point nor do I recriminate them nor do I
punto ni ni les recrimine ni les
I didn't chase them or follow them at all.
perseguía ni les fui detrás nada de nada
they are worthless
de nada valen nada
and it turns out that
y resulta que
I think he made a mistake in the
yo creo que se ha equivocado en el
example of playing has not said anything
ejemplo de jugar no ha dicho nada
Yes, I believe that this
si yo creo que ésta
I don't know if you know Juana Ari but if you do
no sé si conocerá a juana ari pero si lo
They know they don't have much confidence nor
conocen no tienen mucha confianza ni
relationship or anything like that
relación ni nada de ese estilo
evidently it will surely be the same
evidentemente al igual seguramente se le
have told their friends not only
haya contado a sus amigos no solo
comment with someone has commented to
comenta con alguien se lo ha comentado a
friends but what is Juan
los amigos pero lo que es juan
when asked live about
cuando le preguntaron en directo sobre
the subject tried to give a joad cape to
el tema intentó dar un capotazo joad a
I love it very much, I think it's very good.
la lo quiero mucho me parece muy buena
person I hope nothing happened
persona espero que no haya pasado ningún
bad vibes anyway I'm not going to do it
mal rollo igualmente yo no lo voy a
unfollow I don't know what
dejar de seguir no sé qué
that as people were putting it in
que como la gente estaba poniéndolo en
twitter because start putting in
twitter porque empezar a poner en
Twitter whether you're ahead or staying behind
twitter vayas por delante o por quedarse
let Juan continue, I know he doesn't care
deja seguir a juan yo sé que no me lo
I think yes, I don't know how many, I didn't answer anything
creo sí no sé cuántos no respondía nada
I didn't see anything
no vi nada
000 but now but man leave it
000 pero ya pero hombre dejarlo de
continue adding to the video of the es
seguir sumado con el vídeo de los es
late or if I already know that we are going now two more
tarde o si ya sé que vamos ahora dos más
two okay I'm going to read it to you I'm going to read it to you
dos vale os lo voy a leer os lo voy a
read because I'm going to read it to you
leer porque os lo voy a leer por
of course I'm going to read it
supuesto lo voy a leer
eye
ojo
August 11
11 de agosto
August 11th I am with ar and talking
11 de agosto estoy yo con ar y hablando
We are talking about August 11th
de 11 agosto estamos hablando de hace
more than 2000 and now I don't like this
más de 2000 y ahora no me gusta esto de
God always brings up conversations
sacar conversaciones dios siempre
Aris and Javier and uploaded a screenshot
aris y javier y subió una captura
talking to her not about the obvious topic
hablando con ella no del tema obvio
things speak to them in private
las cosas les hablan en privado se
They must remain private unless
tienen que quedar privado a no ser que
one that the other has to use it for
uno que el otro tenga que usarlo para
reply
responder
This was the last thing I spoke to the
esto fue lo último que hablé con la
beautiful bag would be very cool that
preciosa de bolsa estaría muy cool que
before things were invented
antes de que no se inventaron cosas se
They will ask me
me preguntarán
September 20, 2020 or I would make it very
20 de septiembre de 2020 o la haría muy
well how are you
bien qué tal tu
Well, the truth is, there is no need to think about this.
pues la verdad no hay que pensar en este
type of content at the moment but if
tipo de contenido por el momento pero si
I'm quite interested in it later on
más adelante me interesa bastante
Thank you very much for hiring me
muchas gracias por contratarme
also a beautiful perfect greeting
igualmente un saludo precioso perfecto
Carlos Baez
carlos báez
look
mira
[Music]
[Música]
with fact
con hecho
with this
con esto
It's just that things have to be talked about, God.
es que las cosas hay que hablarlas dios
Let's see, look, I know what's happening to him.
a ver mira yo sé lo que le está
offering Ari to Ghosn here by sail, I don't know
ofreciendo aquí ari a ghosn a vela no sé
If you are the vine, it is worth it
si usted es la vid ya vale
point number one point number one what
punto número uno punto número uno lo que
I said, so Ari hasn't told him anything.
he dicho o sea ari no le ha contado nada
in fact, Gonzalez Gonzalez has them
de hecho a gonzález gonzález las ha
taken out with knows he is talking about the
sacado con sabe las está hablando del
topic because we were all talking about it
tema porque lo estábamos hablando todos
the salsa singer's channels and the entire internet
los canales del salsero y todo internet
ok but point number 2
vale pero punto número 2
Here Ari is offering Ghosn Abel
aquí ari le está ofreciendo a ghosn abel
to join the platform very safely
a unirse muy seguramente a la plataforma
from webber to the pri
de webber al pri
to the pri
al pri
sure and then you will see you can upload
seguro y entonces lo veras puedes subir
videos or whatever you want and
vídeos o todo lo que te dé la gana y
then you know the law says no
entonces con sabe la ley dice que no
Thank you very much for hiring me but no
muchas gracias por contratarme pero no
I'm interested in this very thing that I had
me interesa pues esto mismo lo que tenía
What should they have done with Dallas?
que haber hecho ellos con el dallas
answer him and say look, I'm not interested
contestarle y decir mira no me interesa
I appreciate it so much that I don't
te lo agradezco tanto está que no me
interested
interesa
that more bet and something more
que más apuesta y algo más
I recognize that I am the person
reconozco que soy la persona
in following a conversation I have always
en seguir una conversación siempre me ha
seemed impossible to follow the thread
parecido imposible seguirle el hilo a
whoever it may be
quien sea
and I think the biggest complaint I get from
y creo que la mayor queja que recibo de
the people around me never do it
la gente de mi alrededor nunca lo hago
with bad intentions or because they are bad people
con mala intención ni por ser mala gente
apologies
una disculpa
You're going to get wet if you keep watching the video.
te vas a mojar si sigues viendo el vídeo
you could watch it all alone and then
podrías verlo completo a solas y después
If you want to make a video, a hug, dear.
si quieres hacer un vídeo un abrazo cara
kissing with smiling eyes I don't know what
besando con ojos sonrientes no sé a qué
You mean Maya, not that nonsense that
te refieres maya no de tontería esa que
watch a one-hour video now
vea ya un vídeo de una hora sola
months agreed I'm talking about others
meses de acuerdo estoy hablando de otras
different things that have nothing to do with
cosas diferentes que no tienen nada que
to do with the topic with Aryans of a thing of
ver con el tema con arios de una cosa de
that she defended Kenya and some stuff like that
que ella defendía a kenia y un rollo así
and I started talking about beating him but
y yo me puse a hablar de batirle pero de
It's well worth the tip of the text, I tell you why
bien vale la fia del texto les digo por
true tell me something release this court that
cierto dime algo suelte esta corte que
I dropped the ex taco that I told you to send me
suelte ex taco que te mande que me
you did all the 2 ting and it tells me now
hiciste todo el 2 ting y me dice ahora
I answer that I'm in string, worth 11
te respondo que ando en string vale 11
Since August I have never returned to you.
de agosto no me volvió nunca jamás a
reply
responder
Even what you are going to see now is worth it
hasta lo que vais a ver ahora vale el
longest string of his life
string más largo de toda su vida
two and a half months of streaming that doesn't
dos meses y medio haciendo stream que no
can reply to a [ __ ] text and
puede responder a un puñetero texto y
eye eye eye is that I want to give a very
ojo ojo ojo es que yo quiero dar una muy
very important clarification here I
muy importante aclaración aquí yo
I never said that what bothered me was that
nunca dije que lo que me molestó fue que
They wouldn't want to participate, it's worth what I
no quisieran participar vale lo que me
What really bothered me was the fact that neither
molestó de verdad fue el hecho de que ni
even to tell me look you know that's not the case
siquiera para decirme mira sabes que no
I'm interested in what could have happened
me interesa lo que podría haber
he just said you know that I don't
simplemente ha dicho sabes que no me
It is interesting to do this not critically
interesa hacer esto no es críticamente
sting football sting football
fútbol sting fútbol sting
Since when is it mandatory to respond to him?
desde cuando es obligatorio responderle
to someone a message no longer if I don't tell you
a alguien un mensaje no ya si no te digo
that it is mandatory rip but man that
que es obligatorio rip pero hombre que
you may feel bad or worse if you feel
te puedes sentar mal o peor si ya que
for some things and you answer and others
para algunas cosas y respondas y otras
No
no
but hey, he answers that he decided to ignore
pero oye responde que se dio a ignorar a
someone
alguien
The ritz, that is, the rip hater, has already begun
ya empezó el ritz es decir el rip hater
From Dallas, it's okay, but we'll see.
del dallas total vale pero van a ver
I simply answer you
simplemente yo te contesto
[Music]
[Música]
If they had answered like that, hey, well
si hubieran contestado del palo oye pues
I'm not interested, nothing would have happened.
no me interesa ya no hubiera pasado nada
wow, how pretty is the Chula thumbnail
qué bonita la miniatura de chula
air
aire
Although I sincerely thought I would leave the
aunque pensaba sinceramente dejaré el
direct summary but good
directo resumido pero bueno
Thank you Armando, thank you very much.
gracias armando muchísimas gracias
now I see what I do
ahora veo lo que hago
just that god
simplemente eso dios
It's just that they don't answer you
simplemente es eso que no te contestan
Well, what I tell you
pues lo que os digo
Leaving someone on seen is ugly but the
dejar a alguien en visto es feo pero el
rest of the video I think give it to the
resto del vídeo creo que darle a lo
I focus quite badly
enfoco bastante mal
leave someone on bad notice but if
dejar a alguien en visto feo pero si a
They leave me on read
mí me dejan en visto
[Music]
[Música]
It depends on the situation and in this case
depende de la situación y en este caso
I think I would do it in the past
yo creo que lo haría en el pasado
I would have been pissed off
hubiera hecho me hubiera a lo
it would have hurt me better or whatever
mejor me hubiera dolido o lo que sea
Ok, but today I know that I
vale pero hoy por hoy yo sé a mí me
They do this by not answering me on the side
hacen esto de no contestar me por lado
the same, that is, to the people who give it to you
lo mismo o sea a la gente que darle lo
same as the same thing that leaves you and
mismo que lo mismo que te deja a ti y de
return to know
vuelta saber
and it's not until people start to
y no es hasta que la gente empieza a
do this is not on twitter of
hacerlo esto no está en twitter de
I agree that he is within his rights
acuerdo que él está en su derecho
also to unfollow if not
también de dejarlo de seguir si no
wants to follow a person with whom
quiere seguir a una persona con la que
They talk to me and know
me hablan y sabe
that they are not friends
que no son amigos
again I didn't say anything I just told him
de nuevo no dije nada simplemente le
I let her and him follow me and that's it.
dejé seguir a ella ya él y ya está
you just don't talk to me, you don't talk to me
sencillamente no me hablas no me
You answer, I'll send you messages if you don't
respondes te envío mensajes si no me
you say absolutely nothing back
dices absolutamente nada de vuelta
After having helped you with everything
después de haberte ayudado con todo lo
what am I going to mention here okay
que es voy a mencionar aquí vale
It's just that he didn't give it much importance either.
es que tampoco le dio tanta importancia
let someone follow you, don't let them
dejarle a seguir a alguien no dejarle
follow him because of the fact that I don't
seguir le dio por el hecho de que no me
I answered, don't travel to him and he doesn't know either.
conteste no le viajes y tampoco sabe
I'm not going to close doors in Prague either.
tampoco voy a cerrar puertas en praga
today is a person with whom I have
hoy es una persona con la que tengo
cordiality because it is worth it at best for
cordialidad pues vale a lo mejor para
This doesn't answer me but we leave it for
esto no me responde pero lo dejamos para
something else like that, I mean I think that because
otra cosa así o sea yo creo que por
example if it were the best for me I think
ejemplo si fuera lo mejor para yo creo
that is what is wrong
que es que lo que está mal
What was wrong was the fact that there was no
lo que estaba mal es el hecho de no
answer him not to answer the topic and
contestarle de no contestarle al tema y
Be clear, hey, Dallas doesn't interest me.
ser claro oye dallas no me interesa yo
I wish you the best, don't stay as long as
te deseo lo mejor no se quedan en cuanto
I want to understand what work they do
yo quiero entiendo qué trabajo les
It would have cost which Dallas really didn't
hubiera costado cuál dallas de verdad no
I'm interested, I'm not interested in your project
me interesa no me interesa tu proyecto
or right now I can't rule it out
o ahora mismo no puedo no lo descarto en
a future and period knows but not in
un futuro y punto sabe pero no en
answer him and then send him a message
contestarle y luego le manda un mensaje
back thing because I'm sure
para atrás cosa porque yo estoy seguro
that if it was the best for a game or
que si fuera lo mejor para un juego o
for wap for anything else if you
para wap para cualquier otra cosa si le
answer
contesta
He tells me, he tells me, years I saw that you left us
me dice me dice años vi que nos dejaste
to continue and I just wanted to ask you
de seguir y solamente quería preguntarte
because obviously you are in all your right
el porque obvio estás en todo su derecho
but what really threw me off is that I
pero me sacó mucho de onda es que me
This draws attention, let's see, don't I?
llama la atención esto a ver no me
It seems good that private compensation
parece bien que la compensación privada
It is but I don't read them anymore but it's that I
es pero ya no los leo pero es que me
draws attention
llama la atención
that you don't answer a message many times
que no contestas a un mensaje muchas
times in many months
veces en muchos meses
and now at the moment that we give you
y ahora en el momento que te damos
follow if you write
follow si escribes
if you realize how folk
si te das cuenta de lo folk
I believe I have a personal opinion
yo creo haber opinión personal mía m
change everyone here, I don't give a damn
cambien todos aquí a mí me la suda
It was not leaving the seen a were
es que no fue dejar el visto un fueron
months and once Juan didn't even open the door
meses y una vez juan hasta no le abría
the WhatsApp message
el mensaje de whatsapp
that you can do whatever you want
que se puede hacer lo que quiera que no
is obliged to do so but
está en la obligación de hacerlo pero
that how did he explain this
que que como explicó esto
To Beckham, well, the three heads, I am
a beckham bien los tres cabezas yo soy
colleague of the three objectives in relation
colega de los tres objetivos en relación
with such that with them
con tales que con ellos
but but but but but I who am a
pero pero pero pero pero yo que soy una
I have a person who says things about her
persona tengo de las cosas que la dice
Clara knows
clara sabe
It's what I believe here
es que yo lo que yo lo que creo aquí
like juani ar and they have seen each other in a
como que juani ar y se han visto en un
commitment and have not dared to
compromiso y no se han atrevido a
tell Dallas that they don't want to
decirle al dallas que no quieren
participate in its platform
participar en su plataforma
because they have been afraid to stay
porque porque han tenido miedo a queda
the celebration is bad or it may be left to you
la celebración es mal o a quedarle pueda
be a video or whatever
ser un vídeo o lo que sea
many times and you feel bad
muchas veces y se siente se siente mal
you have your job you don't but it's that
tú tienes tu trabajo tú no pero es que
you are going to charge those who
vas a cobrar a quienes
points you know I don't have to give you more
puntos saben no tengo por qué darte más
explanations of you where I am
explicaciones de ti donde estando me
understand that it doesn't come to me now
entiende que no me viene a mí ahora
same as lived in star of dallas me
mismo su vivido en star de dallas me
You understand the but they would have said
entiendes el pero se hubieran dicho
Sure, listen, look, I'm not interested.
claro oye da la mira que no me interesa
that I support you I will mention it in my
que yo te apoyo lo mencionaré en mi
direct so that people know it
directo para que la gente lo conozca se
pass if it is that the fact that Juan
pase si es que ya el hecho de que juan
I guarnizo mentions late or not live
guarnizo menciones tarde o no en directo
It sure makes a lot of traffic pass through
seguro que hace que pase mucho tráfico
without having to upload a
sin necesidad de tener que subir un
video the two or three times he plays more
vídeo las dos o tres veces que juega más
late I'm sure it got traffic
tarde os seguro que le ha dado tráfico
but of course
pero claro
Right now I'm not interested in it.
ahora mismo a mí no me interesa yo lo
I have content that I delayed, Thyssen.
tengo contenido que me demoré thyssen yo
I have no problems, they pay me a fortune
no tengo problemas me pagan un pastizal
Here they pay me a lot of land and I
aquí me pagan un pastizal área ya mí
What do I want? I am a video that yes
para que quiero yo soy un vídeo que sí
what is going to give me what is going to give me money
que me va a dar que me va a dar dinero
that we are going to use my videos better than
que vamos a utilizar mi vídeos mejor que
on youtube because it was the best but what
en youtube porque era lo mejor pero que
I'm not interested in a greasy video and I don't
no me interesa un vídeo graso y no me
I'm interested but tell Alonso a lot.
interesa pero díselo alonso muchas
Thank you king
gracias rey
I believe that no one has the obligation to
yo creo que nadie tiene la obligación de
answer something or put them like that
contestar a algo ni que se les ponga así
That's why I don't care about the messages.
por ello yo el tema de los mensajes no
I like time this always happens a lot
me gusta tiempo esto siempre pasa mucho
here this does not have to do what
aquí esto no hace tiene que hacer lo que
you enjoy with someone private private
tú disfrutas con alguien privado privado
This person doesn't keep anything from you.
no se queda está persona saca algo tuyo
private, it is clear to you
privado te está claro está
I don't like the three of them that badly
no se me caen bien los tres que mal
Let's see, everyone. I think they'll get better.
todos a ver yo creo que se arreglarán
because Juan and Ari are going to have the
porque porque juan y ari van a tener la
position of settling with him right now
postura de arreglarse con él ahora mismo
gives her irritated is burned by
da la está irritado está quemado por de
late or but in the end for you the thing
tarde o pero al final para usted la cosa
They will surely speak more calmly
más tranqui hablarán seguramente
Many people think that I will do and Juan alone
mucha gente piensa que haré y juan solo
became friends with dallas to
se hicieron amigos de dallas para
avoiding a video himself was not of
evitarse un vídeo él mismo no fue de
Ariguani made peace with Dallas
ariguaní hicieron las pases con dallas
because I got myself in the middle of the typical
porque me metí yo por medio el típico
mutual friend
amigo en común
I don't know what we were talking about
no sé qué es lo que estábamos hablando
Juan and I once
juan y yo una vez
I don't know by audio or something like that we were
no sé por audio o algo de eso estábamos
talking and Juan told me hey but you
hablando y juan me dijo oye pero tú
Do you think Dallas would talk to me if I
crees que dallas hablaría conmigo si yo
I apologize, I speak to him and I
le pido disculpas hablo con él y yo
I spoke with Dallas and they spoke
hablé con dallas y hablaron
It went up because of me
subió por mi culpa
You see, I just told a conversation
veis acabo de contar una conversación
private
privada
There are times when it happens
hay veces que pasa
since the slight failure or simply that
ya que el fallo leve o simplemente eso a
not having been clear from the beginning
no haber sido claro del principio por
that is clear
eso que ese claro
and let's see, I have to tell you that
y es que a ver te tengo que decir que
Dallas is angry for the simple fact
dallas los enfadados por el simple hecho
that you do not participate in the platform
de que no participe en la plataforma
because he has made us angry with me
porque conmigo nos ha enfadado
but not that it has made us angry or that it hasn't
pero no que nos haya enfadado ni que no
however a different track with me
obstante una pista diferente conmigo
because in his day and target to my ex self
porque en su día y objetivo a mi ex yo
I gave it several options and none of my
le puse varias opciones y ninguna de mis
valid options my options were
opciones válidas yo mis opciones eran
upload the same ones are going up to
subir los mismos están subiendo a
youtube upload it there
youtube subirlo ahí
that hey something would have helped
que oye algo hubiera ayudado
anyone but the people who were with me
cualquiera que no la gente que me fuera
Let's see if it's late or if it's other people.
a ver en es tarde o será otra gente
new that they don't see me on youtube
nueva que no me ven en youtube
while
mientras
but it could not be summarized by anything
pero no se podía resumida por nada
Well
bueno
It's that things don't clarify, they don't give rise
es que las cosas no aclaran no dan lugar
to misunderstandings
a malentendidos
because I'm sure you do too
porque estoy segura de que también te
I say that I don't know if I would have
digo que no sé yo si yo me hubiera
angry because they stop answering me
enfadado porque me dejen de contestar
He simply sent them packing and even
simplemente los mandó a paseo y hasta
go out or treat me the same as them
sal o trato yo igual que ellos a mí que
we argued with you we have not
nos discutamos contigo no la hemos
[ __ ] on nothing I wish I could get us out of
cagado en nada ojalá pudiera sacarnos de
I send you a hug and hope you are very well
la duda te mando un abrazo que estés muy
well okay and then when he sent the
bien vale y entonces cuando él mandó el
message well I said okay okay I'm going to
mensaje pues dije bueno está bien voy a
tell you I don't understand why you don't know
contarte no entiendo que no lo sepas
Okay, I don't understand why you don't understand.
vale no entiendo que no lo entiendas
but the ideal is neither the block nor my team and
pero lo ideal ni la bloque ni mi team y
It was about her nor about the zero okay no
era sobre ella ni sobre el cero vale no
I said absolutely nothing about the fact that
dije absolutamente nada el hecho de que
What this woman knows is that they are
lo sepa esta tipa es que ellos por
behind they have been counting
detrás han estado contando
when you realize that it wasn't so
cuando se dé cuenta de que no era tan
It's hard to know, it's going to be an F or yes
complicado saberlo va a ser una efe o si
you have to be clear about the truth excuse
hay que ser claro la verdad excusa de
someone suffering is very weak
alguien sufrir es muy floja
I also tell you that I don't think they have
también os digo que no creo que lo hayan
made with bad intention to offend or
hecho con mala intención de ofender ni
to despise what they have not done
de menospreciar lo haber no lo han hecho
with the bad intention of offending children
con mala intención de ofender los ni
belittle them or treat them badly or that
menospreciarlo ni tratarlos mal ni que
He sits like this, they have done it to him
él se sienta así se lo han hecho
simply because they don't get it because they don't
simplemente porque no les sale porque no
They give importance to friendship in
le dan importancia a la amistad en
find her because they don't have a friendship
encontrarla porque no tienen una amistad
with a board they have done it and they have acted like this
con tabla la han hecho han actuado así
because they are not interested in the truth
porque no les interesa verdad la no
They have a very high regard for him
haberlo tienen muy buena estima ellos
They always refer to him very well.
siempre se refieren muy bien a él le
I like the Dallas videos, what I like
gustan los vídeos de dallas lo que me
Angel, thank you very much, it is something that
ángel muchas gracias que es una cosa que
It surprises me because they see the
a mí me sorprende porque ellos ven los
Dallas videos, Uncle Poal business never
vídeos de dallas tío poaló negocio nunca
You answer to jokes because it happens to you because
contestas a guasa porque te pasa por que
cooperation is lowered, it is worth stopping
se baja la cooperación vale para de
suddenly you're watching a video of Darla
repente estás viendo un vídeo de darla
because there is a certain resentment
porque hay por cierto resentimiento
I just remembered that I have envy
envidia la acabo de acordar que tengo
that I will answer your messages
que contestar los mensajes les voy a
answer pi pi pi pi and you answer him
contestar pi pi pi pi y le contestas
lies
mentiras
and they do it too
y también lo hacen
and so?
y eso
you are watching this live when you are and you are not
está viendo este directo cuando ar y no
You may deny that I also feel it
me podrán negar que a mí también me lo
make me give it the importance that I give it
hacen que darle la importancia que me dé
just as the day is already here that you
igual que ya está el día que tú me
I will answer the day you write to me
conteste el día que tú me escribas a mí
I stop and I like him very much, just like I do.
paro y yo me cae muy bien al igual yo lo
I love you very much, yesterday you made a water array
quiero mucho ayer le hizo un array agua
and I greeted him directly
y lo saludé su directo
but honestly I'm going to give it to the
pero sinceramente yo le voy a dar a la
people the same as me for my two
gente lo mismo que a mí para mis dos
worlds equal to me here this topic
mundos iguales a mí aquí este tema
This issue is not about how it is
este tema no se trata de que como está
saying with the knowledge that they are more
diciendo con sabe la que ellos son más
bigger than you that I don't know what
grandes que tú que no sé qué
Not for me, everyone is the same.
a mí no para mí todo el mundo es igual
For me it's the same as Aurum Plate Juan
para mi en lo mismo aurum plate juan
I guarnizo charisma Alan de and I don't know who
guarnizo carisma alan de y no sé quién
For me they are all the same
para mí todos son lo mismo
For me, the bandoneon was Enrique Garca.
a mí me bandoneón was a enrique garcía
I had it and I answer him and if I do
yo tuve y le contesto y si me lo
They sent play, I answer for myself all
mandaron play le contesto para mí todos
They are the same, this is not about there to this
son lo mismo esto no trata de hay a este
been context that is most important for
sido contexto que es más importante para
For me, the numbers here are streaks and there will be
mí aquí los números son rachas y habrá
a streak in which Dallas has more
una racha en la que dallas tenga más
you visit another one that has it and another one
visitas otra en la que la tenga y otra
in which whoever has it, I understand
en la que la tenga quien sea me entiendo
That's what people seem to me
o sea a mí eso me parece las personas
who measure others
que miden a los demás
by number of followers and impact
por número de seguidores y repercusión
that they have and so on
que tengan y demás
had combat
tuvo combate
- Aldridge is a piece of [ __ ].
- aldridge este un trozo de los
The rest are all the same, the opera is fine.
demás todos son iguales vale la ópera
joking, like me too
coña sea en plan a mí también me lo
do that others to me in the past already
hacen que los demás a mí en el pasado ya
Do you know of any case in which I have
sabéis de algún caso en el que me ha
past of people that I would stay my
pasado de gente que yo me quedara mi
friend I treated her and I gave a lot
amiga yo la trataba y yo entregaba mucho
for those people but those people do not
por esas personas pero esas personas no
They were talking about the door and it is true
hablaban de puerta y sí que es verdad
that at the right time it explodes and you react
que en su momento explote y reacciones
in public but because I have another series
en público pero porque a mí otra serie
of things there were other series of factors
de cosas había otra serie de factores
Okay, in this case I give you the
vale yo en el caso de éste te da el
support would not have been given if I had not
apoyo no hubiera dado si yo no hubiera
Having said nothing, I'm not going to let them continue.
dicho nada no los voy a dejar seguir
because I like them
porque me caen bien
juani ar and I'm not going to follow them just because
juani ar y no los voy a seguir porque sí
that it is true that for example there are things
que es verdad que por ejemplo hay cosas
in which it is called answer water
en las que se llama contesta agua
I asked your live shows to do it with me
le pedí a sus directos que conmigo lo
did
hizo
You understand me but it is true that you don't
me entiende pero sí que es verdad que no
He answers this, he cannot deny it, Saint
te responde esto no lo puede negar san
Juan
juan
look at the whatsapp with me and see when
mira el whatsapp conmigo y mira cuando
It was the last time he answered me
fue la última vez que me contestase a
one thing I asked you
una cosa que te pedía
that she is that I should not do it
que ella está que no me lo he de hacer
but happy tell me you don't
pero contenta me dimes a mí no me
I'm interested in this, I can't help you with it.
interesa esto a mí no puedo ayudarte en
This and until nothing happens
esto y hasta no pasa nada
But if they do it, I'll do it anyway.
pero si lo hacen al igual lo hacen yo le
give importance or simply the day that
dé importancia o simplemente el día que
write to me about it, it is not known how many
me escriba en ello no se conoce cuántos
for reading it is the same
por lear es lo mismo
you understand me
me entendéis
Uncle Mouse had brought you here
os te había traído el ratón tío
How disgusting life is to me, man.
qué asco me da la vida tío
Thank you because this is strong because it
gracias porque esto es fuerte porque lo
what is behind what is behind is much
que hay detrás lo que hay atrás es mucho
stronger in agreement which is much
más fuerte de acuerdo lo que es mucho
stronger than I answered I tell him
más fuerte de lo que respondí yo le digo
Sure, no problem, I'll answer you even if I don't
claro sin problema te respondo aunque no
I know why they catch you by surprise when
sé por qué te pillan por sorpresa cuando
I think I don't know, it's pretty obvious.
yo creo que no sé es bastante evidente
but be detailed so as not to leave any doubts
pero sé detallado para no dejar dudas al
respect as you know I am not only
respecto como sabéis yo no sólo es
Forgive me for not remembering these two
perdone para que no se acuerde estos dos
They started insulting me and calling me
se pusieron a insultarme llamarme
pedophile to say pederast to tell me a
pedófilo a decir pederasta a decirme un
a lot of nonsense publicly during
montón de burradas públicamente durante
a lot of time according to by
un montón de tiempo de acuerdo a por
true the discussion I had with her
cierto la discusión que tuve con ella
previously it is because it had been put
anteriormente es porque se había puesto
to make fun of the fact that Kimberly Loaiza was
a burlarse de que kimberly loaiza estaba
operated and there were tweets about her from 2018
operada y habían tweets de ella del 2018
that there is not so much mockery that
que no se hace tanto burlándose de que
if she had had an operation and if she had
si estaba operada y que si había tiene
an abortion and I don't know what it actually is
un aborto y no sé que de hecho es que
I have them for that we have come
los tengo para ello hemos venido
and that's why you can't argue with him about that.
y por eso no puede discutirle eso le
I said this is true you can take it out in the
dije esto es verdad puede sacarlo en el
don't leave that video recorded, that's fake
vídeo no dejes grabado eso eso es falso
Look there, but look at the sadness that it gives him
mira hai pero mira la tristeza que le da
to dallas that juan and answered him about his
a dallas que juan y le contestó sobre su
friendship
amistad
I don't understand the sadness that it gives to
no entiendo la tristeza que le da a
dallas that juan and answered him about
dallas que juan y le contestó sobre
Sudan but look at the sadness that it gives to
sudán pero mira la tristeza que le da a
dallas that john
dallas que juan
Juanes has told me absolutely
juanes que me ha dicho absolutamente
nothing
nada
But because they don't have to see him is that
pero porque no le tienen a ver es que
There is one thing here that needs to be done
es que aquí hay una cosa que hay que
understand below
entender abajo
when he said cheer up because they are not
cuando ha dicho ánimo porque no son
friends
amigos
I mean when they have Dallas as a
o sea cuando lo tienen a dallas como un
friend, meaning a friend is a person with
amigo o sea que amigo es una persona con
friends something else
amigos otra cosa
to a person with whom you are on good terms
a una persona con la que estás en buenos
terms
términos
a partner of the platform and if with
un compañero de la plataforma y si con
time has to be taken into account
el tiempo se tiene que tener cia que
whether you are friends, I don't know, well we'll see.
seáis amigos no lo sé pues ya lo veremos
this
esto
[Music]
[Música]
here
aquí
a tweet from ari responding to the hill
un tuit de ari respondiendo el cerrito
from 2019 to the fox stalker
de 2019 de 2019 al acosador del zorrito
and tells him
y le dice
about kimberly if she were so respectable
sobre kimberly si fuera tan respetable
I wouldn't be pregnant outside of the
no estaría embarazada fuera del
marriage
matrimonio
unai a misfortune as truth
unai una desgracia como verdad
the discussion before this and
la discusión anterior a esto y
logically when I said don't forget to
lógicamente cuando dije no te olvides de
review what someone else sent you above
revisar lo anterior que te mande otro
text and says now I'll answer you never
texto y dice ahora te respondo nunca
He replied, I still have a 5 because I asked him.
respondió sigo con un 5 por le pregunté
Matthew
mateo
I'm still with him, okay?
sigo con él con el rollo vale
As you know, I not only forgive you but
como sabéis yo no solo los perdones sino
that beyond that I have defended you
que más allá de eso os he defendido
publicly beyond that I never told you
públicamente más allá de que yo nunca os
attack on top of everything you gave me
ataque encima todo lo que disteis de mí
Well, it was always good, at least for me to see
pues fue siempre bueno al menos a mí ver
For some time now, you and Juan have been with me
de un tiempo para aquí tú y juan me
You have done castings quite a few times
habéis hecho castings bastantes veces
like means don't answer me okay
gusten significa no responderme vale
nothing zero most of it for nonsense
nada cero la mayoría por chorradas
I tried not to give it much importance each time
intenté no darle mucha importancia cada
who has a busy life and
quien tiene su vida atareada y
complicated but I think that
complicada pero yo creo que
I'm probably much bluer than
probablemente estoy mucho más azul que
you and yet I have always taken out
vosotros y aún así siempre he sacado
You really need time to respond
tiempo para responder os vale de verdad
I tell you, I don't think it exists today.
os lo digo no creo que exista a día de
today I don't think it exists today
hoy no creo que exista a día de hoy
no kind of streamer influence
ningún tipo de influencia streamer
youtuber or anything shittier
youtuber ni nada que tenga más
on top and work more than me and
encima y que trabaje más que yo y lo
I say it very seriously, I say it very seriously
digo muy en serio yo lo digo muy en
Seriously, and this is just to give me the cold shoulder.
serio y esto es por darme las de nada es
that none of the days he works more than me and
que ninguno días trabaja más que yo y
I can assure you of that because
eso os lo puedo asegurar porque
literally my whole [ __ ] day is neither
literalmente todo mi día es ni
not even sleep not even sleep
siquiera dormir ni siquiera dormir
many days to be working
muchos días para estar trabajando
there is no excuse for something sting
no hay excusa una excusa para algo sting
there is no excuse okay even if I am
no hay excusa vale incluso si estoy
busy I say sorry I was busy and you
ocupado digo perdón estaba ocupado y te
You are always silent, you always answer me, you always answer me
callas siempre contesta a mí siempre me
answer I'll answer later but people
contesta respondo después pero la gente
even more is more is more people
incluso es más es más es más gente
random random people who have ever met me
random gente random que alguna vez me ha
written by instagram to send a
escrito por instagram para mandar una
a video thing even for those people
cosa de un vídeo hasta para esa gente
tried to take out even for a while if not
intentó sacar ni que sea un rato si no
It is something relevant that less than giving it a
es algo relevante que menos que darle un
like is not that I leave you a like in the
like no es que te dejo un like en el
message and not even respond or
mensaje y hasta no ni responder ni
answer or answer okay and I say no
responder ni responder vale y le digo no
I like being ghosted, it seems to me.
me gusta que me hagan ghosting me parece
ugly and I don't like it when they do it to me like that
feo y no me gusta que me lo hagan como
It is logical but slaves are better not to expose
es lógico pero esclavas expone mejor no
only Juan defended himself with the tiradera of
sólo defendía juan con la tiradera de
[ __ ] I was doing to him
que le estaba haciendo
traitor of the 10 which by the way ar
traicionero del 10 al cual por cierto ar
and hates with all his soul and is worth it to me
y odia con toda su alma vale y me
I'm writing to thank myself later
escribo para darme las gracias después
to make the video about
de hacer el vídeo sobre
I feel exactly the same way as you.
se me hace exactamente lo mismo que te
It happened to me, I'll defend her and then
pasó con mi haré la defendiste y luego
I didn't even want to see you, it's logical that he gets angry
ni te quería ver lógico que se enoje
also
también
what are you talking about
de qué me habla
pax
pax
he must have been on the wrong channel or something.
no se habrá equivocado del canal o algo
No one like that is known here
aquí no se conoce a nadie así
Maybe because this guy is disgusting, okay?
puede porque le da asco a este tipo vale
not only not only that I agree but
no sólo no solo eso de acuerdo sino que
In addition to having warned him several times
además de haberle avisado varias veces
I also defended him with the Colombia thing and
también lo defendí con lo de colombia y
more rolls more rolls is that this of you
más rollos más rollos es que esto de te
I defended no ma'am when I don't see it either
defendí no señora cuando tampoco lo veo
I can't claim it or throw it in my face
yo reclamable ni que echando en cara ni
you know what I'm telling you had claimable in
sabe lo que te digo tenido reclamable en
you act made the videos you wanted
actúas hecho los vídeos que has querido
do it because you feel like doing it and you
hacer porque te da la gana hacerlo y se
also supposes why why why why
supone también por qué por qué por qué
why did you think that you were
por qué pensabas eso que estabas
saying in the videos you understand me okay
diciendo en los vídeos me entendéis vale
If we start the count in all the
si empezamos el recuento en todas las
classes that have publicly defended them
clases que les ha defendido públicamente
with the bed thing even talking to
con lo de la cama incluso hablando con
him to make sure that the things that
él para asegurarme de que las cosas que
came out were to his liking
salían eran de su agrado para
benefit you if they asked you to
beneficiarle si ellos le pidieron que le
defended if it would be a clear claim but
defendiera si sería reclamar claro pero
If she missed it, yes, but if not, they will be but
si se la perdió sí pero si no serán pero
No
no
the thing is
la cosa es
[Music]
[Música]
no, he doesn't owe them anything, he doesn't owe them anything
no le no les debe nada a él a ellos no
They owe him nothing because he has made them
le deben nada a él porque él los haya
defended
defendido
You understand me in defending it because
me entendéis en la ha defendido porque
He wanted to defend him because they wanted to
ha querido defenderlo porque han querido
make those videos because it's like I
hacer esos vídeos porque es como si yo
now I'm lame
ahora cojo
a video defending blondes from something
un vídeo defendiendo a rubios de algo
Because Rubio I think is right
porque rubio pienso que tenga la razón
something no and then I was lame and I think
algo no y entonces era cojo yo y pienso
that the blond must behave well with me
que el rubio debe portarse bien conmigo
Because if well the example is not the same
porque si bueno el ejemplo no es igual
oh well
pero bueno
The important thing here is to say if they
aquí lo importante es decir si ellos le
They have asked him to get involved
han pedido que se meta
publicly to give him a defense
públicamente para darle una defensa
public correct according to this does not suit me
pública correcta de acuerdo esto no me
benefits at all can make videos
beneficia en absoluto puede hacer vídeos
on the subject that comes out of my balls
sobre el tema que me salga de los huevos
and I'll have visitors anyway if I want
y tendré visitas de todas maneras si lo
You say because I felt like doing it, okay?
dices porque me dio la gana hacerlo vale
and to defend him because he is hurting me
y por defenderle a él porque me está
giving pity point can make videos
dando pena punto puede hacer vídeos
about what was mine damn win be it
sobre lo que era mía puñetera gana sea
totally the same, okay, and if I did it on
totalmente igual vale y si lo hice sobre
the topic of the dt also after why
el tema del dt además después de porque
I'm disgusted by that guy who is sometimes
me da asco ese tipo que a veces es
clearly traitorous I said how you
claramente traicionero dije cómo te
Someone other than you may be doing this
puede estar haciendo esto alguien que tú
you consider yourself a friend and you
mismo consideras tu amigo tu amigo y te
is doing this publicly and I
esté haciendo esto públicamente y yo de
I'm going to defend Juan publicly, fool.
tonto voy defiendo a juan públicamente
for then this so that then I realized
para luego esto para que luego me di
realize that it is literally
cuenta de que está literalmente
but literally
pero literalmente
telling other people behind their backs
contándole a otras personas por detrás
making water
haciendo agua
It's just that he's not counting what he's doing
es que igual no está contando lo por
behind these things but it gets worse
detrás estas cosas pero se pone peor
because it is much more
porque es mucho más
I am not a defender of Colombia's ass that
no soy defendí culo de colombia que
also although well he left minor
también aunque bueno se fue menor
I have also defended them many times
también les he defendido muchas veces
by public and private with wind and
por público y por privado con wind y
wind and has a very strong hatred for them and in
wind y les tiene un odio muy fuerte y en
I understand part of it but many times it has
parte lo entiendo pero muchas veces ha
said things that didn't seem right to me and
dicho cosas que a mí no me parecían y le
I have said and he has defended both of them
he dicho y él les he defendido a los dos
as an indication of the few that are carried
como indicio de los pocos que se lleva
good with wind and worth of the few and it is
bien con wind y vale de los pocos y se
has seen publicly and also by
ha visto públicamente y también por
private agreement always always
privado de acuerdo siempre siempre se
He defended himself with this and more things, but
defendió con esto y más cosas vale pero
Let's read on because it made us freak out and
vamos a ir leyendo porque hizo flipar y
the simple fact of not responding to me
el simple hecho de no responder me o
ignore me for long periods of time
ignorar me por largos períodos de tiempo
back to having spoken to you, having defended you
atrás haberos hablado haberos defendido
or now we see another one of you, well yes
o ahora vemos otro de vosotros pues sí
It bothered me and it's normal and it's normal that
me molestó y es normal y es normal que
I was upset because you can say this
me moleste porque se puede decir esta
type of a few friends has nothing
tipa de unos tantos amigos no tiene nada
what to say sorry or whatever
que decir perdona o sea
and literally don't even answer me
y literalmente ni siquiera me respondan
to tell me
para decirme
I'm not interested in that, nor that, nor that, nor
no me interesa ni eso ni eso ni eso ni
even tell me you know that Dallas is that
siquiera decirme sabes que dallas es que
I'm not interested in this, honestly.
no me interesa esto la verdad no me
interested in helping you, not critically
interesa ayudarte no es críticamente
cost at all not a damn thing
coste en absoluto ni una puñetera
answer about this
respuesta sobre esto
I keep going, I keep going because as I say it gets worse
sigo sigo porque como digo se pone peor
you'll see
vais a ver
and this is seriously embarrassing to me
y esto es en serio me da vergüenza
I feel humiliated, I really say it
me siento humillado de verdad lo digo
I looked for the radio and felt humiliated.
busque radio estando me siento humillado
from reading this that I am going to read to you
de de leerlos esto que os voy a leer a
continuation but deeply
continuación pero profundamente
humiliated and
humillado y
deeply humiliated by the lack of
profundamente humillado la falta de
respect without apparent anger guard him
respeto sin aparente cabreo guardia le
I say a while ago I offered him
digo hace un tiempo le ofrecí
I hate reading so much that I stayed to read.
qué asco me da leer me quedé a leer me
I put
puse
how disgusting I tell you very seriously what
qué asco os lo digo muy en serio de qué
disgust
asco
my stupid my mother
mi estúpido mi madre
no no no no the liberal idea is that you
no no no no la idea liberal es que te lo
I swear
juro
listen to this, this is [ __ ] awesome
escucha de esto que esto es mente
humiliating for me is precisely
humillante para mí es justamente
humiliating
humillante
I tell you, a while ago I offered it to Juan
le digo hace un tiempo le ofrecí a juan
in a totally honest way to be yours
de forma totalmente honesta ser vuestro
friend without any kind of anything or
amigo sin ningún tipo de nada ni
meeting publicly or anything, I don't
juntarnos públicamente ni nada no me
He was interested neither in fame nor in money
interesaba ni la fama ni el dinero
because I honestly said it too much
porque me sobra honestamente lo dije
because it seemed to me that we could get along
porque me pareció que podíamos llevarnos
well, in a totally honest way
bien de forma totalmente honesta
I offered to be my friend but the thing is that
le ofrecí ser mi amigo pero es que las
Friendships are not offered as if it were
amistades no se ofrecen como si fuera
today he wants to be my friend
hoy quiere ser mi amigo
I offered to be his friend.
efectivos le ofrecí ser mi amigo
but it doesn't offer us that, look
pero es que no nos ofrece eso surge mira
For example, I with Dallas
yo por ejemplo con dallas
Let's see, I wouldn't know how to say, my friend.
a ver no sabría decir hombre amigo yo
I think if not, go ahead, we are friends.
creo que si no ándale yo somos amigos a
see I don't know if friends friends a word
ver no sé si amigos amigos una palabra
huge for my friend we don't even know each other
enorme para mi amigo no nos conocemos ni
in person even but I really
en persona siquiera pero me realmente
we have many things if we are not friends
tenemos muchas cosas si no somos amigos
it's something very similar
es algo muy parecido
we have told each other things we have told each other
nos hemos contado cosas nos hemos
supported by things that are not known in
apoyado en cosas que no se saben en
public if one has been under the other
público si uno ha estado debajo el otro
I was quite the morning talking with
estaba bastante la mañana hablando con
he if one has had a problem or
él si uno ha tenido un problema o
need an opinion on something horned me
necesita una opinión en algo astado yo
I don't know if we are not friends, we are something very
no sé si no somos amigos somos algo muy
close but
cercanos pero
neither offered it to the other in fact
ninguno se lo ofreció al otro de hecho
I think but in fact I think it was
yo creo pero de hecho yo creo que era
quite the opposite when I started to
todo lo contrario cuando yo me empecé a
talking to him my idea was to listen to me that
hablar con él mi idea era escucharme que
I don't know that we're going to have a relationship
yo no me que vamos a tener una relación
cordial and such but without knowing anything
cordial y tal pero que a nada de saber
I remember what you said at the beginning
me acuerdo lo que decía al principio te
offered to be my friend
ofreció se mi amigo
that this arises from the examples there are people
que eso surge de los ejemplos hay gente
that connects there are other people who do not
que conecta hay otra gente que no
connects, understands and will look at us and
conecta entiende y nos va a mirar y nos
connect are interested in connect
conectan están interesados en conecta
with you more than a cordial relationship of
contigo más de una relación cordial de
wind and I here know this and this is
viento y yo aquí saber esta y esto es
true, okay, I feel so disgusted now
cierto vale mucho asco siento ahora
same
mismo
I feel so ashamed right now
mucha vergüenza si siento ahora mismo me
I feel totally humiliated by this
siento totalmente humillada de esto
because when he had the problem of what
porque cuando él tuvo el problema de lo
of the vale
del de vale
literally all of his friends that
literalmente todos sus amigos que de
friends have absolutely nothing worth
amigos no tienen absolutamente nada vale
because at first it doesn't take long to doubt
porque a la primera no dura no dudar en
to stick it in her from behind now I realized
para clavársela por detrás ahora me di
realize that they are the same as them
cuenta que es que son iguales que ellos
Okay, for this damn reason it has its
vale por esta puñetera razón tiene sus
friends and for that reason they smelled like
amigos y por esa razón se olían a
fix for no other reason is worth it
arreglar no por otra razón vale
I felt sorry for it, I really say it.
me dio me dio pena de veras lo digo yo
I understand why I live much longer
entiendo porque vivo mucho más tiempo
that they being famous for much that
que ellos siendo famoso por mucho que
is out of here say if there is but
está váyase de aquí se diga si hay pero
does not lack even knows how to burden his
no le falte aún sabe lastrando su
opinion based on what there is god
opinión en base a lo que hay dios
Miret has been one of the opinions of the
miret ha sido de las opiniones de las
further
más
the sat and there
el sat y allá
also many times when they collide
también muchas veces cuando chocan los
rhythms too but this time to
ritmos también pero en esta ocasión al
knowing that it has been respectful to give your opinion
saber ha sido respetuosa dar su opinión
and period in his bubble and so on but oh well
y punto en su burbuja y demás pero bueno
the girl has given her opinion
ha dado su opinión la muchacha
who are far above you by
que están muy por encima de ti por
above me forgive me will be in addition to
encima de mí perdona estarán además de
fact a frozen part is attacked
hecho se asalta una parte helada se
assaults a part that speaks in the intro
asalta una parte que en la intro habla
very well from the alagn save the top of me
muy bien del alagón salve la cima de mí
in tweets but in other places I am
en tweets pero en otros sitios yo soy
much better known than them for things
mucho más conocido que ellos por cosas
good or bad things it doesn't matter
buenas o por cosas malas da igual las
beasts that I am much better known than
bestias que soy mucho más conocido que
they at scales of magnitude or what
ellos a escalas de magnitud o sea qué
balls like they are way above
como que están muy por encima de
I made it as if it were a channel
mí lo hice como si fuera un canal de
10,000 subscribers just out
10.000 suscriptores que acaba de salir
from here
de aquí
what the [ __ ] are you saying that is far above
qué dices que está muy por encima
from me - minutes would be the prsc above and
de mí - minutos sería el prsc encima y
I'm telling you who this girl is.
se lo contando en que quién es esta tipa
This kind of friendly action of theirs then
esta tipa acción amiga de ellos luego
so to know that story
así para saber esa historia
Who is this chick to know this?
quién es esta tipa para saber esta
literal history was not going to say it
historia literal no lo iba a decir
absolutely nothing I swear to you that it is that
absolutamente nada os lo juro que es que
start the live and that's it
inicia el directo y punto en
direct no no written mind nothing
directo no no escrita mente nada
find here live and
encontrar aquí en directo e
I was going because I was reacting to him but
iba porque estaba reaccionando a él pero
I privately went around here halfway
yo en privado iba por aquí por la mitad
and I said I'm going to react live and
y dije voy a reaccionar en directo y
period but this part counts
punto pero es que esta parte la cuenta
here neither on purpose nor on purpose
aquí ni ni ni a propósito ni a propósito
It is true that in fact Gonzalez in
es verdad que de hecho gonzález la en
two or three times in the char he asks
dos o tres ocasiones en el char le pide
respect for the people standing for gala and
respeto a la gente paradas para gala y
go to people who insult Dallas
vane a gente que insulta a dallas
and I tell you also and the only one in
y le digo también y el único en
defend you I have a cold
defenderte a ti tengo un resfriado de la
Juan, already with the controversy about the [ __ ] bed
ya juan con la polémica de la cama
the fears of that thing are [ __ ] awesome
de los los temores de eso que
the whole blue world is throwing hate at
todo el mundo azul está tirando hate a
Juan, with that you remember that, right?
juan con eso os acordáis de eso verdad
You remember that, right?
os acordáis de eso cierto
who defended his friends
quien le defendió sus amigos
friends didn't laugh at him they laughed at
amigos no se rieron de él se rieron de
He and he joined the mommy of the memes
él y se sumaron al mami de los memes
who defended him here, the guy, me but
quien le defendió aquí el menda yo pero
he is tender in bed
es tierno de la cama
I burn with water but the bed
a mi me quemo de agua pero lo de la cama
I said it too, it's not because of Reid
es que yo lo dije también no es por reid
Give me and by program you have to take
me den y por programa hay que tomarse
things with humor, the thing about the bed
las cosas con humor lo de la cama
It really is that Juan's way of
realmente es que juan la manera de
He answers that he had a son of mine, he must know
contesta que tuvo hijo mío hay que sabe
bullfighting and killing has been going on for years
torear y matado ya tiene años de
experience and with the quantity and mass
experiencia y con la cantidad y la masa
of audience that you have you have to know
de audiencia que tiene tienes que saber
a little more to bullfight that type of
un poquito más torear ese tipo de
comment
comentario
If they come to me and say
si a mí me vienen y me dicen
Imagine
imagínate
Here we send Super Charles, there will be 10
aquí mandamos super charles serán 10
for you
para vos
and they put me to jerk off with you
y me ponen a mí me hago pajas con tu
girlfriend your girlfriend is hot every time
novia tu novia está buenísima todas las
nights I jerk off with your girlfriend I
noches me hago pajas con tu novia yo le
I would say I'm glad she does them to me
diría me alegro a mí me las hace ella a
me and from time to time I also support myself
mí y de vez en cuando también me apoyo
But hey, if you made it, the part continues.
pero bueno si llegaste la parte sigue
we would have been dreaming it
soñando lo hubiéramos estado
plan and thank you very much
plan y muchas gracias
And Juan answered yes because I have a better bed.
y juan contestó sí pues tengo mejor cama
than yours and better house than yours
que la tuya y mejor casa que la tuya
He understands that I know how to bullfight
me entiende que saber torear
a very serious thing, the thing about the bed is not
una cosa gravísima lo de la cama no es
a super serious thing
una cosa súper grave
and even a way to devise a way to
y hasta una forma de idear una manera de
defend both of them and leave Juan to you
defender a los dos y dejarte a ti a juan
the best possible and I put one here
lo mejor posible y le puse aquí una
Screenshot of the conversation with Juan
captura de la conversación con juan
where I start talking to him in a "yes" way
donde me ponga a hablarle en plan de si
I can help you say things and
yo te puede ayudar a decir las cosas y
ask you specific questions I will ask you
hacerte preguntas específicas yo te
I'll let you know tomorrow, but that's fine.
aviso mañana but lak tonterías vale
nonsense and more me trying to explain to him
tonterías y más yo intentando explicarle
how to express yourself better so that
cómo poder expresarse mejor para que la
people would follow us with the nonsense with
gente nos siguiera con la tontería con
the disgustingness you basically don't understand
la asquerosidad no básicamente entendéis
not basically
no básicamente
[Music]
[Música]
of what more
de lo que más
Cheers, take care of yourself, babe, I think.
salud a ver si te cuidas churra yo creo
that Dallas with everything that it takes
que dallas con todo lo que le lleva
happening I think it has already taken a
sucediendo creo que ya ha tomado una
excessive belligerent attitude
actitud beligerante excesiva para
people who only give their opinion from
personas que sólo dan su opinión desde
It gets hot outside quickly and
fuera se calienta rápido y
quite the opposite when we saw the video
todo lo contrario cuando vimos el video
I saw no disrespect from the girl who
no vi falta de respeto de la chica que
You may agree with it or not or
puede estar de acuerdo con ella o no o
Whatever it is you can tell him that it is
lo que sea puedes decirle que está
wrong host but this chick is already here
equivocada pero está ya esta tipa
He didn't go ahead because he doesn't know if it would be
no se adelantó porque no sabe si fuera
another person if I see that he deserves it
otra persona si veo que se lo merezca
but bag candle no no drink deserves
pero bolsa vela no no beber se merezca
I tell you what I am most ashamed of
lo que más vergüenza me da os lo digo
very seriously what makes me most ashamed
muy en serio lo que más vergüenza me da
is to have offered you today we can take
es haberle ofrecido hoy llevamos podemos
be friends without any problems
ser amigos sin ningún tipo de problemas
nor showing ourselves publicly is that not
ni mostrándonos públicamente es que no
I was interested in nothing, I didn't need it
me interesaba nada es que no necesitaba
nothing unique public nor that we will collaborate
nada público único ni que colaboraremos
I didn't make videos or anything, I told him how
ni hacer vídeos ni nada le dije forma
totally honest if you need a friend
totalmente honesta si necesitas un amigo
here I am
aquí estoy
literally without any need for
literal sin ningún tipo de necesidad de
nothing public or streams
nada público ni de streams de
collaborations or anything else simply
colaboraciones ni de nada sencillamente
Here I am because I felt sorry for you, no
aquí estoy porque me dio lástima no
I finished the sentence from before because I
termine la frase de antes porque yo
I've been playing for much longer, to be honest.
llevo mucho más tiempo la verdad a jugar
many of the friends he has
muchos de los amigos que tiene
They are interested in those they join
son por interés con los que se juntan
Juan, those who come to play don't
juan los que se acercan a jugar no lo
I say for now of course
digo por ahora por supuesto
I'm not saying it for Aurelio, I'm saying it for
ni lo digo por aurelio lo digo por
Beijing I don't think you need to know.
beijing no creo que haga falta que os
clarify that no but well I say it but of
aclare eso no pero bueno lo digo pero de
those who get together and such are some
los que se juntan y tal son unos
interested parties
interesados de cuidado
the grass and being famous that they much
la grama y siendo famoso que ellos mucho
longer I began to live the
más tiempo yo empecé a vivir las
consequences of fame since the year
consecuencias de la fama desde el año
2013 agreed and I know what it costs
2013 de acuerdo y yo sé lo que cuesta
find
encontrar
true friends and I know what it costs
amigos de verdad y sé lo que cuesta
because it costs a lot
porque cuesta y mucho
You never know who is approaching you.
no sabes nunca a quién se te acerca por
what is close is worth it and I really
lo que se acerca vale y yo realmente
I thought if there is someone who can help you
pensé si hay alguien que te puede de
truth to say look I'm not interested in
verdad decir mira no me interesa por
just because I already have fame I already have
nada más porque ya tengo fama ya tengo
I'm not going to try to take advantage of money
dinero no me voy a intentar aprovechar
I'm not going to try from you
de ti no voy a intentar
I'm not going to try to take your fame
de tu fama no voy a intentar
your money because I already have mine we can
tu dinero porque ya tengo lo mío podemos
being friends outside of public life
ser amigos fuera de lo público no
we need to speak more publicly
tenemos por qué hablar más públicamente
okay and I told him honestly
vale y se lo dije de forma honesta
because I felt sorry for him at that moment
porque me dio lástima en ese momento de
see all that this does not necessarily
ver todo lo que esto no necesariamente
It has to be that it is not that it is for
tiene que ser que no está ser que para
show that you are not approaching someone
demostrar que no te acercas a alguien
out of interest does not necessarily make you
por interés no necesariamente te hace
being very famous, that is, me, for example,
ser muy famoso o sea yo por ejemplo a la
people I talk to
gente a la que me a la que le hablo con
the one who took me to the one who treated me well and
la que me llevo a la que trató bien y
knowledge has told you otherwise that for me
demás te ha dicho el saber que para mí
It's the same for a youtuber as for me
es lo mismo un youtuber que a mí me
It's nice that he has 40,000 subscribers
caiga bien que tenga 40 mil suscriptores
that another one who has 15 million
que otro que tenga 15 millones
I didn't care
a mí me dio igual
I will never approach anyone for the
yo nunca voy a acercarme a nadie por el
interest and if he spoke to me or hung out with me
interés y si me habló o me junto con
someone or I ask someone to collaborate
alguien o le pido a alguien colaborar
with him like come to my channel if he wants it
con él en plan vente a mi canal lo desea
It's not about gaining followers or
no es por no es por ganar seguidores ni
nothing neither for nor for sucking followers nor
nada ni por ni por chupar seguidores ni
for sucking fame because I really am this
por chupar fama porque realmente yo esto
I say it from the heart, it's because I love myself at all
lo digo de corazón es por quererme nada
I'm not lying to you nor am I being
ni os estoy mintiendo ni estoy siendo
It looks good, I really don't give a damn, that is, I
bien queda me la suda de verdad o sea yo
I consider I consider
considero yo considero
that today with what I have I
que a día de hoy con lo que tengo me
I promise you enough, I mean I'm fine.
sobra os lo prometo o sea estoy muy bien
in all respects I do not need
en todos los aspectos no necesito
suck anyone's ass or go after anyone
chuparle el culo a nadie ni ir detrás de
no one or take me with someone who in
nadie o llevarme con alguien que en
I really don't like it so they continue
realidad no me caiga bien para que sigan
a little more followers a little more me
un poco más de seguidores un poco más me
the sweat is literally I hope I
la suda sea literalmente ojalá me
I would remain the same all my life as I am now
mantuviera toda la vida como estoy ahora
I mean, incredible, I'm privileged.
o sea increíble soy un privilegiado
I work in what I like, I do what I
trabajo en lo que me gusta hago lo que
I love it, I have a great time, I split my dick
amo me lo paso pipa me parto la
I am very happy and I earn well, you know.
estoy muy a gusto y lo gano bien saben
plan
plan
I'm not going to eat anyone's ass nor will I
no voy a comer le el culo a nadie ni me
I'm not going to get close to anyone because I'm more famous
voy a acercar a nadie por ser más famoso
because it has more followers than me
porque está más seguidores que me la
literally sudan look at this let's go to the
sudan literalmente mira esto vamos a las
I refer to the evidence
pruebas me remito
If I suddenly approach someone for
si yo de repente me acerco a alguien por
fame or whatever you're going to waste your time
fama o lo que sea vas a perder el tiempo
You really have to earn fame
realmente la fama te la tienes que ganar
you yourself and in your community you have to
tú mismo y en tu comunidad la tienes que
go harvesting yourself and
ir cosechando tú y
strengthening it over time by gaining you
afianzando la con el tiempo ganando te
the confidence of it even if you collaborate
la confianza de ello aunque tú colabores
With a country's footing you will not become famous
con pie de país no te vas a ser famoso
The next day I did a live show with
al día siguiente he hecho un directo con
Aurum Play I did a live show with pain
aurum play he hecho un directo con dolor
I have done a live show with Juan Guarnizo and
he hecho un directo con juan guarnizo he
made 8000 direct with the dallas of els
hecho 8000 directos con el dallas de els
Thank you very much, you see that I have grown
muchas gracias veis que yo haya crecido
that's why
por eso
Well, honestly, by
bueno sinceramente por
the facts not the facts because they are
los hechos no los hechos porque se los
I did it because I wanted to
he hecho porque a mí me porque yo quería
doing them is fine but do you really see what
hacerlos vale pero realmente veis lo que
is gained in a collaboration of this type
se gana en una colaboración de este tipo
That is to say, for me to burst, I would have to
o sea para que yo reventar se tendría
that every day the live broadcasts of
que estar todos los días los directos de
euros play every day collaborating
euros play todos los días colaborando
with now a lawsuit
con ahora un pleito
You understand me, it doesn't make sense, the ass to
me entendéis no tiene sentido el culo a
Nobody, for fame or whatever, there are people
nadie por fama o lo que sea hay gente
that does it there are many people who
que lo hace hay mucha gente que
They are literally there all day long
literalmente están todo el día
looking for the mouth of YouTube and apart
buscándole la boca a youtube y aparte
They are very shameless looking in the mouth to
son muy descarados buscando en la boca a
other youtubers all [ __ ] day to watch
otros youtuber todo el día para ver
If you compare it and they answer you
si lo compares y les contestan
leaning towards one and not holding on
arrimándose a uno y no teniéndose
to mess with each other
meterse con uno con otro
then what I tell you no
entonces lo que te digo no
necessarily because it is famous is that
necesariamente porque sea famoso es que
Dallas material
dallas material
I think it gives the nickname or it is not known
yo creo que da el apodo o no se conoce
from another who has seen something in Juan and
de otro que ha visto algo en juan y
dinar and well I have also spoken to them
dinar y bueno yo también les he hablado
many times very well from Juan Idear and the
muchas veces muy bien de juan idear y la
It's true that I like him very much, especially
verdad que me cae muy bien sobre todo
Juan
juan
To play, he seems like a super noble boy to me.
a jugar me parece un niño super noble
ok but
vale pero
but but what do I know?
pero pero yo que sé
I don't know, I think Dallas has been thought about
no sé yo creo que dallas se ha pensado
more of a friend than he was
más amigo de lo que era
That is, you are the cordial colleague in good
o sea tú ere el colega cordial en buenos
terms ok but your project is going to
términos ok pero tu proyecto te va a
support
apoyar
that is very ugly
eso está muy feo
your project is supported by your people
tu proyecto te apoya tu gente
for example how I make this one which is
por ejemplo como yo la haga este que son
closest to you
más cercanas a ti
or youtube is smaller than they are getting
o youtube es más pequeños que se están
getting in is late or not because they want
metiendo en es tarde o no porque quieran
support wishes but because he wants them
apoyar deseos sino porque quiere que los
Dallas fans know them and
seguidores de dallas les conozcan y
through the people of youtube that is
través a la gente de youtube eso es
right now
ahora mismo
I'm sorry, it's like this right now, okay, I
lo siento es así ahora mismo vale que yo
I trust it's too late or it's going to work
confío que es tarde o va va a funcionar
over time it has worked, it happens that it goes
con el tiempo ha funcionado pasa que va
to take a long time to have their lives and their coming and
a tardar a tener sus vidas y su venida y
will have its falls and will have to have
va a tener sus caídas y tendrá que tener
failures so that it can be polished until
fallos para que se vaya puliendo hasta
that it goes well and that is what will happen
que vaya bien y eso es lo que va a pasar
but it's going to be okay if it's Dallas no
pero que va a ir bien si si es dallas no
He gives up now, I consider that he does.
se rinde ahora yo yo considero que se
you have to take a little break
tiene que tomar un descansito en plan
go away for a week with Alice at
vete una semana con la alicia a las
islands are where the plant went
islas está donde se fue vegetal
or are the islands called before this beta
o se llaman las islas antes de esta beta
those islands with the propeller for a week
las islas esa con la hélice una semanita
and then comes back with another mentality
y luego vuelve con la mentalidad de otra
more relaxed way and you continue working
forma más relajada y sigues trabajando
calmly that it will take a while or it will not go
tranquilamente que tarde o no va a
work this year or tomorrow in the envelope
funcionar este año ni mañana en el sobre
comes to be vice functioning a little
viene estar de vice funcionando poquito
a little Maldives that and being inside
a poco la maldiva eso y estar dentro de
five years director life what I
cinco años director vida lo que me
changed his head within the 5th year
cambió la cabeza dentro del 5 de año lo
that gave me the head and look now
que me que me dio la cabeza y mira ahora
and look now how well later
y mira ahora lo bien que más tarde
because he doesn't give up he will continue
porque él no se rinde él va a seguir
pee and he's going to take it out but this takes its
pipí y lo va a sacar pero esto lleva su
time its users its falls is
tiempo sus usuarios sus caídas es
impossible or very difficult for you to do a
imposible o muy difícil que tú hagas un
project of this style and the first day
proyecto de este estilo y el primer día
go perfect man not even facebook
ya vaya perfecto hombre ni facebook
Instagram and Facebook are down today
instagram y facebook se caen a día de
today
hoy
You know Brain will have its downfalls.
sabes en brain tendrá sus caídas tendrá
your mistakes will have a thousand things the other
sus errores tendrán mil cosas el otro
day they looted tweets
día saquearon tweets
but it will not be the first day of the
pero no va a ser el primer día de la
beta cursed her the week relax come
beta la maldijo la semana relájate ven
with a calmer mind with a better one
con la mente más calmada con otro mejor
humor you know
humor sabes
but let's see if it doesn't come close by
pero a ver si las no se acerca por
interested Juan and that is very clear
interesada juan y eso está clarísimo
It's absurd to think that, no
es absurdo pensar eso no
It is clear that there are many people
es que claro la gente sea hay mucha
people who fought on twitter who have
gente que luchó en twitter que se ha
taken the fact of remaining loyal by throwing
tomado el hecho de quedar leales echando
in face is that I defended you I made videos
en cara es que yo te defendí hice vídeos
defending yourself in front of people there
defendiéndote de cara a la gente hay
people who are thinking that they did the
gente que se está pensando que hizo los
videos to defend him for later
vídeos para defenderlo para luego
ask him to leave to throw away what
pedirle que se retire a echar de lo que
There was one that I'm not going to mention
había uno que no voy a mencionar
there was an achievement I'm going to mention
había un logra voy a mencionar
because it is quite true
porque da bastante la verdad
saying clearly that after the after
diciendo claro que pasadas las después
of everything that sucks or supports it is
de todo lo que la chupa o la apoya es
refer to other banks in
referirse a otros los bancos en
dissolution to another person
disolución a otra persona
after all that [ __ ] sucking
después de todo lo que la chupa la
This and the defended now does not get into
este y las defendido ahora no se mete en
your starting platform
tu plataforma de arranque
I think coffee is good but
yo creo que bueno es el café pero
Listen Magdala, hello, hello, hello
escucha magdala hola hola hola
was happening with his friends
estaba pasando con sus amigos amigos
publicly that literally the video
públicamente que literalmente el vídeo
was to join the public filth
fue sumarse a la asquerosidad pública
okay and it made me very sad and right now
vale y me dio mucha pena y ahora mismo
because I feel sorry for myself that
porque siento penas por mí mismo que
You'll [ __ ] disgust him, I'm telling you, it really disgusts me.
asco le darás lo digo me da mucho
disgusting who is that I really swear no
asco quién es que de verdad lo juro no
I said nothing, nothing, nothing, nothing, eh no
dije nada de nada de nada nada eh no
I said nothing about any of these topics, nothing.
dije nada de ninguno de estos temas nada
I just unfollowed them and they
simplemente les deje de seguir y me les
I didn't even tell them, hey, why?
recrimine ni les dije oye por qué por
why haven't you talked to me why don't you do it to me
qué no me has hablado por qué no me hace
I don't know what because you haven't told me I don't know when
no sé qué porque no me has no sé cuando
I didn't say anything, I just told them it is
no dije nada simplemente les dije es
continue and that's it, I didn't do anything else, wine
seguir y ya está no hice nada más vino
she because she came because people did
ella porque vino ella porque la gente lo
is making it public on Twitter because
está haciendo público en twitter porque
There are many people publicly putting in
hay mucha gente poniendo públicamente en
twitter oh yes because today because there is one
twitter ay sí porque hoy porque hay una
great
gran
and I keep reading but I really
y sigo sigo leyendo pero realmente lo
What bothered me the most is after having
que más me molestó es después de haber
offered my most sincere friendship than a [ __ ]
ofrecido mi amistad más sincera que
I'm ashamed, I swear, I'm very ashamed
vergüenza me doy os lo juro me doy mucha
shame right now without following any
vergüenza ahora mismo sin seguir ningún
public interest just being friends now
interés público solo siendo amigos ya
is here to chat and get to know each other
está para charlar y conocernos
totally oblivious to fame and after
totalmente ajenos a la fama y después de
defend Juan and you in three controversies
defender a juan ya ti en tres polémicas
different
diferentes
then I remember there were four others
luego me acuerdo de otras fueron cuatro
wall four times four times that they
pared cuatro veces cuatro veces que les
I defend
defiendo
the last message I wrote to Juana
el último mensaje que le escribí a juana
what's up didn't even bother
what's up ni siquiera se molestó en
open it
abrirlo
literally didn't even bother to
literal ni siquiera se molestó en
Okay, okay, okay, the mute was saying
vale vale vale la mute estaba diciendo
that makes me see it a lot too
que a mí también me la hace mucho a ver
no ghosting or sting like why go
no ghosting o sting en plan porque go
team is as if they did not exist but that
team es como si no existieran pero que a
Me too, many times they don't answer me.
mí también muchas veces no me contestan
but I only do them too
pero que yo sólo hago a ellos también
It came out to the one who does it to me the user
salió al que me lo haga el usuario
I also give importance to the one who
también yo le doy importancia al que me
gives importance to the fact that I have
da importancia al que me tenga
importance my idea is to play myself
importancia mi idea está en jugar yo
many times written by good websites
muchas veces escrito por webs bueno
play
jugar
and this is going to make us deny it
y esto nos lo va a poner negar
eight thousand eight thousand good messages but
ocho mil ocho mil mensajes buenos pero
Yes, he has several messages from me, joking.
sí que tiene varios mensajes míos guasa
that I asked for one thing and there is more left
que le pedía una cosa y hay más dejado
They are not even the blue tica worth that is
no están ni el tica azul vale eso está
in the double tick that you have received it
en el doble tic de que lo ha recibido
but it follows us until the blue ticket
pero nos sigue hasta el ticket azul ni
hasn't even opened it and if he has it
siquiera lo ha abierto y si lo tiene
activated by the theories so blue
activado por las teorías tan azules
the last one who described pti the last one
el último que describió a pti el último
that I wrote to you even to you
que te escribí yo a ti siquiera te
you bothered to open me I guess still
molestaste en abrirme supongo que aún
You will follow a Guinness record on stream
seguirás en stream un récord guinness
of the longest stream and we put and
del stream más largo y le ponemos y
hanging out in the ass knowing the jokes
departiendo en el culo saber las bromas
passive aggressive which are my specialty
pasivo agresivas que son mi especialidad
but also you marked me is
sino que también además me marcaste es
the incredible view with the thing of being
el visto increíble con lo de estar de
osh which makes no sense because
osh lo cual no tiene sentido porque
above all that is something that also
encima eso es algo que también nos
benefits you was only unique and
beneficia a vosotros era solo única y
exclusively upload the videos that you
exclusivamente subir los vídeos que tú
This is already getting into a debate about being
esto es ya meterse en debatirlo de estar
of or I don't know what it is that it is simply not
de o no sé qué que es simplemente que no
They are interested until it is very
les interesa hasta que sí que está muy
well and that they can benefit because
bien y que se pueden beneficiar porque
They may have lived but they do not
pueden su vivido pero que no les
interested
interesa
you had already monetized will not have
tuvieseis ya des monetizados no tendrán
monetized videos and if they have them
vídeos de monetizados y si los tienen
well
pues
and if they have it, they are not interested
y si lo tienen pues no les interesa
upload it from WhatsApp they prefer to have it in
subirlo de whatsapp prefieren tenerlo en
your channel that is not interested in uploading the
su canal que no le interesa subir la
late until
tarde hasta
I'm sure you only have one wave and I
que seguro que tenéis una sola ola y yo
I already took care of the rest, that's why
ya me encargaba del resto es que de
The truth really pisses me off because
verdad me cabrea profundamente porque me
taught
enseñaron
and it is true that it is also another for me
y es que de verdad me también es otra
thing I was taught to do
cosa me enseñaron que se hagan
publicly as Juan said in this
públicamente como el juan dijo en este
anthem I have no problem and
himno no tengo ningún problema y
doing it with style
haciéndoselo con el estilo
super good I hope everything is okay no
super bien espero que todo esté bien no
two of us are leaving
se nos van dos
and he got upset, or rather, he didn't even bother
y se molestó o sea ni se molestó en
He didn't even bother to write to me
escribirme ni se molestó en escribirme
privately what good is it to me? I wanted
por privado de qué me sirve a mí quería
things publicly if you don't write to me
las cosas públicamente si no me escribes
however private I want to understand that
por privado que quiera entender eso que
That matters to you, the public face, not to see if
eso te importa la cara pública no ver si
talk to his wife so that she will go to you
habla con su mujer para que te va a
write
escribir
I guess not, I'm cool, I would have
supongo no yo soy guay le hubiera
spoken in plan
hablado en plan
I didn't answer you and in a thousand things
no te contestaba vos y en mil cosas
chile to two and I can't answer you but
chile a dos y no puedo contestarte pero
Look, I feel sorry for the Protestants who
mira lo siento por los protestantes que
I'm not interested in being in this late or what
no me interesa estar en es tarde o que
I'm not interested in your platform that yesterday
no me interesa tu plataforma que ayer
I thank you so much, I wish you good luck and
tal agradezco te deseo mucha suerte y lo
I will mention my live that you are creating the
mencionaré mi directo que estás crea la
platform and such but I'm not interested
plataforma y tal pero que no me interesa
Upload videos there, I have the videos
subir vídeos ahí que yo tengo los vídeos
On the other hand, I'm not interested anymore.
otro lado ya mí no me interesa
just that and that's it, give them and you are done
simplemente eso y ya está darlas y se
wants to take the wind too, you know it
los quiere tomar viento también se te lo
has taken more abuse more you know but
tiene toma maltrato más más sabes pero
They call me, that's what it is
me llaman es ya eso qué
Aris and cares about only one
aris y se preocupa por el uno solo
I personally believe this is one of mine
yo creo personalmente mío esta es una
opinion personally well I have not spoken
opinión personalmente bien no he hablado
in fact with them
de hecho con ellos
I think there is
yo creo que hay
and John
y juan
evidently they did not consider him a friend
evidentemente no lo tenían como un amigo
They have it maximum and always speak well
lo tienen máxima y siempre hablan bien
of him even in private
de él incluso en privado
but when they saw that Juan when he
pero cuando se vieron que juan cuando se
They saw that Dallas gave him not only would he say
vieron que dallas le dio no sólo diría
eyes to see if this one is going to be put now
ojos a ver si ahora éste se va a ponerse
In the videos I will tell the truth.
en los vídeos voy a hablar la verdad le
happens
pasa
I think that was what worried him if
yo creo que fuese lo que le preocupó si
You don't answer that you are not interested in being there
no le contestas que no te interesa estar
It's late and now he writes it for him
es tarde y ahora la escribe para el
ufologist
ufólogo
because if not if you don't write to me by
porque si no si no me escribes por
private and makes everything public that
privado y lo hace todo público que
wants to understand that it only responds if
quiere a entender que sólo responde si
people pressure you to answer
la gente te presiona a responder
publicly on the subject no
públicamente sobre el tema no
It's the only thing that makes me understand
es lo único que me da a entender a mí
and literally the topic of being a [ __ ]
y literal el tema de estar de
That's also another one he said
también esa es otra que dijo
publicly what is now not
públicamente el que es que ahora no
I had time, we would see more
tenía tiempo es que ya veríamos más
go ahead or something like that he said okay
adelante o algo así dijo vale que
we would do later
haríamos más adelante
[Music]
[Música]
how much time do you need
qué tiempo necesitas
really get into your youtube channel
realmente entra en tu canal de youtube
give to the one who does not want to study yes
darle al que no quiere estudiar sí que
you don't have to think that you don't want to
no tiene que estimar que no quiere
give them years each one has a reason
darlas años cada uno tienes un motivo la
demobilized videos tab
pestaña de videos desmovilizados
and summarize them now but we have to
y resumirlos ya pero nos tiene que
remove on your channel and would rather have it
quitar en su canal y preferiría tenerlo
monetized on your YouTube channel that
de monetizado en su canal de youtube que
upload them to these desires that there are no more or
subirlos a estar deseos que no hay más o
either it is what I said or it is not
sea es lo que yo he dicho o sea que no
wants youtube only offers I hope not
quiere youtube sólo ofrece espero que no
He loves you because he is not interested in what you have
os quiere ya que no le interesa que ha
played the platform is known for itself
jugado la plataforma sea conocida por si
You are interested but you don't have to close it
le interesa pero no lo tienes que cerrar
the door neither
la puerta tampoco
but they never told him that if that happened
pero nunca le dijeron que si eso los
cell phones the error here is there is no
celulares el error aquí es no hay de
forehead
frente
the mistake here in not telling him Dallas is not me
el error aquí en no decirle dallas no me
it is interesting when it comes to having a lot of luck
interesa a la hora de tener mucha suerte
but I'm not interested
pero no me interesa
That's it, you can't blame someone.
ya está no puede recriminarle a alguien
that you are not interested in uploading videos to a
que no le interese subimos vídeos a una
new wave churri platform is like
plataforma de nueva ola churri está como
has been here, thank you very much, it's going away, I'll send you
ha estado muchas gracias se va te mando
a hug
un abrazo
You don't care if I'm in the videos of
te da igual que esté en los vídeos de
monetize on youtube, it doesn't matter what
monetizar en youtube que da igual que da
I also have videos to monetize in
igual yo tengo vídeos de monetizar en
youtube calm Andean see and I'm not going to
youtube calmado andino ver y no lo voy a
remove from my YouTube channel I prefer
quitar de mi canal de youtube prefiero
have it without monetizing it than upload it in another
tenerlo sin monetiza que subirlo en otro
I want them on my channel, do you understand me?
lado los quiero en mi canal me entendéis
that he is not interested and until he is
que no le interesa y hasta que no lo
you have to eat the pot, nobody has to
tienes que comer la olla nadie tiene que
Hey, but why don't you not want to, damn it?
oye pero como no no que no quiere
that's it
ya está
that he loves us I was like
que nos quiere yo estaba como
they are not giving you money
no te están dando dinero
video those videos do not report you any
vídeo esos vídeos no te reporta ningún
benefit doesn't cost you anything, it doesn't cost you anything
beneficio no te cuesta nada no te cuesta
Recording new videos doesn't cost you anything
grabar vídeos nuevos no te cuesta
Producing new videos doesn't cost you anything
producir vídeos nuevos no te cuesta nada
but it's more if you don't want to upload videos
pero es más si no quiere subir vídeos
Well, don't upload them, it doesn't matter, the only thing is
pues no los subas da igual lo único que
is saying is the videos that you don't
está diciendo es los vídeos que no te
generate no money that already exists
generan ningún dinero que ya de por si
I have a solution here that I can find
yo aquí tengo una solución que se me
It happens, not to stir up trouble, but sometimes
ocurre no es para malmeter pero a veces
Dallas has very thin skin
dallas tiene la piel muy fina
it is not thin skin
no es la piel fina
If I had thin skin I would tell you
si tuviera la piel fina yo te digo yo
that many things would have been offended even more
que se hubiera ofendido muchas cosas aún
He said he was a disaster at speaking on
dijo que era un desastre para hablar por
WhatsApp and he was the same, I think they act
whatsapp y él era igual creo que actúan
with everyone the same, well if you have
con todo el mundo igual bueno si tiene
One thing my car has never happened to me but
una cosa mi auto nunca me ha pasado pero
neither by WhatsApp nor by Will be nor by
ni por whatsapp ni por estarán ni por
nothing if I have to ask him or
nada si le tengo que preguntar o lo
I have to call to see if I have
tengo que llamar para ver si a mí me ha
answered in one go
contestado del tirón
It will depend on the importance that
será dependiendo de la importancia que
leaves people or how well you
le deja a la gente o lo bien que te
people fall or the cordiality that one
caiga la gente o la cordialidad que uno
Please be cordial, but look, you know
tenga por cordialidad pero mira sabes
Here, there might be a very good solution.
aquí igual a hubiera si una solución muy
simple uncle
sencillita tío
let's see if it leaves water for him to upload a video.
a ver le deja agua que suba un vídeo es
late or even if you already have it
tarde o aunque lo tenga ya
But if you're telling him he has to
pero si le estás diciendo que tiene que
be a video that is not in any other
ser un vídeo que no esté en ninguna otra
platform or admire one of the videos
plataforma o admira uno de los vídeos
that you are going to upload to Facebook surpassed
que vas a subir a facebook superó
I also see you
también a estar veo
even if you're not going to be in this one later
aunque luego no vayas a estar en esta
late or if you are not going to upload more videos
tarde o si no vayas a subir más vídeos
but at least to give it a push
pero por lo menos para darle el empujón
continue at the beginning if you had asked for it
sigue al principio si lo hubiera pedido
Juan doesn't say no to that.
a eso juan no le dice que no
but that's what he's asking people for
pero así le está pidiendo a la gente
if you are asking people the same thing
si le está pidiendo a la gente lo mismo
from Facebook because Facebook doesn't
de facebook porque facebook no te
monetize videos when facebook by
monetizar los vídeos cuando facebook por
That's because I uploaded videos that were already uploaded
eso porque subía videos que ya subieron
I don't even know how they realized it
que no sé ni cómo ellos daban cuenta
if you are asking people to
si estás pidiendo a la gente que el
video that you upload late or has to be
vídeo que subas tarde o tiene que ser
exclusive of being there is already
exclusivo de estar de ahí ya les está
complicating things for people is putting them
complicando a la gente le está poniendo
people a commitment understands me
gente un compromiso me entiende
The problem is that Google
el problema es que google
does not support summarized content they want
no admite contenido resumido quieren
original content on the pages in which
contenido original en las páginas en las
to monetize
que monetizar
and I, through a live broadcast, Juan brings us all up.
y yo por un directo juan nos sube todos
Juan could have told him the direct ones
los directos le podría haber dicho juan
Look, it's something to do me a favor.
mira es una cosa para hacerme el favor
Do you mind uploading a live of yours?
te importa subir un directo tuyo que
This handsome guy
este guapo
a directory that will not upload you
un directorio que no vaya a subir te
It matters to upload it, man, there are a thousand channels of
importa subirlo tío hay mil canales de
clips
clips
There are a thousand channels of Juan clips
hay mil canales de clips de juán
guarnizo there is a click channel from juana
guarnizo hay un canal de clic de juana
who earns millions from visiting me
que gana millones de visitarme
and I, Juan, a director of don't go to
y yo juan un director de no vayas a
upload uploads the afternoons without editing and nothing
subir sube las tardes sin editar y na
but at least to give me a chick
pero por lo menos para darme una pollito
there
ahí
You see, I couldn't even do that because I'm all
veis yo ni eso podría ser porque yo todo
I upload it
lo subo
Dallas, I'm not going to help you.
dallas yo no te voy a ayudar
percent this helps me by
por ciento la presente me ayuda por
Of course it helps you but I don't know how
supuesto que te ayuda pero no sé cómo
The kings deleted my Facebook and
a mí me borraron los reyes el face y
I never saw anything but I left Facebook too
nunca vi nada pero dejé facebook también
but look at least on Facebook
pero mira por lo menos de facebook me
It served to bring me lordship
sirvió para traerme la señoría
I have a better date, he didn't care.
yo tengo una mejor cita no le importaba
Why don't I call them and talk things over?
porque no los llamo y hablo las cosas
Man, what do you want me to tell you?
hombre yo qué quieres que te diga
each one takes things depending on the
cada uno se toma las cosas depende del
moment and it depends on how you throw
momento y depende como eches
It depends on how I am at the moment
depende de cómo esté en el momento
I also tell you
también te digo
Let's see, I understand that Juan doesn't want to
a ver yo entiendo que juan no quiere
It's too late to participate today
participar es tarde hoy
What I don't understand is why you don't tell him.
lo que no entiendo es que no se lo digas
It's clear, help her, I'm not interested in what
es claro ayúdala no me interesa lo que
you're going to go up
vas a subir
I'm not going to record that on YouTube
no voy a grabar que en youtube
I don't feel like it
no me da la gana
but he says it
pero dice lo
And I tell you, I am the proof.
y es que ya os digo la prueba soy yo
Friend, I'm not angry with you, right?
amigo conmigo no me enfada verda la oiv
he posted a tweet quietly
ha puesto un tweet tranquilamente
some alpha from ardales are suitable, I don't
conviene unos alfa de ardales yo no
I'm in the moment that I will be there
estoy en estar de momento que estaré yo
I will be there, the doors did not do it for
estaré no lo hicieron las puertas para
take out myself I have nothing
sacar a mismo no tengo nada
but to put a video in your face
pero que se meterse a la cara un vídeo a
tonight I'll be interested in three videos a day
la noche me interesará tres vídeos al
year
año
I know that if you get involved, things will be done, especially
sé que se mete se harán cosas sobre todo
when we react to something like save me or
cuando reaccionamos a algo de sálvame o
something of the sort
algo por el estilo
Do you get me
me entiende
But who are we talking about, Juano and I?
pero de quién hablamos de juano y yo
Juan de One Guarnizo and not paying anything
juan de one guarnizo y no pagando nada
for them
por ellos
2those in states that make money by
2los en estados que ganan dinero por
they
ellos
in what way or in what form as he says
de qué manera o de qué forma como dice
This clown here, I'm telling her
esta payasa de aquí yo estoy diciéndole
today promotes something that only me
hoy promociona algo que sólo me
benefit to me
beneficio a mí
it is more nor if it is more it is more nor even
es más ni si es más es más ni siquiera
I was asking them to promote it
les estaba pidiendo que lo promocionarse
Hi Javi, I love your content and I follow you.
hola javi amo tu contenido y te sigo
I just wanted to comment a long time ago that I am
hace mucho sólo quería comentar que soy
one of the little ones who is in to be
uno de los pequeños que está en estar de
osh and honestly I don't intend to bring
osh y honestamente no pretendo traer a
No one on YouTube, I'll just upload trailers.
nadie a youtube más bien subiré trailers
to YouTube so you can see it in full
a youtube para que vean completo en
be from osh the video I really believe in
estar de osh el vídeo creo de verdad en
the platform and hopefully everyone can
la plataforma y ojalá todos pueden
operate by hand in our case forgive me
operar a mano en nuestro caso perdóname
Yes, it is widespread, but I know of some and there are
si generalizado pero sé de algunos y hay
This one that smells like a kilometer away is some
este que huele a kilómetro pasa son unos
3 for vouchers and there are some who ask for it
3 para vales y hay algunos que le piden
enter dallas in the afternoon or
entrar dallas en la tarde o
maybe it's not your case, I'm not saying it is
a lo mejor no es tu caso no digo que sea
your case because you don't want to, you don't
tu caso porque no se quiere no te
I know but that I'm going back you know
conozco pero que yo voy de vuelta sabe
like I've been here for many years
en plan yo llevo ya aquí muchos años
I have also been through many kinds of
también he pasado por mucho tipo de
Friendships and lots of people on the street
amistades y mucha gente en la calle
I have I have the university of the street
tengo tengo la universidad de la calle
but I do have many hits and
pero sí que tengo muchos palos dados y
I see them coming but from afar
yo los veo venir pero de lejos los
You come beautiful, okay, I see you from afar
bellos venís vale de lejos los veo yo
come and I look a little on twitter and
venir y yo viendo un poco en twitter y
when such people who ask the
cuando tal la gente que le pide a la
I want the room is on your platform
sala yo yo quiero está en tu plataforma
and I see them, I see them coming and there are some
y yo lo veo los veo venir y hay algunos
that they want to get into it late or with
que se quieren meter en es tarde o con
the intention that it is late or
la intención de que es tarde o
It is obviously late for you
evidentemente es tarde os está
promoted for giving many thanks
promocionada por dar las gracias muchas
thank you
gracias
This video is provided by Dallas
este vídeo está proporcionada por dallas
You understand me, whatever they give us
me entiendes quiera que nos dan las
you have a lot of promotion in this
levas en mucha promoción en esta
platform
plataforma
right now how many creators to yen
ahora mismo cuantos creadores a yenes
late or 10
tarde o 10
5 events have been going on for more than 2 years
5 los eventos hay más de 2 años
and with time goes 2030 creators no
y con el tiempo va 2030 creadores no
Whether you like it or not, there are many people
quieras que no es una hay mucha gente
that he will see it as an opportunity
que lo va a ver como una oportunidad
d
d
expose yourself to the Dallas public
exponerse al público de dallas
do you understand me or not
me entendéis o no
and I know I'm thinking a lot and I'm
y yo sé que estoy pensando mucho y estoy
asking I will not be of them I will go
pidiendo no voy a estar de ellos yo voy
to be on it because the intention is
a estar de ello porque la intención es
that bringing to make itself known more
esa traerse darse a conocer más
You understand that this will not be the case in all cases.
me entendéis que no será todos los casos
but I know there are some who are 13
pero sé que hay algunos que son 13
because that is the intention
porque son esa la intención
Okay
vale
not even
ni siquiera
You know the shame I felt
vosotros sabéis la vergüenza que sentí
when people assumed it
cuando la gente que la gente lo asumió
in a perfectly normal way because the
de manera perfectamente normal porque la
people are not that bad in general
gente no es así de mala por rama general
I asked Juan today will you be there?
le preguntaba a juan hoy estarás es
Later we will have you in stadiums
tarde os tendremos en estadios por el
people say progress and they are doing well
lado la gente dice avance y van bien
Well, it will be in stadiums, it is not logical anymore
pues estará en estadios no es lógico más
Even though I have defended four
aún pensando que he defendido cuatro
sometimes good
veces bueno
because he only has to see the real one
porque sólo tiene que ver a la de verdad
So your side defended because you have
o sea que tu lado defendió porque tú ha
darling
querido
more than four times defended but
más de cuatro veces de defendido pero
four different controversies that have
cuatro polémicas diferentes que han
had they who are not
tenido ellos que no son
that they are not them
que no son ellos
white little sheep that get into
blancas ovejitas que se meten en
Of course, controversies arise
polémicas por supuesto que se meten en
controversial and commentary
polémicas y que hacen comentarios
strong of course they do it or so
fuertes por supuesto que lo hacen o sea
and on top of that I have defended them totally
y encima yo les he defendido totalmente
according to that at night
de acuerdo con que a la noche
People assume this and what do they do?
la gente asume esto y ellos que hacen
say don't make them search I don't have
decir no hagas que busquen no tengo
time but what time do you need if it is
tiempo pero qué tiempo necesitas si es
only put the videos that are
sólo poner los vídeos que están
demoralized by YouTube on a site in
desmoralizados de youtube en un sitio en
another is nothing more
otro no es nada más
that is to say, what time or what time is to continue
o sea que tiempo ni qué tiempo es seguir
insisting that they defended him that
insistiendo en que le defendieron esa
guide itself does not represent any to you
guía de por si no te representa ningún
benefit and put it in states that do
beneficio y ponerlo en estados que sí
that will represent any benefit to you or
que te va a representar beneficio ni
you're not even going to earn more than me
siquiera vas a ganar tú más que yo
but exactly even if they didn't want to
pero exactamente incluso si no querían
how hard it is to say no thank you
que cuesta decir no gracias
just exactly just I'm seeing it
justo exactamente justo lo estoy viendo
That was really hard to say no thanks.
eso sí que costaba decir no gracias
nothing nothing and instead months ago
nada nada y en lugar de eso meses hace
months months of this many months because
meses meses de esto muchos meses porque
In August was the last time I spoke
en agosto fue la última vez que hablé
with her but she really does a lot
con ella pero realmente hace muchos
months of this many
meses de esto muchos
and
e
[Music]
[Música]
However, you left me completely
sin embargo me dejaste es completamente
in Austin complete and absolute during
en austin completo y absoluto durante
months and months
meses y meses
However, what does interest you seems to be
sin embargo lo que si os interesa parece
that you have no problem answering and
que no tenéis problema en responder y
This is where the eye comes in because what
aquí es donde viene el ojo porque lo que
I'm going to say now it may sound like that
voy a decir ahora puede sonar a que
I'm feeling jealous but it's worthless
estoy en plan celoso pero para nada vale
not at all true and in fact
para nada en absoluto verdad y de hecho
I have never said anything to him, neither Auron nor A.
no le he dicho nunca nada ni auron ni a
Bilin never being in this state is because
bilin jamás de estar en estad es porque
already assumed is a first moment that does not
ya asumido es un primer momento que no
They were going to be there for them, I don't think so.
iban a estar por ellos no creo que
have no problems with its content
tengan ni problemas con su contenido
It can remain in the previous situation but
puede quedar en el contigo anterior pero
in this one no
en este no
be proper which neither
sea propio cual tampoco
That is to say, in turn, the US assumes that it has not yet
o sea a su vez eeuu a asumes que aún no
you're going to have a problem with your content
va a tener problema con su contenido
Neither Biden nor John because he is going to have with
ni biden y juan porque va a tener con
problems and here this is what is not there either
problemas y aquí esto es lo que tampoco
I see the videos well about what in the
veo los videos bueno sobre lo que en la
part of what I'm doing but plays goes up
parte de lo que rato pero juega sube
video games and quite childish
videojuegos y bastante infantil su
content do not see the content of juan and
contenido no ver el contenido de juan y
gameplay is not the same as living
al gameplay no es lo mismo que vivir
It may sound really annoying, okay.
realmente de molesto vale puede sonar
I'm offended but it's not in that
que estoy ofendido pero no es en ese
plan because again I left them like that and no
plan porque de nuevo les deje así y no
He rebukes him but I was seeing the
le recrimina pero yo iba viendo las
things of course yes while I
cosas por supuesto que sí mientras yo
It was totally cool, not even in sight.
estaba totalmente madre ni en visto vale
literally coast at all and that's it
literalmente coast en absoluto y eso lo
that is, you have no problem answering and
que es no tenéis problema en responder y
Being soul mates is not the same.
ser los amigos del alma no no es igual
the contents of one when divided
el contenido de one al dividir
If it is almost the same, it is good to clarify the
si es casi lo mismo bueno aclarar el
vocabulary that the videos will have nor of
vocabulario que tendrá los vídeos ni de
neither one nor the other
uno ni de otro
that you are best friends and [ __ ]
que sois mejores amigos y
skills together if you talk to him that eye
habilidades juntos si le hablas que ojo
I'm not saying this in a jealous way, you can be
no lo digo en plan celoso podéis ser
friends of whatever comes out of our balls
amigos de que nos salga de los huevos
but how many but how many controversies
pero cuantas pero de cuantas polémicas
they have defended you
os han defendido ellos
but I was seeing things by
pero yo iba viendo las cosas por
Of course yes while I was
supuesto que sí mientras yo estaba
totally mother not even in sight
totalmente madre ni en visto
literally coast at all and that's
literalmente coast en absoluto y eso es
what is you have no problem in
lo que es no tenéis problema en
respond and be the soul friends of a
responder y ser los amigos del alma de a
one does not begin
uno ni begin
sometimes
a veces
I mean, it's like someone pretends I'm
o sea es como si alguien hace como si yo
I don't answer someone because I don't have the time
no contesto a alguien porque no me da la
wins
gana
Imagine being Enrique Garca from YouTube
imagínate ser enrique garcía del youtube
In Enrique Garcs I had a person who did not
a enrique garcés tuve una persona que no
She is my friend if she doesn't give me time to
es amiga mía si no me da tiempo de
I don't have time to talk, I have time to talk
hablar no me da tiempo hablando me da
the same as what the videos defend me
igual lo que me defiendan los vídeos
Enrique understands me, the perfect example.
me entiende el ejemplo perfecto enrique
Garcia YouTube Enrique has been I had
garcía youtube enrique ha sido tuve
many times he talks to me on WhatsApp and no
muchas veces me habla por whatsapp y no
I answer this to myself the same way you see 728
le contesto esto a mí igual que ve a 728
videos defending myself but imagine that
vídeos defendiéndome pero imagínate que
comes in wealth if it were there later
viene en riqueza si estuviese ahí luego
If reading is a close friend of Dallas
si leer es muy amigo de dallas
and then if you are a good friend of charisma
y luego si eres muy amigo de carisma le
I would say that
diría que
but talk about yourself, what do you care what
pero habla de ti qué te importa lo que
I do
yo haga
ah
ah
and that you are best friends and [ __ ]
y que sois mejores amigos y
skills together and speaks to him that eye does not
habilidades juntos y le habla que ojo no
I say it in a jealous way, you can be friends
lo digo en plan celoso podéis ser amigos
that we feel like it but
de que nos salga de los huevos pero
How many controversies have you had?
cuantas pero de cuantas polémicas os han
defended them by showing their faces
defendido ellos dando la cara
publicly for you how cool it is
públicamente por vosotros qué guay lo
copy
ejemplar
euronews and they are not going to make a video let's see
euronews y no van a hacer un vídeo a ver
if someone asks him live
si alguien le pregunta en directo
I would surely answer
seguramente respondería
But if now how do you make a video, imagine
pero si ahora como hace un vídeo imagina
euros making a video defending
euros haciendo un vídeo defendiendo a
Juande
juande
Lauro doesn't do that
lauro no hace esa
cable costs of your controversy
cuesta cable de la polémica suya
and the comparison
y la comparación
one thing that was that you defend them
una cosa que estuvo que tú los defiende
because your content is to talk about the
porque tu contenido es hablar de las
controversies
polémicas
but now it's about a video defining
pero ahora va sobre un vídeo definiendo
water
agua
and you don't ghost them but you
y a ellos no les hacéis ghosting pero a
It's okay with me and again I don't dislike them.
mí sí vale y de nuevo no me caen mal
Now Juan uploads a lot of reaction to tick
ahora juan sube mucha reacción a tick
tock and that not monetize because it was a
tock y eso no monetizar porque era una
That would be a good idea for your life.
buena idea sería esa para su vida es
late or for example clear
tarde o por ejemplo claro
a little bit of live
un ratito de directo
and that would be absolutely but I the fact
y eso sería en absoluto pero yo el hecho
that I want you to understand this
de que quiero que entendáis esto el
made of
hecho de
that I
que yo
The content of Latin America is very different.
el contenido de latam es muy distinto
from the vocabulary they make cool streams
desde el vocabulario hacen chupi streams
they usually get wet the objective is
se suelen mojar el objetivo es
entertain without caring much more
entretener sin importar mucho más
Carmen or take how long did I take everything?
carmen o lleve durante cuanto llevo todo
the last year plus the previous one
el último año más el anterior
defending yourself from all the controversies in
defendiéndote de todas las polémicas en
the ones you've gotten into, I don't know about friendship
las que te has metido la amistad no se
measures in the defense that is still derived
mide en la defensa que todavía derivarse
in plan it is as if for example
en plan es como si por ejemplo
let's see one thing is that one thing is
vamos a ver una cosa es que una cosa es
that you say
que tú digas
Imagine that Juande suddenly throws at her
imagínate que juande repente le tira
[ __ ] dallas
dallas
then you can throw it in his face
entonces así se lo puede echar en cara
Hey man, I've been defending you for a year.
oye tío llevo un año defendiendo te
always speaking well of you and
siempre hablando siempre bien de ti y
Now you go and talk badly about me
ahora tú coges y hablas mal de mí
but the fact of measuring friendship is no longer
pero ya el hecho de medir la amistad no
It is measured in that today looks like now never
se mide en que hoy mira que ahora nunca
I have defended you and Auro has defended you
te ha defendido yo sí y auro si le
you speak and I don't speak euros and he is a friend of
hablas y a mí no euros y es amigo de
Juan, they have been left, the four have
juan ellos han quedado los cuatros han
gone on vacation together have been almost
ido de vacaciones juntos han estado casi
twenty days living in the same house
veinte días conviviendo en la misma casa
vacation
de vacaciones
They talk every day and many nights
hablan todos los días y muchas noches
by salt discs
por discos sal
not me
no me
It matters how I'm going to get in the middle
importa como me voy a meter en la mitad
of a person who is not even that
de una persona que ni siquiera esa
person in my friend and I'm going to get in myself
persona en mi amigo y me voy a meter yo
to ask him for explanations about the
a pedirle explicaciones sobre las
friendships he has
amistades que él tiene
each and every one I'm not telling you that we have
todas y cada una no te digo que tengamos
to be best friends because we don't have
que ser mejores amigos porque no tenemos
why be it I offered it to you you didn't
por qué serlo yo te lo ofrecí tú no lo
you want okay it's fine nothing happens no
quieres vale está bien no pasa nada no
nothing happens
pasa nada
But we are talking here about that
pero es que estamos hablando aquí de que
we went from
pasamos de
25 complete, that is, not even responding
25 completo o sea ni siquiera responder
I mean, this is another level, it's not a question
o sea este es otro nivel no es cuestión
It's not that we are less your friends, no
de no es que somos menos amigos tuyos no
is that we don't even answer you but
es que ni siquiera te respondemos pero
instead, with whom they get along so well
en cambio con quién se llevan tan bien
They even publish videos saying that.
que hasta publican vídeos diciendo eso
it's your thing
es cosa suya
Carlos, thank you very much.
carlitos muchas gracias
This part in action having a lot
esta parte en acción teniendo mucho
will be a friend of Kim and his great video with
será un amigo de kim y su gran vídeo con
whoever wants it today is who they are
quien le dé la gana hoy es que son
our best soul friends
nuestros mejores amigos del alma
I hope we live together because I don't know
este ojalá viviremos juntos porque no sé
that
qué
the problem and here of course I can't avoid
el problema y aquí claro no puedo evitar
think badly, that is, here is where I can't
pensar mal o sea aquí es que no puedo
avoid thinking badly
evitar pensar mal
because I also [ __ ] and say [ __ ]
porque también cojo y digo
What a damn coincidence that just
qué puñetera casualidad que justamente
the only person you nest in today
la única persona en la que te nidos hoy
My best friend I would love to live with
mi mejor amigo me encantaría vivir con
He is a person who is the first to know
él es una persona que primero a conocer
quite recently because we
hace bastante poco tiempo porque nos
we have known each other for a long time
conocemos hace mucho tiempo juntos
Let's see, have they known each other for a year or
vamos a ver se conocen de hace un año o
two years or whatever but they have to
dos años o lo que sea pero tienen a que
go now too if it doesn't go that way
ve también ahora si no va por ese lado
Javi, I don't know, somehow I understand
javi no sé de alguna forma entiendo a
dallas is that one gets annoyed when it is
dallas es que uno se fastidia cuando es
a constant behavior of people
un comportamiento constante de la gente
It's like they feel it's okay
es como que sienten que está bien
do it to you
hacértelo a ti
[Music]
[Música]
You can be friends with anyone who gives you the
se puede ser amigo de quien le dé la
wins and if for what he thinks that with
gana y si por lo que él piensa que con
Aura has become a friend out of interest
aura un se ha hecho amigo por interés
I don't think it's the same thing I said
yo no creo que es lo mismo que he dicho
before about my case in the case of Wang and
antes sobre mi caso en el caso de wang y
Ari can be a couple who
ari pueden ser una pareja que
quietly
tranquilamente
that quietly
que tranquilamente
can win
pueden ganar
how much
cuánto
150 thousand dollars each
150 mil dólares cada uno
per month
al mes
very calm mind
tranquilísima mente
very quietly among its channels of
tranquilísima mente entre sus canales de
youtube between the pri and between this between
youtube entre el pri y entre esto entre
the others
los otros
For $150,000 or more a month you can
por 150 mil dólares o más al mes podrás
win each one surely or more not
ganar cada uno seguramente o más no lo
HE
sé
why are they going to approach by the
para que se van a acercar por el
interior or employ
interior o emplee
What more does it matter to him if he charges 300 thousand to
qué más le va a dar de cobrar 300 mil a
collect 300 thousand 50 350 thousand
cobrar 300 mil 50 350 mil
and they are going to take someone who is not
y se van a llevar con alguien que no
They are simply a couple with whom
simplemente son una pareja con la que
have connected was aura and beat and
han conectado fue aura y beat y
those who have invited them to
los que los han invitado a ellos a
sites
sitios
They went on a trip because they connected very well
se fueron de viaje porque conectaron muy
well and when you go on a trip with one
bien y cuando tú te vas de viaje con una
couple is worth it
pareja vale
One thing is that if friendship arises
una cosa es que si surge la amistad
It happens that you can't fake it, for example.
surge eso no se puede fingir por ejemplo
things they have told look at one
cosas que han contado ellos mira una
night they gave us laurel and me both
noche nos dieron de lauro y a mí las dos
They started talking just the two of them
se pusieron a hablar las dos solas se
They went around talking with their drinks
fueron por ahí hablando con sus copitas
They have connected but that is who we are
se han conectado pero eso quién somos
the others to mess with us like this
los demás para meternos así con
You need a friend and with wine I don't think so.
necesitas es amigo y con vino yo no creo
for nothing that there is
para nada que haya
[Music]
[Música]
let's go no interest rate
vamos ningún tipo de interés
apart I don't know
aparte no sé
here he gave us
aquí nos dio
given time and is also the only person
dado tiempo y además es la única persona
who has more provisions than he does
que tiene más víveres que él en which
It really can't be avoided
de verdad es que no se puede evitar
I tell you very seriously that I think badly
pensar mal os lo digo muy en serio los
I say very seriously I can't help but think
digo muy en serio no puedo evitar pensar
bad because again it is that you like in
mal porque de nuevo es que guste en
absolute
absoluto
but I don't like it at all
pero me gusta en absoluto
and then from them or to the goat that they know and
y luego de ellos o al chivo que sepan y
Whatever you want is going to be great but
va súper bien lo que tú quieras pero
Damn, how many times are they defended from
cuántas veces están defendido de
How many times have they helped
ellos cuantas veces están ayudado a
they
ellos
ibai also has more vigor than water
ibai también tiene más vigor que agua
I don't know what each of us has, we know
no sé los que tienen cada uno sabemos
I don't care, I already said that I don't know
que me da igual que ya digo yo que no se
note
nota
s paulo a thank you very much king
s paulo a muchísimas gracias rey
How many times do I understand that I feel you
cuántas veces yo entiendo que te sienta
It's bad that they make you the Westin and that they don't
mal que te hagan el westin y que no te
answer of course that's ugly but
contesten por supuesto eso está feo pero
Well, you send them to hell, that's it.
bueno los mandas al ya está
but
pero
it is no longer
ya no es
Another thing is that as Dallas knows that
otra cosa es que como sabe dallas que a
They don't host them, they don't have it
ellos no les hace hosting no tiene
no proof that they answer them
ninguna prueba de que les contestan
all messages now not even beginning
todos los mensajes ahora ni a begin
The point is that the best thing
el punto es que lo mejor
Dallas is not interested in answering you and Auro
dallas no le interesa contestarle y auro
If Dallas is very tired and frustrated
si dallas está muy cansado y frustrado
not because he defended something that seemed right to him
no porque defendió algo que le pareció
unfair at the time can charge it
injusto en su momento puede cobrarlo
after not having also I tell you one
después no haber también os digo una
which I understand perfectly that he is
cosa yo entiendo perfectamente que él se
develop on your channel and on your live stream
desarrolle en su canal y en su directo
Because Aurelio, thank you very much
porque es que aurelio muchas gracias a
Dallas has something that also happens to me
dallas le pasa una cosa que también me
It happens to me okay and it is that if he has one
pasa a mí vale y es que si él tiene una
idea and he thinks something about someone
idea y él piensa algo sobre alguien lo
has to let go
tiene que soltar
He doesn't eat it because maybe in these
no se lo come porque a lo mejor en estas
things are tradition because you think about it
cosas es tradición porque la piensa
and then this one happens to him the same as to me
y entonces éste le pasa igual que a mí
as long as I have something inside that I think
como yo tenga algo dentro que yo piense
something about a person or that has been done to me
algo de una persona o que me ha hecho
something ugly or that I see there are bad ones
algo feo o que yo veo que hay malas
intentions or whatever until you do it
intenciones o lo que sea hasta que no lo
loose
suelto
I burst like it happened to me with Juanjo like I
reviento como me pasó con juanjo como me
It happened with others, okay, this is about me for
pasó con otros vale esto de yo por
take the ige and it doesn't fit in
llevarme el ige y por no entra en
controversy keep quiet no that's not my thing
polémica callarme lo no eso no es lo mío
and you know it
y lo sabéis
and then he thinks like this about them and this
y entonces él piensa así de ellos y esto
He keeps it inside, in the end he creates you
se lo guarda dentro al final te crea
inside like a tumor this is not for you
dentro como un tumor esto no te lo
You can leave it here inside your chest
puedes dejar aquí dentro del pecho te
it inflames okay then they are releasing it
inflama vale entonces lo están soltando
what he thinks I do not agree with
lo que él piensa yo no está de acuerdo
in everything he is saying
en todo lo que está diciendo
[Music]
[Música]
I just think it needs a
simplemente yo creo que necesita un
rest same same room
descansito iguales misma sala se
He regretted having exploited himself
arrepintió de haber explotado a sí
yes because I think not
sí porque yo creo que no
so the way he thinks that's what I think
así las cosas como él piensa eso me lo
is watching
está viendo
on your part of things and others that are not
de su parte de cosas y otras que no
and I remember
y yo recordemos
the relationship my relationship with them began
la relación mi relación con ellos empezó
with them attacking me with them
con ellos atacándome con ellos
calling me a pedophile pederast but it's okay
llamándome pederasta pedófilo pero da
Maybe they have been forgiven a lot
igual se les ha perdonado un montón de
erase the different parts of remembering
borra las diferentes partes de recordar
since they warn forgiven
ya que alertan perdonada
They have only received things from me
ellos de mí sólo ha recibido cosas
good things only and exclusively
buenas única y exclusivamente cosas
Good, I have received very good things from them
buenas yo he recibido de ellos cosas muy
bad and some good things
malas y algunas cosas buenas
well yes
bueno sí
we did a couple of streams
hacer un par de streamings lo hicimos
together then that streaming pair that
juntos pues ese par de streaming que
had done together for me in the test
había hecho junto para mí en la prueba
that they embarrass us to get together
de que ellos nos avergüenzan de juntarse
with Dallas they are not even ashamed to get together
con dallas ni se avergüenzan de juntarse
with Dallas they never even hide to speak to each other
con dallas ni ocultan nunca a hablarse
with dalla you understand me
con dalla me entiende
They embarrass us and hide our conversations with each other
nos avergüenzan y ocultan a hablarse con
he just doesn't have no feel
él simplemente no tienen no sienten la
same friendship with him
misma amistad con él
they do not feel the same
no sienten la misma
friendship towards the one he believed was going to
amistad hacia el que él creía que iba a
having with it maybe is what I
tener con ello a lo mejor es lo que yo
I perceive from outside
percibo desde fuera
and I understand that the problem bothers you.
y entiendo que te joda el problema el
problem that I see with water and air because
problema que le veo agua y aire porque a
The best thing is that one doesn't answer you because it is
lo mejor uno no te responde porque es
Thalia, but the two of them don't answer you, man.
thalía pero los dos no te responden tío
It's scary to say to his face that
está dando miedo decirle a la cara que
you do not want to participate it is late or with
no queréis participar es tarde o con
jodie celo
jodie celo
I think that a friendship does not have to
yo pienso que una amistad no tiene que
forced but arises in a way
ver forzada sino que surja de manera
organic
orgánica
but you can totally talk to Dallas
pero totalmente puedes hablar con dallas
and make him see reason to see what he does
y hacerle entrar en razón a ver hacerle
come to your senses, I can explain to you
entrar en razón yo le puedo explicar
As I see things, this doesn't mean
como yo veo las cosas esto no quiere
say that I have the resonated that the
decir que yo tenga la resonado que la
have each one of us have another point of view
tenga el cada uno tenemos otro punto de
obviously I talk to him but
vista evidentemente yo hablo con él pero
I'm not going to tell you the thing here
no os cuento aquí la cosa
I don't tell you here the things I talk about
no os cuento aquí las cosas que hablo
with him he understands me
con él me entiende
of course but I talk to him he talks
por supuestísimo pero hablo con él habla
with me when something happens to me and we
conmigo cuando a mí me pasa algo y nos
we are getting to know each other surely
vamos conociendo mutuamente seguramente
many of the things that are said here
muchas de las cosas que se dicen aquí
because I'm new and I already knew
por me estoy haciendo nuevo y ya sabía
He understands me but from the outskirts
me entiende pero de extrarradio
Well, you don't know, it's not like the same
pues no sabéis no es como que la misma
bargaining chip
moneda de cambio
What I think is this, I think he
yo lo que creo que es esto creo que él
It has felt like Tibet in another half
se ha sentido como tíbet en otra mitad
with them and they the others have not
con ellos y ellos los otros no lo han
sense the others have felt the same
sentido igual los otros han sentido
put a cordiality and some birds
poner una cordialidad y unas aves
Okay
vale
and literally from people who do know
y literal de personas que pues sí se
They can carry very well and what you
pueden llevar muy bien y lo que tú
you want
quieras
They are soul mates
son amigos del alma
Okay, there is no problem at all, but
vale no hay ningún tipo de problema pero
they really have not had it themselves
ellos realmente en sí no han tenido
not even a chance to show one's face
siquiera oportunidad de dar la cara por
I have stood up for you, yes.
ti yo sí he dado la cara por ti por
you two on several occasions, professor
vosotros dos varias ocasiones profesor
On the other hand, I'm not saying that we have to
de otra cara no digo que tengamos que
be best friends who at least
ser mejores amigos que al menos
answer me no if that's what I tell you
responderme no si eso os digo yo al
less answer me like that is just simple
menos responderme así es simple solo
answering was enough for me yet no thanks
responder me bastaba aún no gracias
and then I find out that I don't
y luego me entero de que yo que no
I wanted to talk about that topic or continue
quería hablar de ese tema o bien seguir
I was never going to talk about that subject in the
no iba hablar a ese tema jamás en la
life and is completely ignored to speak
vida y es ignorado por completo hablar
People have asked me about this topic
de este tema la gente me ha preguntado
in esteem today is because you left the he
en estima hoy es porque dejaste los he
skipped because you stopped following them
saltado porque dejaste de seguirles los
exalted I did not want to respond to that
exaltados no he querido responder a eso
because I didn't feel like talking about this either
porque no apetecía hablar de esto además
I tell you that I feel humiliated very much
que me siento humillado os lo digo muy
seriously and I find out now that this
en serio y me entero ahora de que esta
girl knows who this girl is
tipa lo sabe quién es esta tipa
No
no
and I tell him
y le digo
and this is what I already asked
y esto fue lo que ya pregunte a
beginning of the year in a capture of
principios de año en una captura de
WhatsApp December 19 May 19
whatsapp diciembre 19 de mayo el 19 de
May imagine how long it was for me
mayo imaginad el tiempo que hacía que me
I was doing Austin, I say Juan, I
estaba haciendo austin yo digo juan me
you are ignoring for some reason
estás ignorando por alguna razón
The film says because when I say well
el filme dice porque cuando yo digo pues
on discs in tweets in twitter dm or
en discos en tuits en dm de twitter o
literally but these were
sea literalmente pero esto fueron
nonsense and I didn't care because it was
tonterías y no me importaron porque era
the same various things on these topics that
igual cosas varias sobre estos temas que
they have nothing to do with each other
no tienen nada que ver
just for the sake of chatting just for the sake of it
sin más sólo por charlar solo por
just chatting then it didn't bother me
charlar sin más entonces no me molestó
This in itself bothered us
en si nos molestó en sí mismo esto
because
porque
They say now more than once I have opened
dicen ahora más de una vez he abierto
a conversation thinking about responding
una conversación pensando en responder
later I forgot it without truth
más tarde se me ha olvidado sin verdad
If it happens to me every day, I'll finish it.
si a mí me pasa todos los días lo acabo
to give a thousand examples but when you
de poner mil ejemplo pero cuando te las
they do all the time
hacen todo el tiempo
4 halftimes
4 las entretiempo
to see many people who are not from
a ver a mucha gente que quien no es de
start chatting jokingly too
ponerse a charlar en guasa también los
say
digo
For example, I used to be
yo por ejemplo si acostumbraba que soy
to chat on WhatsApp by audio by
de charlar en whatsapp por audio por
20 minute audio taking about 20
audio de 20 minutos tomando unos 20
minutes taking a 3 to my audio
minutos tomando un audio de 3 a mi
sister sends him a 2-minute audio 2
hermana le manda un audio de 2 minutos 2
minute and a half and tells me to go to
minuto y medio y me dice que vaya a
search knows
buscar sabe
and yes it is true that there were a lot of people
y sí que es verdad que había mucha gente
for an important thing
para una cosa importante
6 of the 697 thanks, maybe it's known, but now put it
6 los 697 gracias tal sabe pero ya poner
It's like no chatting and I think that
está charlar como que no y yo creo que
Juan and Ari are this type of people
juan y ari es de este tipo de personas
of those who are not to start chatting
de los que no es de ponerse a charla
nash but they also have no interest in me
nash pero que tampoco tienen interés me
understands
entiende
and one thing someone
y una cosa alguien
feels a certain confidence
siente cierta confianza
next feel confident for example to
siguiente sienta confianza por ejemplo a
I was given the Guasa One and Ari and
mí a mí me dieron los guasa one y ari y
Now it is also seen that they have the
ahora también se ve que tienen los
You don't keep him, but what do you give him?
guardas de él no pero para que le dan
you joke if you don't have it in later
los guasa si luego no lo tienes en
consideration as a friend
consideración como un amigo
and it also leaves me
y es que a mí también me deja se han
seen many times in seen not to me
visto muchas veces en visto no a mí me
has left unanswered look one le
ha dejado sin contestar mira one le
I've been asking ban to help me with
llevo pidiendo a ban que me ayude con
I'm not going to tell you about a month-long thing.
una cosa de darse un mes no os voy a
say that for a month now I have not forgiven
decir que desde hace un mes no perdón
look at it well yes
mirarlo bien sí
Since July Rodolfo, thank you very much
desde julio rodolfo muchas gracias
thanks elena
graciaselena
from the end of July beginning of
desde finales de julio principio de
August I am asking for water that I
agosto le estoy pidiendo agua que me
help me with something and he says not for me
ayude con una cosa y me dice no para mí
If you answer me and say yes yes yes yes
si me contesta y me dice sí sí sí sí
I knew it now I do it
sabía ahora lo hago
[Laughs]
[Risas]
but I think it's because they don't give me
pero yo creo que porque no me dan
importance because you can't help it
importancia porque no puedes ayudar se
thanks you very much
os da muchas gracias
let's see, let's see, joke
a ver a ver guasa
It's worth a month and thank you very much.
vale al mes y muchísimas gracias
[Music]
[Música]
I asked him for guasave to urge him
por guasave se lo pedí por instar a
because he spoke to me to ask me I don't know
porque me habló para preguntarme no sé
what and I asked him for something, it's my business
qué y le pedí una cosa es un asunto mío
and I told him
y le dije
Dallas needs a serious helping hand
dallas necesita una mano amiga sería
great that you could talk to him and
genial que pudieras hablar con él y
explain to him that everything was public
explicarle que todo fue público
recommend that he offer apologies and a
recomendarle ofrecer disculpas y un
break and I'll do whatever you tell me
break y yo todo lo que me digáis
clearly I am truly grateful but everything
claramente agradezco de verdad pero todo
whatever you tell me of course
lo que me digáis por supuesto
and you have probably already done many of them
y seguramente ya habréis hecho muchas de
the things you are telling me
las cosas que me estáis diciendo
I remembered it
lo recordé
the following month
al mes siguiente
Well, it's probably because he doesn't love me.
pues seguramente sea porque no me quiere
help for what I'm asking you for
ayudar por lo que le estoy pidiendo
Juan, answer me about Javi, look, you don't
juan respóndeme de javi mira que no te
I'm going to this favor
voy a este favor
that I only do it to my friends
que se lo hago solamente a mis amigos de
more confidence and it doesn't even make me angry
más confianza y hasta no me enfada
What I feel is that
yo lo que siento que es
no
que no
It makes him feel embarrassed, I don't think they'll do it with
le da apuro no creo que lo hagan con
I don't think they give it any evil either.
maldad tampoco yo creo que le dan a que
he is embarrassed
le da apuro
and be clear when saying hey that
y ser claros a la hora de decir oye que
I can't help you with this, my friend.
no te puedo ayudar en esto amigo
I grana will put the shots
yo grana van poner los tiros
as it's been almost a year since that happened and
como además ya hace casi un año de eso y
It didn't bother me as such as to
no me molestó como tal como para
really getting angry has been a set
realmente enfadarme ha sido un conjunto
of things already Alain to Beckham and when
de cosas ya alain a beckham y cuando
Tales told me about the Westin back in the day.
tales en su día me contó lo del westin
I felt identified because I know that way
me sentí identificada porque sé que así
says they do it I don't think it goes with
dice que lo hacen no creo que vaya con
bad intention or anything it just is
mala intención ni nada simplemente es
that does not have the same importance as
que no te tiene la misma importancia que
has it covered not so a set of
le tiene cubierta no así un conjunto de
things not just one but a set of
cosas no sólo una sino un conjunto de
things that even adding one after the other
cosas que nin sumando una detrás de otra
Javier seriously think about it, do you think that for
javier serio piénsalo tú crees que para
one if he has time to see read the
uno si tiene tiempo para ver leer los
WhatsApp
whatsapp
if you have time because they are your friends
si tiene tiempo porque son sus amigos
I understand, let's see, no, I don't think it's because
entiendo a ver no no creo que sea por
interest that I don't think needs to be
interés que no creo que necesiten estar
with no one for personal gain, truth be told
con nadie por interés la verdad sea
Don't be like that either, I don't think they need it.
tampoco seáis así no creo que necesiten
be with no one out of interest
estar con nadie por interés
but this
pero esto
let this chick know that
que esta tipa sepa eso
and I tell him
y le digo
He is partly right, although he believes
tiene su parte de razón el aunque cree
that
que
There are things I don't agree with him on
hay cosas que no estoy de acuerdo con él
but it has its
pero tiene su
point and his way of seeing things
punto y su forma de ver las cosas
but ideally I forget to do
pero el idealmente me olvides hacer
casting and in a very important project
casting y en un proyecto muy importante
for me and that would have also been very
para mí y que también hubiera sido muy
beneficial for you then by
beneficioso para vosotros entonces por
Being there did bother me.
lo de estar de ahí sí que me molestó
How can it be that I help you?
cómo puede ser que yo te ayude yo te
help me, I will defend you face to face
ayude yo te defienda yo de la cara por
you only enclosure but there you think that still
ti solo recinto pero allí crees que aún
have time if you want we can do the
tiene tiempo si queréis hacemos la
try I'll send you a waza right now in
prueba le mando un waza ahora mismo en
play and see how long it takes to answer me
play y vemos cuánto tarda en contestarme
I think it depends on the importance that
yo creo que depende la importancia que
Let everyone give him the respect he has
le dé cada uno el respeto que le tenga
another person or you want to know me
otra persona o lo deseas saber a mí a
see if you're telling me that maybe
ver si me estás diciendo que a lo mejor
I don't know if you're telling me that Dallas
no lo sé si me estás diciendo que dallas
This heavy all day talking to you and no
esto pesado todo el día hablando te y no
You want to answer him, oh I'll keep quiet, but no
le quieres contestar ay me callo pero no
I think they come out in general, this is it
creo que salgan en general está la tiene
reason it's ugly that they do that to you the subject
razón está feo que te hagan eso el tema
It's that it gives the intense and it seems to me
es que da la es intenso y me parece
some things were unnecessary, for example
estuvo de más algunas cosas por ejemplo
I see the Hauran thing, yes, yes, it could be
lo veo lo de hauran sí sí podría ser a
see in general you are right you have a
ver en general tiene razón tienes un
simply reason that I believe that
motivo simplemente que yo creo que
other things should have been related
habría que haber relacionado otras
ways like these people don't give you
formas en plan esta gente no te dan
importance because it is not left to
importancia porque tampoco se la deja a
they
ellos
Today the south will not be able to eat because the
hoy el sur no podrá comer porque el
dollar the south can't talk about these
dólar el sur no puede hablar de estos
themes is not so much the part of having the
temas no es tanto la parte de tener la
reason but the way of managing it
razón sino la manera de gestionarlo
It is somewhat disproportionate, I pay a lot
es algo desproporcionada pago muchas
thanks so I think that's what it is
gracias así que yo creo que es lo que se
is believing that this aunt is doing
está creyendo que esta tía está haciendo
the video because well, I'm not going to like this girl
el vídeo porque bueno esta tía no le voy
to speak like that but makes an expression
a hablar así pero hace una expresión
ok but we are asking for it
vale pero estamos pidiendo que se la
treat with respect I'm not going to say this
trate con respeto no voy a decir esta
aunt that Gonzalez is speaking for
tía que gonzález está hablando por
because he has sent it to you because there you
porque se lo haya mandado porque ahí le
have told whatever you know what
haya contado lo que sea sabes en lo que
I think the Dalai Lama is making a mistake.
yo creo que se está equivocando el dalai
what is turning you on or when
lo que le está calentando o sea cuando
there is literally no sufficient evidence
literalmente no hay indicios suficiente
and everyone is talking about it
y todo el mundo está hablando de eso le
will put a strike on who
pondrá un strike a quién
jolie
jolie
and good things about my only and
y cosas buenas de mi única y
exclusively received good things from
exclusivamente recibió cosas buenas de
my people many people from my community who
mi gente mucha gente de mi comunidad que
I didn't know you because Juan
no te conocía porque pues juan le
They will know him, they know him above all
conocerán le conocen sobre todo
mainly in Mexico but outside of
principalmente en méxico pero fuera de
iu doesn't know much more nobody knows
iu no le conocen mucho más nadie sabe
who is outside of the sector
quién es fuera de dentro del sector
closed tweets
cerrado de tweets
and from Mexico
y de méxico
Thank you Empire, thank you very much
gracias imperio muchísimas gracias al
the rest are not really that well known
del resto no es tan conocidos realmente
I mean
o sea
and you literally leave me stranded on something
y literal me dejas tirado en algo me
You ghost, sorry, you cast me.
haces ghosting perdón me haces casting
in something that benefits you if there were
en algo que te beneficia a ti si hubiese
request hey man
pedido oye tío
promote my channels make a video
promociona mi canales hace un vídeo
telling everyone to help me in
diciendo a todo el mundo que me ayude en
my channel is awesome and more something
mi canal es impresionante y más algo
for you too it is something for you too
para ti también es algo para ti también
yes or no
si o no
in the case of Juan but again
en el caso de juan pero de nuevo de
new if it would benefit you have to fall into
nuevo si le beneficiaría hay que caer en
I don't think Juan has the content
el contenido que tiene juan no creo que
Tunisia that I don't know I don't think it has
túnez que no sé no creo que tenga
real problems it was hard for me to say no
problemas de verdad me costaba decir no
but no thanks
pero que no gracias
no, thanks
no gracias
in fact let me see let me see why not
de hecho déjame ver déjame ver porque no
I know the messages I have
sé los mensajes que tengo
in private on Twitter with Juan
en privado de twitter con juan
Which Dallas do you name the South Star?
a que dallas le pones estrella el sur
Ok, jolie, that's not well understood.
vale jolie que no está bien entendido
Amer Azizi did not react to this.
amer azizi el su reacción a esto no le
you put
pones
I don't think so
no creo
I'm sending you a message that I'm sending to everyone
le envío un mensaje que envíe a todos
the creators of the stars god pauli
los creadores de the stars dios pauli
that is giving money to Dallas
que le está dando dinero a dallas
instead of wasting fabric here it's a joke and the
en vez de gastar tela aquí es broma y el
July 17th, look at my paulo and say, tell me
17 de julio mira mi paulo y dice me dice
I'll let you know, I don't think so.
lo leve te aviso nombre no creo que le
They put in extra and a month later I tell him
metieron extrae y un mes después le digo
[ __ ] the ghost in one a month later
el ghost in one un mes después
said [ __ ] the ghost in one
dijo el ghost in one
and he answers me three days later
y me responde tres días después
He tells me to tell me where you took your exam.
me dice pásame donde hiciste tu examen
of iq
de iq
because he wanted to do it live or
porque él quería hacerlo en directo o
be just talk to me just answer me yes
sea solo me habla solo me respondes si
you want something from me I don't know but that's the
quieres algo de mí no sé pero esa es la
answer yes but if you realize
respuesta sí pero si te das cuenta
treat them at the same level
tratarlo tú a ellos al mismo nivel
treats it brings it to the same level
trata lo trae al mismo nivel
is the answer
es la respuesta
and the last message
y el último mensaje
Anyway, he continued with the messages, sorry
en fin continuó con los mensajes siento
that I did a lot for you and I
que hice bastante por vosotros y me
offered in the most honest and sincere way
ofrecido la forma más honesta y sincera
to both and in exchange obtained pure Austin and
a ambos ya cambio obtenido puro austin y
However, people who have not done the
sin embargo gente que no ha hecho ni la
half for you because that is not me
mitad por vosotros pues eso no soy la
half is that in itself they have done
mitad es que en sí pues que han hecho
so collaborate
pues colaborar
but they haven't done anything else apart from that
pero ya no han hecho más aparte de eso
unless publicly so time
a menos públicamente así que tiempo
you have
tenéis
I'm not at all serious about it
en absoluto lo digo muy en serio
now I have never been made Austin
ahora ni bien nunca me han hecho austin
I'm even sure that now it is
es más estoy seguro de que ahora está
I am much busier than them
mucho más ocupado que ellos estoy
next you don't even imagine weapons never nor you
próximo ni te imaginas armas nunca ni te
Can you imagine he has never let me answer a
imaginas jamás me ha dejado responder un
message never
mensaje nunca
never is never
nunca es nunca
So you have time, what happens is that
así que tiempo tenéis lo que pasa es que
You don't even want to dedicate it to me
en mí no lo queréis dedicar ni siquiera
to give me a look at the ones I don't
para decirme una mirada a las no me
interested
interesa
Let's see, he has his reason for giving it a follow.
a ver tiene su razón de darle un follow
I might not have given it to him.
yo a lo mejor no se lo hubiera dado
because I what I do in the past
porque yo yo lo que hago en el pasado
month and they do something ugly to me and so on but something
mes y me hacen algo feo y así pero algo
ugly there is nothing without something ugly I mean
feo no hay algo sin algo feo me refiero
to
a
a lack of respect
una falta de respeto
an ugly example that someone tells me one
un feo ejemplo que a mí me digan una
thing but then I found out about the
cosa pero luego me enteré de la
contrary you know I don't know the examples I in
contraria sabes no sé los ejemplos yo en
In this case, what I would do would not be to give it a
este caso lo que haría no sería darle un
follow yes it is true that dallas
follow sí que es verdad que dallas
is more selective about the people it serves
selecciona más a la gente a la que se
guide me that in that sense the
guíen yo que en ese sentido el
twitter follow like that doesn't matter
seguimiento de twitter como que no le
gave too much value and I'm still almost
dio demasiado valor y sigo casi a
anyone to imagine to be
cualquiera para imaginar para estar
pending on everything that is said
pendiente de todo lo que se habla lo que
yes such and many times even for
sí tal y muchas veces incluso por
egg cordiality lo follow and dallas
cordialidad de huevo lo follow y dallas
is more selective
es más selectivo
You know Dallas is more selective when it comes to
sabes dallas es más selectivo a la hora
very few people follow
de seguir sigue muy poquita gente
So if they are people who don't
entonces pues si son gente que no te
They contribute nothing but being your friend and such
aportan nada que no son tu amigo y tal
a forum has its reason it's not me
un forum tiene su motivo es yo no
I would have done it then
hubiera hecho yo hubiera hecho pues lo
treatment at the same level
trato al mismo nivel
besides at the end at the end is ar and the
además de al final al final es ar y la
that the one who asked him has asked him
que le ha preguntado a él la que le ha
requested in the explanations of why
pedido en las explicaciones de por qué
unfollow her for taking your
la deja de seguir por toma tus
explanations you can agree or
explicaciones puedes estar de acuerdo o
no but that's what you think
no pero es lo que da la piensa
so that's all I don't wish you bad but
así que eso es todo no os deseo mal pero
I feel like you haven't valued me.
siento que no me habéis valorado he
treated very well and the truth is that I have been very
tratado muy bien y la verdad he sido muy
patient, oh yes, patient has come out
paciente vaya que sí paciente ha salido
things from the beginning of the year
cosas de principios de año
but it's been many months like this and
pero ya han sido muchos meses así y
Well, nothing, you will see that what
bueno nada vosotros veréis que a lo que
you want to give priority to what you don't and
le queréis dar prioridad y a lo que no y
something that doesn't seem to me to be the bottom line
algo que no a mí no me parece el fondo
not bad no no not bad
no está mal no no no está mal
each of us would have acted in a different way
cada uno hubiéramos actuado de una
way but they love them but here what
manera pero los aman pero aquí lo que
I see that you are making a mistake
veo que se está equivocando
in which it is
en que se
He is speaking out because they come out against the
está hablando porque salen contra los
others in the end it is as it is
otros al final de cuenta es como lo es
in the end as he sees it and that
al final de cuentas como él lo ve y que
he can follow and unfollow that
él puede seguir y dejar de seguir que
supports them and besides, it is true
les apoya y aparte sí que es verdad
and he's going to say yes that it's true that he doesn't
y va a decir sí que es verdad que él no
He has said nothing but man it has been known
ha dicho nada pero hombre se ha sabido
because
por qué
because he posted a tweet saying
porque él ha puesto un tweet diciendo
that he would do the same if they were ignoring him and
que haría igual le estaban ignorando y
because he said in the video that the
porque él en el vídeo ha dicho que la
We feel bad that some YouTubers don't like it
sentamos mal que algunos youtube no le
answer and so on all the people and the or
contesten y demás toda la gente y la o
No
no
and I tell them ah and there I remembered and what about
y les digo ah y ahí me acordé y lo de
Winnie also [ __ ] I have given my face for
winnie también he dado la cara por
you are also defending with
vosotros hay también defendiendo con
She has faced four controversies
ella cuatro polémicas que dado la cara
then for you
entonces por vosotros
Well, don't even open my messages x
bueno ni abrir mis mensajes x
I didn't think he was going to ask me and I think
no pensé que me fuera a preguntar y creo
that boxing mixed it up punctually, no
que eso lo mezcló el boxing puntual no
nothing happens about the CMS hosting thing
pasa nada la cosa del hosting de a cms
If you expect to see it, what I have here is
si espera ver es que yo aquí lo que me
It is clear that Juan and Ari x do not
queda claro es que juan y ari x no
have no interest in
tienen ningún tipo de interés en
strengthen relations with Dallas and there is no
estrechar relaciones con dallas y no hay
I don't understand anything about the wood ones but I
más entiendo nada las de duela pero yo
I could say okay, well I'll put it to
podría diría vale pues yo pongo a
you on the same level and if one day
ustedes en el mismo nivel y si un día
I have to react to a video of yours
tengo que reaccionar a un vídeo vuestro
and another to defend in a controversy
y otro que defender en una polémica
because I believe it I will defend you and if a
porque yo lo creo os defenderé y si un
day 89 criticize or criticize
día 89 criticar o criticar
We are no longer friends, we got together because
ya no somos amigos nos juntamos porque
People have realized it and that's it
la gente se ha dado cuenta y ya está
because if not I don't think that if you had
porque si no no creo que si tuvieses
bothered to tell me anything
molestado en decirme nada
and well nothing that's all obviously not
y bueno nada eso es todo obviamente no
I can keep the same offer standing
puedo mantener en pie la misma oferta de
friendship that I offered before because that way
amistad que ofrecía antes porque así
I never treated you and without more they are not forms
nunca os trate y sin más no son formas
to treat me either and I think that's
de tratarme tampoco y yo creo que eso es
all
todo
what a [ __ ] rage
que rabia
It made me very angry to see that she was
me ha dado mucha rabia ver que se la
are telling others that it is not only
están contando a otros que no solo está
counting
contando
those of me seriously
los de mí en serio
If you tell me that they will be counted, auro
si me dice a mí que serán contados auro
Walter or someone or Comanche then
walter o alguno o al comanche pues
It could be okay but knowing ours
podría ser vale pero al saber la nostra
take into account that they are telling others
en cuenta eso están contando a otros
Reed says I'm going to sound like a hater for a change.
dice reed voy a sonar hater para variar
But with this, Dallas is demonstrating
pero con esto dallas está demostrando
very little dignity souls in that do not them
muy poca dignidad ánimas en eso no les
I insist on the same saying that it is
insisto el mismo la dicho ri que se
feels humiliated and ashamed
siente humillado y que le da vergüenza
having been behind them
haber estado detrás de ellos
Honestly, that's what I'm telling you.
sinceramente es que lo que te digo yo
more than a follow because even giving it
más que un follow porque incluso darle
a clear follow but the bases that
un follow claro pero los bases que los
two that dallas with his account he follows
dos que dallas con su cuenta él sigue
only very close people are worth it
solamente a gente gente muy cercana vale
but even I, for example, in my case
pero incluso yo por ejemplo en mi caso
that if it goes to 300-400 people give it a
que si va a 300 400 personas darle un
It would only be giving it importance
solo sería darle importancia
you understand me, I would have taken you
me entendéis yo hubiera cogido tú me
You haven't answered me in two years. I ask you a favor.
hace dos no me contesta te pido un favor
He doesn't answer me, don't worry
no me contesta no te preocupes
Next year you will ask me for something
el año que viene me pedirá tú algo a mí
or next year or next month
o el año que viene o el mes que viene me
will try to answer because you will be interested
intentará responder porque te interesará
to ask me something or to talk to me
a pedirme algo oa hablar conmigo para
something
algo
Do you understand me? I will answer you or I will not.
me entendéis yo te contestaré o no te
I will answer if I am interested
contestaré si me interesa
It's what I would have done
es lo que yo hubiera hecho
What I don't see is the fact that it is good
lo que yo no veo es el hecho de bueno el
platform issue I think we are
tema de la plataforma creo que estamos
everyone agrees that they know everything
todos de acuerdo en que saben todo su
right does not want to participate
derecho no quiere participar la
platform each one can do with his
plataforma cada uno puede hacer con su
work and the way you manage it
trabajo y su forma de gestionar su
time whatever comes out of his balls
tiempo lo que le salga de los
with his videos
con sus vídeos
but don't tell him
pero que se lo diga no
I mean, like, I say later
o sea en plan yo es que luego digo yo de
right now I'm not the
momento ahora mismo no estoy la
platform not because it has the path no
plataforma no porque tenga el camino no
because the doors are closed to the
porque tenga las puertas cerradas a la
late or else because it is right now
tarde o sino porque es que ahora mismo
I can't even think of what to upload and I don't want to.
ni se me ocurren a qué subir ni quiero
delete in one of the videos I have neither
borrar en uno de los vídeos tengo ni
I have problems with monetization or
tengo problemas con la monetización ni
nothing but it is a platform that will help me
nada pero es una plataforma que me va a
come well there
venir bien ahí
but he says it and I think thank you very much and
pero dice lo y creo que muchas gracias y
I think the fact that I am a
creo que el hecho de yo que soy una
person closest to Juani ar and them
persona más cercana que juani ar y les
have said that it is not late or and with me
haya dicho que no es tarde o y conmigo
neither gets angry nor has changed nor in the
ni se enfada o ni ha cambiado ni en la
way of speaking is there I was talking
manera de hablar es ahí estuve hablando
with Dallas of something else
con dallas de otra cosa
and I noticed he was tense, let's go all out
y yo lo noté tenso vamos todo lo
on the contrary it has been cooked, that is not what it is
contrario se ha cocinado no es eso lo
that what Augustine bothers him
que le molesta lo que agustín
son says he listens to me that he doesn't listen to me
hijo dice lo escucha me que no me
interested
interesa
Dallas being watching, always watching
dallas siendo viendo siempre viendo
conspiracies where there are none on the subject
conspiraciones donde no la hay el tema
what I don't see where it should have been
lo que no veo dónde debería haberse
The euro is inserted according to who I have with
metido es el euro según tengo con quien
want
quiera
you're not going to go
no vas a ir
because they are telling others
porque se lo están contando a otros
I mean, it makes me really angry because
o sea me da mucha rabia porque
publicly what was said is not logical
públicamente lo dicho nada lógicamente
Here they are going to say that it is like he said in
aquí van a decir que o sea como dijo en
a month in a response on twitter that
un mes en una respuesta en twitter que
She specifically in a message to him
ella específicamente en un mensaje le
He said no, let's see
dijo que no a ver
And all this leads me to a question, Javi.
y todo esto me lleva a una pregunta javi
In your opinion, do you think that after a bad
en tu opinión crees que tras un mal
gesture or misunderstanding between two
gesto o malentendido entre dos
colleagues in the sector, you can return to
compañeros del sector se puede volver al
original point of friendship if the
punto original de amistad si es que la
there were or will be wells
hubo o quedarán pozos
To Mara Lpez, thank you very much
a maría lópez muchas gracias
yes man I think so
sí hombre yo creo que
I think so, I think so, I think so
yo creo que sí yo creo que yo creo que
It will be fixed, man, unless I don't consider it
se arreglará hombre a menos no considero
that this is a super strong thing
que esto sea una cosa súper fuerte
apart from the fact that Juan doesn't seem to be in good spirits
aparte que no se le vea a juan con ánimo
When fighting with him, they make pure excuses.
de pelear con él dicen puras excusas
write it to him because it is never public
escríbelo a él por por público jamás lo
you do to look good it is understood that
haces para quedar bien se entiende que
is busy but more than two months by
esté ocupada pero más de dos meses por
They only answered messages attacking the
sólo contestaron mensajes en atacan al
interest on your part that can tell him
interés por tu parte que puede decirle
no and that's it, he says he had already written it to him
no y ya está dice ya se lo había escrito
a would stop inventing heart a
a sería deja de inventar corazón un
hug
abrazo
no no no no no has only counted on
no no no no no sólo ha contado con
to
a
his friends but he knows the fault here
sus amigos pero él sabe la avería aquí
He says yes, he has told him no
dice que sí le ha dicho que no
I will do here is saying that if I had
haré aquí está diciendo que si le había
said no
dicho que no
Thanks from Castro - Thank you very much
gracias de castro- muchísimas gracias
Many might say that dada is a
muchos podrían decir es que dadas es un
hoarder wants to hoard me
acaparador quiere acaparar me
It is not very toxic, it is very intense because
no es muy tóxico es muy intenso por
example
ejemplo
thinking of taking thank you very much
pensando tomar muchísimas gracias
He says it reminded me of what they mentioned
dice a mí me recordó lo que mencionaron
Roberto's about the group that had the
de roberto sobre el grupo que tenían los
Four Juans did not send any messages
cuatro juan no mandaban ningún mensaje
of giving a lot and I think that neither
de darse mucho y creo que tampoco ni
I opened the group, I think they went like this
abría el grupo creo que pasaron para así
say yes I think that is a thing that
decir sí yo creo que eso es una cosa que
Wow
guau
it is usually
acostumbra ser
I just found out that he was dancing
simplemente me entero que bailaba
saying from behind
diciendo por el atrás
because I'm really on a wire
porque realmente estoy en un cable
publicly and she no longer says she here
públicamente y ya no dice ella ella aquí
The girl doesn't say no, why?
la tipa está no dice no por qué
because influencers don't talk about
porque los influencers no no habla de
two people and listen comes because
dos personas y escuchan viene porque
tells the exact story
relata la historia exacta
listening
escuchando
then staying tempered by that no
entonces quedándose templado por eso no
I understand because I don't know what you expect, right?
lo entiendo porque no sé qué esperas no
I know what you expect from people who don't even know you.
sé qué esperas de las personas que ni
not even the
siquiera los
terms
términos
that
que
bag has answered in yours and has
bolsa ha contestado en su tuyo y lo ha
denied everything that leads you to say a
negado todo el que os lleva a decir un
the tweets you sometimes pass by
los tweets que algunas veces pasas
I never get involved with anyone on YouTube.
yo no me mojo nunca por nadie de youtube
because look, can you imagine that in the end
porque mira os imagináis que al final
says
dice
says so okay okay okay okay one
dice así que vale vale vale vale una
clarification says that
aclaración dice que
wish and that in this tweet he is telling us
desear y que en este tuit nos está
saying no but that he already asked him
diciendo que no sino que ya le pidió
apologies to Dallas
disculpas a dallas
that he already apologized that here is not
que ya le pidió disculpa que aquí no
He's saying that he told him not to do the
está diciendo que le dijo que no haga la
and that of Cyrus, do you imagine that in
y la de ciro os imagináis que en
reality
realidad
Gonz Vela does know it from
gonzã vela sí que lo sabe por parte de
Ari
ari
I don't think so
no creo no
I don't really believe the things that have
en realidad no creo las cosas que ha
said knows they are very generic
dicho sabe las son muy genéricas las
conclusions we have reached
conclusiones a las que hemos llegado
almost all from outside
casi todos desde fuera
let's see what I tell you in plan is
a ver qué es lo que te digo en plan es
improve maybe they have told it to
mejorar igual se lo han contado a
someone close
alguien cercano
I was completely legitimate when they passed me
totalmente lícito yo cuando me pasaron
I only tell who I tell you but
solo cuento a quien te digo yo pero
You'll have to see if there was anything there
habréis a ver si ahí se lo hubiera
counted with knows the bag sails no
contado con sabe la bolsa vela no
I would talk about the subject in public because it is
hablaría del tema en público porque se
A friend is telling it in
lo está contando una amiga en
primary
primaria
an acquaintance to a colleague knows
una conocida a una compañera sabe
today is
hoy está
great but it seems to me
estupendo pero me parece
think
pensar
five specific things about the two of them that
cinco cosas específicas de ellos dos que
says this is not a coincidence
dice esto no es una coincidencia
who refers to two people with whom
a quién se refiere dos personas con las
that I have had problems I never had
que he tenido problemas yo nunca tuve
problems we connect the thanks king god
problemas conectamos el gracias rey dios
By the way, they were with me.
por cierto ellos estuvieron conmigo yo
never attack them publicly
jamás les ataque públicamente a ellos
on top of it it seems that it is but well look it is
encima como que es pero pues mira es
but by people to whom
pero por parte de personas a las cuales
after having attacked me I have
después de haberme atacado yo he
publicly defended in four
defendido públicamente en cuatro
different controversies throughout the
polémicas distintas a lo largo de los
years
años
I expect them to at least
espero de ellos que por lo menos me
respond
respondan
I'm not even telling you to help me with
ya ni siquiera te digo que me ayuden con
being in Osh is not helping me
estar de osh que no es ayudarme a mí
It's just about keeping themselves with
solo es quedarse ellos mismos con
content that doesn't make money
contenidos que no generan dinero
and now generate it like this
y ahora así generarlo
the thing is
es que
Christopher, don't be a jerk either, let's see.
christopher no seas tampoco a ver
Christopher knows he's talking about her
christopher con sabe la está hablando de
d
d
bag sail to see what people have given for
bolsa vela a ver la gente ha dado por
fact that referred to Juana Ari, let's see
hecho que se refería a juana ari a ver
let's listen look being totally
vamos a escuchar mira siendo totalmente
aim
objetivo
being totally adjective here they put it
siendo totalmente adjetivo aquí le ponen
on Twitter on October 3rd to Ari Juan
en twitter el 3 de octubre a la ari juan
They were invited but never said anything
fueron invitados pero nunca dijeron nada
and dalla says effectively okay here
y dalla dice efectivamente vale aquí
Dallas confirms that Juani is and never
dallas confirma que juani ar y nunca le
They said nothing about making an invitation, okay?
dijeron nada de hace invitación vale no
They responded to his invitation and then
dieron respuesta a su invitación y luego
have
tenemos
in the video he vents
en el vídeo que se desahoga
I had thought that I had to have and I know
yo había ideado que tenía que tener y sé
that will have it in it at some point
que lo tendrá en algún momento en él
this way at the end
por aquí por el final
ask on time maybe a while ago
pedir en hora hace tiempo tal vez
all these others too by the way
todo estas otras también por cierto
youtubers and this one pissed me off
youtubers y está me ha
deeply youtubers some of the
profundamente youtubers algunos de los
which I even did favors for
cuales incluso hasta les hecho favores
I even have the level of defending them
yo nivel de incluso hasta defenderlos
publicly when I talk to them
públicamente cuando hablo con ellos me
They say yes, what a good idea to be there
dicen al sí que buena idea lo de estar
of or if I love it I don't know that I don't know
de o si me encanta no sé que no sé
how many and when it finally comes out I'll tell you
cuántos y cuando por fin sale les digo
Hey, I need your help. We are here.
oye necesitó de tu ayuda estamos
starting we must support now so that
empezando hay que apoyar ahora para que
then this can actually result in
después esto pueda realmente resulta en
something and what they do is literally good
algo y lo que hacen literalmente es bien
ghosting me but complete and
hacerme ghosting pero completo y
absolute support since not even
absoluto sostén ya que ni siquiera
answer me at all leave me
responderme en absoluto dejarme
completely in sight but
completamente en visto pero
completely in direct view
completamente en visto directamente
tell me no, if it turns out well, if it succeeds, it is
decirme no ya si sale bien si triunfa es
as if it triumphs or is that I need now no
como si triunfa o sea necesito ahora no
later later I don't need you at all
después después no te necesito para nada
now is like I need you now is like
ahora es como te necesito ahora es como
You have the opportunity to show that
tienes la oportunidad de mostrar que
you can support when we are at
puedes apoyar cuando estamos al
principle when it is necessary to support it for
principio cuando hay que apoyarlo para
that it starts to come out is that on top of it
que comience a salir es que encima
Physics I'm asking you for something that is
física te estoy pidiendo algo que sea
just for me which is also for you
sólo para mí que también es para ti
We are talking about offering you a
estamos hablando de que te ofrece una
platform where you will not be demobilized
plataforma donde no te va a desmovilizar
absolutely nothing, everything is going to happen to you
absolutamente nada que todo se te va a
pay all this payment plus what it's going to
pagar todo este pago más se lo que va a
pay for tweets in is late or is paid to the
pagar tweets en es tarde o se paga a los
creators more than what the creator himself pays
creadores más de lo que paga el propio
tweet and on top of that each one publishes
tweet y que encima cada uno publíquese
automatically reach your subscribers
llega automáticamente a tus suscriptores
YouTube doesn't even notify its users
youtube ni siquiera notifica a sus
subscribers when you upload a video to
suscriptores cuando tú subes un vídeo a
youtube youtube the well-being of the
youtube youtube el bienestar de los
students after taking it is positive
estudiantes luego que tome es positivo
for you and you're telling me now and
para ti y me estás diciendo a mí ahora y
you'll see, you'll see later when
ya verás ya verás más adelante cuando
literally many the only thing there is to
literalmente muchos lo único que hay que
to do is summarize your videos of the
hacer es resumir sus vídeos del
monetized are videos that by themselves are not
monetizados sean vídeos que de por si no
They are generating Van Gogh's
les están generando de van gogh
abandoned now foster money in
abandonados ahora fomento dinero en
youtube summaries late or if until
youtube los resúmenes tarde o si hasta
They already make money from those videos that already
ya ganan dinero por esos vídeos que ya
They did neither that nor that, I don't even know.
hicieron ni eso ni eso full no sé ni
how to call it then call it varies no
cómo llamarlo entonces llamarlo varía no
I don't know if I should call it double-sided, I don't know if
sé si llamarlo doble cara no sé si
Call it interested, I don't know what to call it
llamarlo interesado no sé cómo llamarlo
but there are many like that I'm talking about
pero hay muchos así estoy hablando de
that Alves contacts without exaggeration 100
que alves contacte con sin exagerar 100
youtubers and some of them quite
youtubers y algunos de ellos bastante
large and of them 100 maybe 90
grandes y de ellos se 100 puede que 90
they have perfectly hosted me or
perfectamente me hayan hecho hosting o
They haven't answered me at all because
no me hayan respondido en absoluto por
What they answered me was that right now
lo que me respondían fuera eso de ya
We will see when it triumphs and when it triumphs
veremos cuando triunfe y cuando triunfa
active costs you nothing is that it is being
activo te cuesta nada es que se está
referring to several to see if it is
refiriendo a varios a ver si que es
true that clear
verdad que claro
You add the tweets, not you add this tweet.
tú sumas el tweets no tú sumas este tuit
Schumacher
schumacher
this anger
el cabreo este
and if you stop following them, the murky thing is
y su más dejarlos de seguir lo turbio es
the fairy's face painted in the background
la cara del hada pintada de fondo
but then people have taken it for granted
pero entonces la gente ha dado por hecho
yes it is true that I just realized
por sí que es verdad que me acabo de dar
Note that water is not mentioned here.
cuenta que aquí no se refiere agua
because of course Juan and Ari
porque claro juan y ari
has not responded
no ha respondido
It is said no, when I triumph I will rise yes
se dice no ya cuando triunfe subiré si
Juan has not responded, he is not here
juan no ha respondido no se está
referring to water is referring to
refiriendo agua se está refiriendo a
other people here don't
otra gente aquí no
We'll see that phrase later, Juan la
esa frase ya veremos después juan la
He said live, let's see if no no no but
dijo en directo a ver si no no no pero
Dallas says someone answers him.
dallas dice que alguien le contesta
Let's see, here he is talking about Juanar and
a ver aquí está hablando de juanar y
obviously but generally more
evidentemente pero en general de más
people
gente
It could also be people like Juan de
podría ser gente también como juan de
god' no
dios' no
here in Berlin
aquí en berlín
and Javi
y javi
before Dallas never says that Harry
ante el dallas nunca dice que harry le
gave information to that girl but to
dio información a esa chica sino a
someone else and that spread elsewhere
alguien más y eso lo regó por otro lado
That always happens, Dallas has already said it.
siempre pasa eso dallas ya lo ha dicho
They are all hypocrites, all those who
todos ellos son hipócritas todos los que
They are in an omelet
están en tortilla
but still no one could find her
pero al igual no la encontraba nadie
when we went straight to see
cuando dimos directo a ver
[Music]
[Música]
My error is probably about 500
probablemente mi error sea de unos 500
a thousand according to me for example I tell you in
mil según yo por ejemplo te lo digo en
Twitter, according to me, I have two million here.
twitter según yo tengo dos millones acá
of several things that cannot be seen
de varias cosas que no se puede ver
I started but I think there are like a hundred left
empecé pero creo que si faltan como cien
a thousand data visits had had to see bequeathed to me
mil datos visitas tuvo tuvo ver me legó
from the daily view goal because I heard
del daily view gol pues oía a
buy it I bought the plans approx no
comprarlo lo compré los planes aprox no
Scott today but the one where the lizard appears
scott hoy pero la que aparece el lagarto
eggs straight from Coca-Cola I think
huevos de directa de cocacola creo que
can become a competition
pueda llegar a hacer una competencia
direct but a very good one
directa pero sí una muy buena
alternative to the little that I have seen
alternativa a lo poquito que yo he visto
Look, I can enter the page.
mira que me puedo entrar a la página
because it has fallen I don't know if it continues
porque se ha caído no no sé si sigue
fall and in 36 after 150 thousand at the same time
caída y en 36 en tras 150 mil al mismo
time and he died, we all know that
tiempo y se nos murió todos sabemos que
You want to enter, so leave us your email.
quieres entrar así que déjanos tu e-mail
If it is still down, why is it that the
si todavía sigue caído porque es que la
people broke it too many people came in
gente se lo peto entró demasiada gente
which is fine is a very good sign
lo cual está bien es una muy buena señal
by the way, there's not much left for five
by the way faltan poco para los cinco
millions in tweets are almost there
millones en tuits falta poco
Dallas also doesn't follow Kimberley because it's not
dallas tampoco sigue a kimberley por no
answer you we have already said it before
contestarle ya lo hemos dicho antes
Damn, where's the hotel video, dude?
dónde está el vídeo del hotel tío
Saleh
saleh
Look, Juan has reacted to videos of
mira juan ha reaccionado a vídeos de
Dallas too
dallas también
what do you mean by that
qué quiere decir con eso
And where is his stuff?
y yo donde está lo de los de él
this pitiful
este penoso
what a shame what a shame
qué pena qué pena
and where is the bird thing?
y yo donde está lo de ave
where is the hotel uncle I want to see
dónde está la del hotel tío quiero ver
is that it said exactly
es que decía exactamente
the uncle
el tío
but if we saw it here it far exceeds the
pero si lo vimos aquí supera a mano el
another day
otro día
We saw it super cute the other day
lo vimos super amaro al otro día
through
mediante
Thanks friends, what do you think about that?
gracias amigos opina acerca de eso qué
You want me to give my opinion, I think that the
quieres que opine yo pienso que los
Videos speak louder than my opinion
vídeos hablan más que una opinión mía
I think they know what my opinion is and
yo pienso que saben cuál es mi opinión y
My side, I really like Dallas.
mi bando yo yo me cae muy bien dallas
Listen to me Juana Apoyo if this is
escúchame juana apoyado si es que esto
It costs me publicly that one has
me costa a mí públicamente que one ha
supported Dallas a lot in the defense
apoyado mucho a dallas en la defendido
publicly in other things
públicamente en otras cosas
in wing michu things and in things a
en cosas de wing michu y en cosas un
author clicked so I did too
autor puso el clic así que yo también
the buses
los buses
very good
muy buena
a little bit
un cachito
and then doing live shows is difficult and
y luego hacer directos es difícil y
apart from char I'm going to start uploading videos
aparte char voy a empezar a subir vídeos
on Facebook that I'm not going to upload to YouTube
en facebook que no voy a subir a youtube
That is, there will be other things
o sea van a ser otras cosas
completely apart does not mean that
completamente aparte no significa que
I'm going to upload to YouTube not in what
voy a dar de subidas a youtube no en lo
Absolutely, but I'm going to upload videos now.
absoluto pero si ya voy a subir vídeos
in three happy silver in three channels by
en tres plata feliz en tres canales por
so to speak and doing live shows I don't
así decirlo y haciendo directos no me
I create with the ability to upload videos
creo con la capacidad de subir vídeos
also on another new platform no
también en en otra plataforma nueva no
I can't cope if I had a team that
no doy abasto si tuviera un equipo que
will take care of those specific things
se encargará de esas cosas en específico
because what we have is an agency that
porque lo que tenemos es una agencia que
He is more dedicated to advertising issues
se dedica más en los temas de publicidad
but if I had a team like that
pero si tuviera un equipo como por así
The production comes out a little more for me
lo productora me sale un poquito más
easy but I don't have it and what is happening
fácil pero no lo tengo y lo que se está
putting it in is like taking out a one
metiendo es como si yo sacara una un
soft drink that was the competition
refresco que fuera la competencia
Direct from Coca-Cola, the market is already there
directa de cocacola el mercado ya está
very imposed is a very ambitious challenge
muy impuesto es un reto muy ambicioso
that although it can generate I believe that
que si bien puede generar yo creo que
good results at the economic and
buenos resultados a nivel económico y de
popularity I don't think it can reach
popularidad no creo que pueda llegar a
make direct competition but yes
hacer una competencia directa pero sí
a very good alternative by the way
una muy buena alternativa por cierto
clinic has been Juana's and that of
clínica ha sido lo de juana y lo de
would do something that has been notorious since no
haría algo que ha sido notorio dalla no
has concealed
ha disimulado
they are going to be in stadiums
van a estar en estadios
I have said it many times planet yes
yo lo he dicho muchas veces planeta sí
for me to already manage two channels and then
para mí ya manejar dos canales y luego
doing live shows is difficult and apart from that
hacer directos es difícil y aparte ya
I'm going to start uploading videos on Facebook
voy a empezar a subir vídeos en facebook
that I'm not going to upload to YouTube, that is, they're going to
que no voy a subir a youtube o sea van a
do other things completely not
hacer otras cosas completamente no lo
says I'm going
dice ir yo
Now the part was coming
ahora se venía la parte
you get to position yourself very well and you can see it
se llega a posicionar muy bien y se ve
as a very good one reaches more than
como una muy bueno se llega más de
Dallas is positioned very well and
dallas se llega a posicionar muy bien y
It looks like a very good opportunity to
se ve como una muy buena oportunidad a
The best and I already said, hey, how cool am I?
lo mejor y ya digo oye qué chido le voy
to introduce this anal nuance
a meter este matiz anal
if then we could say that
si entonces si podríamos decir que
dallas and that left enough pizza that
dallas y que dejaba bastante pizza que
so that we would know that he was Juan Garino
a que conociéramos que era juan garino
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes let's see if
sí sí sí sí sí sí sí a ver si se
He understood calmly
entendió tranquilamente
It was calmly understood if we cannot
se entendió tranquilamente si no podemos
say that we are going to see her has been the one that has
decir que vamos a verla sido la que ha
discovered the formula for Coca-Cola
descubierto la fórmula de la coca-cola
you know how with that candle we have
sabes cómo que con esa vela nos haya
opened the way
abierto el camino
[Laughs]
[Risas]
like what I hope
como que que espero
I hope that at least they answer me
espero que por lo menos me respondan es
what it is but it is that on top of that not even
lo que es pero es que encima ni siquiera
I talked about them in my life, I said contact
hable de ellos en mi vida dije contacte
with more than 100 and I think in the video
con más de 100 y yo creo que en el vídeo
his
suyo
It refers to one year and also but that
se refiere a one year y también pero que
refers to more refers to more people
se refiere a más se refiere a más gente
fluence ers refers to more people not
fluence ers se refiera más gente no
only to the Balearic Islands
solamente a baleares
at what point did Brad talk about them?
en qué momento hable de ellos brad de
thank you so much
muchas gracias
incredible
increíble
incredible thanks mj measurable I tell you
increíble gracias mj medibles os digo
very seriously incredible then
muy en serio increíble luego
subsequently
posteriormente
and proceeds to answer me in a message
ar y procede a responderme en un mensaje
where it says it is true we have a lot
en donde dice es verdad tenemos mucho
problem with casting that changed
problema con hacer casting que cambio
I believe and yes yes yes they have it they have it
creo y sí sí sí lo tienen lo tienen
I think it is a doubt about the mobile value
yo creo que es duda del móvil valor
then also then
luego también pues
that it is no evil
que no sea ningún mal
the message itself does not attempt to
el mensaje en sí mismo no intent a
variable also refers to truth is
variable también se refiere verdad es
What marsh is Maria look at him
que marjal es maria le mira
before drama starts I want
antes de que se arme drama quiero
clarify that I simply don't have time
aclarar que simplemente no tengo tiempo
to generate exclusive content for
para generar contenido exclusivo para
a new platform in addition to the
una nueva plataforma adicional a los
videos that I upload daily on YouTube
vídeos que subo diariamente en youtube
We have always wished you all the best
hemos siempre deseándole todos los
improvements to aunts late or well
mejoras a las tías tarde o bueno
Listen to me, he said, hey, I'm cold
escúchame es el ha dicho oye tengo frío
short
corta
a while being cold time that older
un rato teniendo frío tiempo que mayores
in the clear pulses and then no
en los pulsos claros y entonces no
we would be putting in the bag
estaríamos metiendo en el saco
for how to fix anything by itself or that is
para cómo arreglar nada de por sí o sea
don't try to say like Dallas, I
no intenta como decir ni a dallas yo
I'm very sorry because for me I
siento mucho porque para mí yo
I sincerely tell you, very honestly, I don't
sinceramente os digo muy honesto no me
It had been important to take it and say okay it is
había importado y decir vale está
come on
bien venga
It was a mistake, no more, we will return to
fue un error sin más vamos a volver a
try it
intentarlo
If I had said any Dallas plan it would be
si hubiera dicho algún plan de dallas es
We are really sorry for you, the truth is
que los sentimos un montón la verdad es
that has completely passed us by, no
que se nos ha pasado por completo no
We have thought about it and we would like to
hemos pensado en ello y nos gustaría de
It is true that we will resume our friendship and this
verdad que retomaremos la amistad y esta
time to do it really well and you
vez hacerlo bien de verdad y te
We promise it won't happen again
prometemos que no volverá a pasar
With that I would have already said it although
con eso ya lo hubiera dicho aunque
I previously said no to those people.
anteriormente de esa gente yo dije ya no
is to pretend friendship
es pretender la amistad
although he said that
aunque ha dicho eso
But I say this very seriously because I don't know
pero lo digo muy en serio porque no se
treats
trata
about that
de eso
organically or you don't do it you have to
orgánicamente o no lo haces tú tú tienes
good vibes of cordiality with people
buen rollo de cordialidad con la gente
that with this one no and with time it is not known
que con esta no y ya con el tiempo no se
make it a friendship or not Alex
convierte en una amistad o no álex
Thank you very much but it's not like you
muchas gracias pero no es como que tú
cooler this way, colleague, many
más fresca de esta manera colega muchas
times Alex, I mean I don't mean that this
veces álex o sea no me refiero que este
I don't offer you a comment that seems to be from school.
comentario parece del cole no te ofrezco
My friendship is good for us on this side
mi amistad bien este lado para nosotros
and above all I can be your friend no
y sobre todo yo puedo ser tu amigo no
We already had people like that today we are here
personas así ya tuvo hoy estamos
I find it is not cool, it did not touch me
encuentro yo no está guay no me tocó a
These fixes do not forgive me this
éstos solucionar no me perdonan esto me
Sorry about the other thing, hey, you have a problem
perdonan lo otro oye tienes un problema
I don't have it and with time
yo no lo tiene y con el tiempo
organically one arises to under-exercise
orgánicamente surge uno subejercer
friends friends no it's not like you
amigos los amigos no no es como que tú
You see, I say now I want to be friends with
veas yo digo ahora quiero ser amigo de
goal knows the
gol sabe la
with sabella wants to be my friend and
con sabella quiere ser mi amiga y
we are friends
somos amigos
okay let's go let's go
está bien vamos vamos
literally his message is a
literalmente su mensaje es un
Well I wish you the best and much success in
bueno te deseo lo mejor y mucho éxito en
your projects and what is offered
tus proyectos y lo que se ofrezca un
I hug you and beautiful Alicia now that
abrazo a ti y alicia hermosa ahora que
I tell you, it is being said that see you later
te diga se está diciendo que hasta luego
it's literally a take my excuses
es literalmente un toma mis excusas
but that it goes well for you
pero de que te vaya bien
goodbye, hams, well, tribe, time for later
goodbye hamás bien tribu time para luego
what does he want
que quiere
That's a yes if your life is the
ese es un sí si tu vida la son el
example of this from cage goodbye to de
ejemplo de esto de cage adiós a de
organic friendship change I did not have
amistad orgánica cambio yo no tenía
no intention of being his friend
ninguna intención de ser su amigo
absolutely nothing and I imagine that
absoluta de para nada y me imagino que
He doesn't do it with me either
él conmigo tampoco
in fact we said no, listen to me
de hecho decíamos no yo escúchame
cordial, not lacking in respect and
cordial no falta respeto y
criticism
crítica
Dallas must be bridging the gap
dallas debe ser salvando las distancias
of people like Steve Jobs at some point
de las personas como steve jobs en algún
moment will succeed in his project and his
momento triunfará en su proyecto y su
platform will be worth millions of course because
plataforma valdrá millones claro porque
no auto action a good idea and there is no
no autito acción una buena idea y no hay
others actually that change mixer
otras en realidad que cambio mixer
failure
fracaso
I'm not fatal
yo no fatal
[Music]
[Música]
Tokyo I don't know what I lived yesterday
tokio no sé que vivo ayer
Tomorrow is not about graduating from the platform
mañana no es titularse en la plataforma
the new youtube no ocean plan te
la nueva youtube no ocean plan te
you wait and with the years one year two years
esperas y con los años un año dos años
five years is known, so it is already
cinco años se sabe pues ya está
growing and is and will continue to sound in the
creciendo y está y seguirá sonando en la
everyone's head because this
cabeza de todo el mundo porque esta
tonight I'm going to upload a very video
noche yo voy a subir un vídeo muy
controversial and youtube won't let me upload it and
polémico y youtube no me deja subirlo y
If you want to upload it to YouTube or come
se meterse subirlo a youtube o viene
serious and throws me a video again and I say
grave y me tira un vídeo otra vez y digo
So curly now he doesn't see his well-being
así crespo ahora no ve a su bienestar
but throw it away and if you have balls or you have
pero tirarlo y si tienes huevo o tienes
A fart doesn't just emerge over time
un peo no se va surgiendo por el tiempo
I hope it goes well, I don't know if you understand me
que vaya bien no sé si me entendéis
because like seeing, looking a little bit
porque como que ver mirar un poquito
between the lines I explain myself no
entre líneas me explico no
ar and I think it should go up
ar y yo creo que debería subir
I think I should go up and explain no
yo creo que debería subir y explicar no
your ari version
tu versión ari
the tp project to lose its strength
el proyecto de tp de perder su recio
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] failure of course
fracaso por supuesto
and I think I should go up and
y yo creo que debería subir y
explain to us how well we are not doing
explicarnos lo bien porque no lo estamos
understanding nothing well I will do I think that
entendiendo nada bien haré yo creo que
you should go up because we are not
deberías subir porque no nos estamos
knowing nothing, I think Dallas will
enterando de nada pienso que a dallas le
It affects him because he has been so closed off
afecta porque él ha estado tan cerrado
for what has happened to him and if he opens up to
por lo que le ha pasado y si se abre a
someone and they do something to him it hurts him more than
alguien y le hacen algo le duele más de
the normal thing
lo normal
Let's see this kid
a ver este chaval
They have done a lot of damage in the past and that
han hecho mucho daño en el pasado y eso
want it not to condition you a little
quiera que no le condiciona un poco
Dallas has to get over it
dallas tiene que superarlo
You have to get over the things of the
tiene que superar ya las cosas del
past is worth it
pasado vale
in the sense that it has to
en el sentido de que tiene que
normalize the situation because because already
normalizar la situación porque porque ya
already
ya
really gives the many times believes that
realmente da las muchas veces cree que
There are people who don't like it or groups that
hay gente a la que le cae mal o grupos a
those who dislike him and really don't
los que él le cae mal y realmente no
have nothing against him has happened to me
tienen nada en contra de él me ha pasado
I have happened to see him as he believes himself to be
me ha pasado de verlo como él se cree
that there are people who can't see it or
que hay gente que no lo puede ver o
people who speak badly of him, he believes it
gente que habla mal de él él se lo cree
but then I know the groups a little
pero luego yo conozco un poco los grupos
and I know that they don't have a bad relationship with him
y sé que no que no le tienen mala mala
image or whatever you know
imagen o lo que sea sabes
so that you can see that things affect
para que veáis que las cosas afectan
you know so that you can see that things
sabes para que veáis que las cosas
affect
afectan
oh well
pero bueno
There you have the tortilla event now no
ahí tiene el evento de tortilla ahora no
has been
ha se
has already gone
ha ido ya
but I think I think I'm going to go up
pero yo creo que yo creo que voy a subir
Because I said this is not clear to us
porque dije no nos queda claro esto
let's see one thing
a ver una cosa
area that is not clear to us this
área que no nos queda claro esto
Thank you Laura, thank you very much
gracias laura muchísimas gracias
It is that this is not clear to us and
es que no nos queda claro esto y
you should clarify I won't do it
deberías aclarar no lo haré
until the artillery event
hasta el evento de artillería
will no longer be here
ya no estará por aquí
13 ms laura b
13 ms laura b
and 13m sacks
y 13m sacos
Of course it is open 10,000
claro que si es abierta 10.000
free viewers to see I say it
espectadores de gratis a ver yo lo digo
for her
por ella
to do him a favor
para hacerle el favor
something
alguna cosa
is that the insurance that I thought to leave the
es que el seguro que pensaba dejar la
keel
quilla
It's that if Juan is going to talk now, right now
es que si juan va a hablar ahora ahorita
From those in Dallas, let me know, let me know
de los de dallas pues avísame avísame
Please don't start talking about the subject right away.
por favor no empieza a hablar del tema a
see
ver
big for follows for not answering
en grande por follows por no contestar
messages integrating this already results in a
mensajes integrando esto ya resulta un
high school problem and even
problema de preparatoria e incluso de
secondary school I don't know if I'm the only one who
secundaria yo no sé si soy el único que
he sees it like this
lo ve así
or is it that I just don't see it you know
o es que simplemente no lo veo sabes
but I'm not into fighting over sheets of paper.
pero a mí andar peleando por folios por
not answering a message and nothing like that
no contestar un mensaje y nada de eso
moderators I would also appreciate you
moderadores también agradecería ustedes
comply with the emo test mode because it
cumplan con el modo emo test porque lo
The last thing I want is to read opinions myself.
que menos quiero es leer opiniones yo
I just want to say what I think
simplemente quiero decir lo que pienso
It seems to me that all this is a
a mí me parece que todo esto es una
situation of teenagers who ignore me
situación de adolescentes que me ignora
this is a message
este un mensaje
me
me
you stopped following me these are things that
me dejaste de seguir esto son cosas que
To me, they honestly seem very banal.
a mí sinceramente me parecen muy banales
and I'm not interested in Dallas.
y no me interesan yo con dallas la he
I screwed up and I screwed up really hard and
cagado y la he cagado muy fuerte y por
Forgive me for that, yes, forgive me with
eso me perdone yo sí me perdone con
Dallas was because he genuinely recognized
dallas fue porque genuinamente reconoció
a mistake not out of interest
un error no por interés
If I had been interested I would be
si hubiera sido interesado estaría
behind any person all the
detrás de cualquier persona todo el
time
tiempo
From that moment on my relationship with
a partir de ese momento mi relación con
I think he has been cordial.
él pienso yo que ha sido cordial ha sido
kind will return rather and he can and
amable volverá más bien y él lo puede y
You can see it on your friendship channel.
lo pueden ver en su canal de amistad yo
I have defended some situations
he defendido de algunas situaciones unas
that I am so grateful to you may be because
que le agradezco demasiado puede ser por
example the topic of the bed and when it is
ejemplo el tema de la cama y cuando se
He was stalking me in a way
me estaba acosando de una manera
ridiculous and there I genuinely
ridícula y ahí yo genuinamente le
I was grateful because I believe that although I
agradecí porque creo que si bien me
It also helped him a lot because it
ayudó bastante también a él pues le
likes to talk about these topics to get your
gusta hablar de estos temas llegar su
thematic with other topics such as
temática con otros temas como por
An example is Roberto Barca and everything.
ejemplo son los de roberto barca y todo
I never spoke about the subject of those four
el tema de esos cuatro yo jamás hablé
With Dallas, I was in Ibiza.
con dallas de eso yo estaba en ibiza
when this and I could tell you that and
cuando esto y les podría decir que y
I think I could confirm this.
esto creo que lo podría confirmar
perfectly I never spoke to him about
perfectamente yo jamás hablé con él de
that topic not even yet what did you think
ese tema ni siquiera aún que te pareció
nothing
nada
I think he didn't ask for it, I think it was from
creo que no se lo pidió creo que fue de
He spoke because quite some time later
él hablo porque bastante tiempo después
a week later a few days
una semanita después unos cuantos días
After I told him, hey, thanks for
después que yo le dije oye gracias por
I appreciate it a lot for putting yourself there but
ponerte ahí te lo agradezco montón pero
I never asked for it, I never asked for it and I want it
yo jamás lo pedí yo yo jamás y quiero
Let me be very clear about something: Dallas is not
que quede algo muy claro a mí dallas no
I don't like him at all and he knows it.
me cae mal en lo absoluto yo y se lo
I wrote yesterday in private
escribí el día de ayer por privado
because I think the person who
porque creo que la persona que le
It must be his interest that he spoke to me yesterday
interesa debe ser a él ayer él habló mi
admiration and my appreciation towards yesterday
admiración y mi aprecio hacia el ayer el
who spoke to Dallas then
cual habló a dallas entonces
continue, I know that he has it
continúa yo a mí me consta que le tiene
They told him and in a good and thin way
se lo dijeron y de buenas y delgado como
I tell you and I tell you today
les digo y se los digo hoy a ustedes
I regret and disappointment to Dallas and
yo lamentos y decepciones a dallas y
somehow and also this too
alguna manera y también esto también
There is the private message I am very sorry if
está el mensaje privado lamento mucho si
I ended up disappointing them as a person
llegué a decepcionarlos como persona
as friendship
como amistad
but it would happen yesterday after the book and its
pero pasaría ayer después del libro y su
cordial did not answer messages yes and you
cordial no contestó mensajes sí y te
I could say ask him
podría decir que le preguntes a
any friend to any acquaintance already
cualquier amigo a cualquier conocido ya
anyone who has spoken
cualquier persona que haya hablado
with me if you have never left it on read
conmigo si nunca lo ha dejado en visto
I ask you to achieve it, how strange it is
te lo pido a lograrlo lo raro que se
anyone asks anyone
pregunta la cualquiera a cualquiera
ask him sometime I'll let you have seen
pregúntale alguna vez te dejo han visto
Juan
juan
because if I leave, it's not like he'll open the door for me
porque si me marcho no es que me abre el
message and I don't know it's me I'm a little bit
mensaje y no sé soy yo soy un poquito
so the truth is that it is something that in the
así la verdad si es algo que en la
current events is an offense and deserves
actualidad es una ofensa y que merece
that the whole internet is on me again
que todo internet otra vez me esté
crucifying again
volviendo a crucificar
and I tell you
y te digo yo
sorry now I will pay more attention to that and
perdón ahora me fijaré más en eso y
I will try to change it
trataré de cambiarlo
but but I don't know the truth is that everything
pero pero no sé la verdad es que todo
This topic seems extremely to me I will not do it
este tema me parece sumamente no lo haré
The friend said, "You don't know, that is."
ha dicho el amigo no sabes o sea
I have seen opinions from very good people
he visto opiniones de personas muy
mature ones to whom I also have a
maduras a las que también les tengo un
a certain appreciation for the subject and that
cierto aprecio acerca del tema y que
They arrive and say, let's see, I think it's ugly.
llegan y dicen a ver me parece feo lo
from the casting and it's like for, I think
del casting y es como para o sea creo
that if I'm screwing up and I don't realize it
que si la estoy y no me doy
counts but refers to the person
cuenta pero se refiere a la persona
mature
madura
If I tell you something, it's for me.
yo si algo les digo ustedes es por mi
part and I said it the other day that I
parte y lo dije el otro día que me
They asked where I was going to fall
preguntaron dónde se me va a caer la
wave mark and I said I didn't even know
marca de onda las y yo dije yo ni sabía
that I had a sheet of paper and I told them why
que me había de un folio y les dije por
My part is all good, I think it's a
mi parte todo bien pienso que es una
excellent person and all that and yet
excelente persona y todo eso y aún así
after everything that happened yesterday, too
después de todo lo de ayer también se
I say to you
los digo a ustedes
I think he's a good person, I think
me parece una buena persona me parece
that is a person but where was that
que es una persona pero donde estaba que
there are some who have done very good things that
hay que ha hecho cosas muy buenas que
As a person he has done quite a few things
como persona ha hecho cosas bastante
impressive one man said
impresionantes uno ha dicho un hombre
all immature and with white hair
todos inmaduro y con el pelo blanco le
I said yesterday that if I want to talk later on
dije ayer que si luego quiero hablar por
private we can perfectly talk and
privado perfectamente podemos hablar y
now you shouldn't talk here
ahora no deberías hablar aquí la
need to say yes nor do I
necesidad de decir que sí ni yo tampoco
It's that what I'm telling you is one thing
es que es que lo que les digo es una es
an extremely cordial relationship and I want
una relación sumamente cordial y quiero
clarify a few similar things I
aclarar unas cuantas cositas iguales yo
I think they should not be with anyone
creo que deberían con nadie a las
backs of dallas this girl with
espaldas de dallas esta chica con
Sabella was giving her opinion as a curtain
sabella estaba opinando como cortina
anyone as my friend thinks
cualquier persona como opina mi compa
Javi as inhaled as anyone
javi como inhalada como a cualquier
person you know nothing is change that you
persona sabes nada es cambio que te
I gave away without speaking to her for
regalaba yo no hablado con ella por
private in my life I had to take her
privado en mi vida la tenía que llevarme
It was once that I was without video donating
fue una vez que estaba sin vídeo donando
streamers that was the only time that
streamers esa fue la única vez que
interacted with her I think that
interactuado con ella yo creo que
the thing that speaks the backs of
la cosa que hablar las espaldas de
Dallas
dallas
the backs
las espaldas
if I don't dislike him and directly and if I
si no me cae mal y directamente y si me
falls and if I don't like it, I don't think I'll even do it
cae y si me cae mal creo que ni lo hago
Chavez then
chávez entonces
I, I have spoken badly behind the back of
yo yo han hablado mal a las espaldas de
Dallas did not speak badly to the Maltese late
dallas no hablado mal a las maltés tarde
I never give you my opinion of being
os en ningún momento mi opinión de estar
I gave it to you many times live
de os la di muchas veces en directo yo
I don't think I saw her even twice
creo que no la vi ni siquiera dos veces
I think that even three times in
yo creo que la de incluso tres veces en
direct or work said that their service
directos o trabaje decía que su servicio
Bordals, who although he has the
bordalás que si bien tiene la
very tough competition can generate
competencia muy difícil puede generar
good income for me and that's it
buenos ingresos que para mí y eso lo
I also said live many times
dije también en directo muchas veces
It is impossible for me to put in later
para mí es imposible meter más tarde os
so summarize videos because I have two
así sea resumir vídeos porque tengo dos
YouTube channels I have 20 videos a day
canales de youtube tengo 20 vídeos al
month on Facebook and the truth is that I don't
mes en facebook y la verdad es que no
I feel the need at this moment to
siento la necesidad en este momento de
enter another platform nor
entrar en otra plataforma ni tampoco
I have the time this week for me to
tengo el tiempo esta semana para que yo
There is something that beats me, there are people who manage
lo hay me gana hay gente que administra
better time than me too but I
mejor el tiempo que yo también pero yo
I have a very quiet lifestyle
tengo un estilo de vida muy tranquilo
But Warner says it's something that I
pero dice la warner bien es algo que me
It bothers me a lot and I am very calm
molesta mucho y yo estoy muy tranquilo
Now believe me I'm not trying not to
actualmente créanme que no trato de no
get into absolutely nothing and you
meterme en absolutamente nada y ustedes
they realize, that is, I, I, my
se dan cuenta o sea yo yo mis
worries are getting up enjoying myself
preocupaciones son levantarme disfrutar
my morning watching something on TV
mi mañana viendo algo en la tele
sit here to work and at night
sentarme aquí a trabajar y en la noche
go to dinner and that's what I want
irme a cenar y es lo que yo quiero que
I get into more [ __ ] but say it
se me meta más en pero decirlo
although later people are there again
aunque luego otra vez la gente esté ahí
again again again again I don't do it
otra vez otra vez otra vez yo no lo
finally clarified I'm avoiding everything
aclaró finalmente estoy evitando todo
to get into trouble I declared it to
para meterme en cagadas yo lo declaró a
I see a lot that I should come here
mucho yo veo que debería venir para acá
Juan, I don't see it clearly.
juan yo no lo veo claro
I see that you should come here
yo veo que deberíais de venir para acá
really
de verdad
Also, I'm coming, he says, I think that
además ya vengo dice yo creo que
They should come and talk about it here in
deberían de venir a hablarlo aquí en
person because it is what is left for us
persona porque es que nos está quedando
This is not at all clear
nada claro esto
I see that this is not leaving anything
yo veo que esto no está quedando nada
clear
claro
Let's see, the only fault here is the lack of
a ver aquí el único fallo es la falta de
communication
comunicación
since the only fault here says what
ya que aquí el único fallo dice lo que
I can't but I'm interested, yes it is
no puedo pero me interesa sí que es
truth that he has said in public
verdad que él ha dicho en público
dallas there
dallas ahí
It's not that everything is super super either.
es que tampoco que sea todo súper súper
super serious and he's not coming here
súper grave y no está viniendo para acá
if he's coming when I think he is
si está viniendo cuando creo que está
coming here goes Seville the jump the
viniendo para acá va sevilla el salto el
The problem is that he didn't just say to give it to her
problema es que no solo dijo a darla
Man, a little chat falls, it's solved by me
hombre una charlita cae se soluciona yo
I think I should throw it away. I think that
creo que debería echar yo creo que
They should come and discuss it
deberían venir comentarlo
I don't know if I should write to you at the same time.
no sé si escribirle a la vez visitas en
long
largo
I think they should come and talk about it.
yo creo que deberían venir a hablarlo
because
por qué
let's see
a ver
but why does he come when he is
pero para que viene cuando esté
listening for him
escuchando por él
he is demanding things from me
me está demandando cosas
feeding the salt canals
dándole de comer a los canales de sal
CEOs and tortilla castles
ceos y castillos de tortilla la
and I think he didn't understand the headline and
y yo creo que no entendió titular y
should come
debería de venir
He should come because he didn't understand it
debería de venir porque no lo entendió
really
de verdad
to your magic Javi and I think they should
a tu magia javi y yo creo que deberían
come
venir
Now, the truth is, I don't have anything else.
ya esto la verdad no no tengo nada más
I consider that currently and if it comes
considero que actualmente y si viene
been a problematic person many times
sido una persona problemático muchas
times in my life I considered that
veces en mi vida consideró que
I'm not currently haha I am
actualmente no lo soy jaja estoy
trying to avoid anything that
tratando de evitar cualquier cosa que
may simply bring me a pain of
simplemente pueda traerme un dolor de
head a nuisance of mine and me
cabeza una molestia mía y a mi
tranquillity
tranquilidad
and there yes answer no answer some
y ahí sí contestar no contestar unos
messages and yes
mensajes y sí
and if not answer messages and this
y si no contestar mensajes y ésta
The Westin is no longer fashionable.
terminó ahorita de moda lo del westin es
being a terrible person then believe me
ser una terrible persona pues creerme
that I am terrible then with all the
que soy terrible entonces con todo el
world the truth is I do not treat anything banal well
mundo la verdad yo nada banal trate bien
treat him well and be a cordial person
tratarlo bien y ser una persona cordial
and I think he knows it and the times that
y creo que él lo sabe y las veces que
We have talked about this and although it has not been
hemos hablado esto y si bien no estado
I'm going to go but how beautiful to see ar and if
voy a ir pero qué guapa a ver ar y si
Well, he has been a person I think he is
bien ha sido una persona creo que está
from the slump that I think is under Juan lo
de bajón que creo está debajo juan lo
I tell them that he didn't answer or so they know
que les digo que no contestó o así saben
that yes, listen, if it's something important that
que sí oye si es algo importante que
never that it is really very necessary
nunca que que en verdad es muy necesario
I know I answer it but it is because
saber lo respondo pero es que por
example the last conversations will be
ejemplo las últimas conversaciones serán
about being of or if I am not wrong and
acerca de estar de o si no estoy mal y
other things for example today I was
otras cositas por ejemplo hoy estuve
watching our latest on WhatsApp
viendo en whatsapp nuestra última
conversation was when I donated to him
conversación fue cuando le doné para
for a video of mine that came out
para un que salió un vídeo mío el de
scaring star resulting I think that
asustando estrella resultando creo que
It was the last time we spoke if not
fue la última vez que hablamos si no
I'm sick and
estoy mal y
I think I have been cordial and well
pienso yo que he sido cordial y pues
nothing I think that what I tell them
nada yo pienso que lo que les digo la
It really seems to me that this is what he is doing
neta me parece que esto está haciendo
for a small thing or at least I do
por una pequeñez o por lo menos yo lo
I see it like this, sorry if I don't see it
veo así perdón si no le veo la
importance
importancia
Dallas, I repeat it to you once again, is not
dallas te lo repito una vez más no es
absolutely nothing against you
absolutamente nada contra ti
I know that this bad habit that now
yo sé que esta mala costumbre que ahora
I see that maybe it is a terrible one
veo que a lo mejor es una pésima
habit of not answering messages
costumbre de no contestar mensajes la
I have with a lot of people and it's because
tengo con muchísima gente y es porque
I just get distracted today and that's it
simplemente me distraigo hoy y ya está
to emphasize also that not spoken of
para recalcar también que no hablado de
the backs of no one ill spoken to
las espaldas de nadie mal no hablado con
absolutely no one's
absolutamente de nadie
It also seemed a little strange to me
también se me hizo un poquito raro
because right now they also put in
porque ahorita como que también metieron
Ah, but if they were Auron and Beijing, yes.
que ah pero si fueran auron y beijing si
I answered, "Well, they are my friends and
contestaba pues son mis amigos y
They are probably some of my closest friends
probablemente sean de mis amigos más
close now you know clearly I'm going to
cercanos ahorita sabes claramente le voy
to answer the people closest to you
a contestar a las personas más cercanas
that I have now and maybe not what he
que tengo ahora y tal vez no lo que él
He said it himself a thousand times over.
mismo lo dijo una y mil veces nosotros
We are not friends, we are people who
no somos amigos somos personas que nos
we get along well
llevamos bien
It's not for interest you know or interest to
no es por interés sabes o interés a
At this point and since 2020 I believe
estas alturas y desde el 2020 yo creo
that I don't need anyone and I could go on
que no necesito de nadie y podría seguir
having what I have right now without
teniendo lo que tengo ahorita sin
need to talk that they are not
necesidad de hablar que no son
absolutely no one interests that do not
absolutamente nadie intereses que no
I have is that I am not a piece of sending
tengo es que no soy un pedazo de enviar
of friends and believe me I know that this
de amigos y créanme yo sé que esto las
Good people don't have to be in
buenas personas no tienen que estar en
pretending that they are good people and yes
calcando que son buenas personas y si
Well I don't know if I'm a good person.
bien no sé si soy una buena persona no
I am a bad person and I only have clear
soy una mala persona y sólo tengo claro
You know
sabes
What I tell you I try to avoid
lo que les digo trato de evitar
any [ __ ] that might bother me
cualquier que me pueda molestar
and I inevitably get involved now for not
e inevitablemente me meto ahora por no
reply to a twitter message or something
contestar un mensaje de twitter o algo
So nothing on my part, everything is fine
así nada por mi parte todo todo bien
My admiration for him continues and continues
mi admiración hacia él sigue y continua
and
y
nothing, I have nothing more to say
nada no tengo nada más que decir la
It is true that it is such a small topic and
verdad es que es un tema tan pequeño y
so superficial that it is that I
tan y tan superficial que es que me
it seems a little bit
parece un poquito
It seems to me that it is something so simple I don't know
me parece que es algo tan simple no sé
It's that I see it like this and I think I'm the one
es que yo lo veo así y creo que soy el
only one who sees it that way you know
único que lo ve así sabes
the most controversial edge is I want
el de arista más polémico está quiero
play manga
jugar al manga
play whatever you want
juega lo que tú quieras
I don't have anything
no tengo nada
a [ __ ]
una
write
escribir
It is no secret that
que no es un secreto el hecho de que
Juan and I are terrible at following the
juan y yo somos pésimos para seguir el
thread of a conversation is not given to us
hilo de una conversación no se nos da yo
I swear to God that I don't
es que se los juro por dios no le
I answer my mom, I don't answer me
contesto a mi mamá no le contesto a mi
best friend younger than my best friend who
mejor amigo menor a mi mejor amiga que
He didn't answer anyone, that is, simply
no le contestó a nadie o sea simplemente
It's something that maybe I don't know
es algo que tal vez yo no lo sé
organize I can show you here
organizar les puedo mostrar aquí
openly
abiertamente
just covering a sum of money like
solo tapando una cifra de dinero como
You can see I think I have to get into
pueden ver creo que me tengo que meter a
a conversation to see will get me into
una conversación a ver me va a meter en
the thing about motorcycles
lo de las motos
Here I have
aquí tengo
conversations I haven't even had
conversaciones que ni siquiera he
open and can be from anyone
abierto y puede ser de cualquier persona
Here comes I can show you cloud that
aquí viene les puedo mostrar cloud que
She is my goddaughter, she hasn't even
es mi ahijada ni siquiera le ha
answered and so days go by we go to
contestado y así pasan días nos vamos a
literary download what we saw press
literario bajar lo que nos vimos prensa
and they go down like this, days pass here
y van bajando así pasan días que aquí se
You see that days are changing, days are ten days
ve que van cambiando días días diez días
and I don't answer and it's not the fact that
y yo no contesto y no es el hecho de
because he hates my daughter or because he doesn't
porque odia mi hija o porque no le
I want to answer my goddaughter because
quiera contestar a mi ahijada es porque
It just goes away, no no, I don't get it
simplemente se me va no no no se me da
I swear here are more examples, that is.
se los juro acá más ejemplos o sea
you can see whatever you want
pueden ver lo que ustedes quieran
with the context and I'm going to give you the
con el contexto y les voy a dar la
most important test
prueba más importante
the biggest project I have with
el proyecto más grande que tengo con
Juan, what matters most to me is what
juan que más me importa que es lo que
I need more and it is the construction of
más necesito y es la construcción de
our house
nuestra casa
and not even in that group did we answer
y ni siquiera en ese grupo contestamos
Here are the porous ones
aquí les van las porosas
So let's not even answer in
o sea que que ni siquiera contestemos en
something that we actually
algo que a nosotros en realidad nos
It matters a lot, it's like
importe mucho es como
Sunday 12 13 s 13 September
domingo 12 13 s 13 de septiembre
frantic
frenético
but literally these have been days that I
pero literal estos han sido días que me
They talk and here you can see the little balls that
hablan y aquí se ven las bolitas de que
changes from day to day also changes from day to day
cambia de día también de día cambia de
day and I don't answer I put it hello he sent me
día y no contesto lo pongo hola me mandó
a photo and left
una foto y dejó
mobile is something that is simply not
el móvil es algo que simplemente no se
gives us or gets into friends too that
nos da o se mete en amigos también que
nothing to do with it, they refer to two people
nada que ver se refieren a dos personas
that we love very much I have a message from
que queremos mucho tengo un mensaje de
that person of whom this was referred
esa persona de la cual se refirió esta
person who also has his/hers open
persona que tampoco tengo abierto su
message is not preference for anyone
mensaje no es preferencia por nadie
I just don't get it and many people
simplemente no se me da y mucha gente
He thinks I'm Juan's mom or I don't know.
piensa que yo soy mamá de juan o no sé
What's the matter, but he comes to me and complains
qué pedo pero a mí viene y se me queja
a thousand people of hey why don't I
mil personas de oye porque no me
Juan Gey answers because Juanes Juan and
contesta juan güey porque juanes juan y
I am me and what I do is not going to have
yo soy yo y lo que haga yo no va a tener
that to put Juan in and what Juan does not
que meter a juan y lo que haga juan no
It has to be up to me that we are
me tiene que meter a mí que estemos
Married doesn't mean we're the same
casados no significa que somos la misma
person
persona
same so and they know that he is a very good friend
mismo tan y que saben que es muy amigo
mine neither
mío tampoco
but I told him a little while ago
pero hace poquito yo se lo dije
Hey, it's just that he doesn't answer me and
oye es que es que no me contesta y
sending me proof that he has spoken to you
mandándome pruebas de que le ha hablado
by Juan day by day by day by day by day by
por juan dia por dia por dia por dia por
day and does not answer
dia y no le contesta
friend what do I tell you or is it
amigo que te digo o sea
It seems unreal to me and that will remind me
me parece irreal y eso me va a acordar
because I have a lot of affection for them but
las porque le tengo mucho cariño pero
It has to do with its people, its community
tiene que ver pero su gente su comunidad
you are literally not paying for messages in
literal no estás pagando mensajes en
twitter these days of why not
twitter estos días de por qué no le
you answer
contestas
my beautiful holy mother to whom I owe
mi madre santa hermosa a la que le debo
the life that gave birth to me and I am literally
la vida que me parió y literal estoy
here thanks to my parents
aquí gracias a mis papás
I didn't answer them, they don't complain to me because in
no les contestó no me reclaman porque en
12 year old youtube that I don't know you no
youtube de 12 años que no te conozco no
I have no [ __ ] idea who you are and you don't
tengo ni idea de quién eres y no te
I owe nothing, are you going to come to me and tell me?
debo nada vas a venir tú a mí a decirme
Who should I answer to and who should I not?
a quien le debo contestar y a quién no
we are crazy or rather we are fine
estamos locos o sea estamos bien de la
head really to get to the point where
cabeza en verdad de llegar al punto en
that you have to demand from me
el que ustedes tengan que exigirme a
Who should answer the messages?
quien tengo que responder los mensajes
that he didn't answer them to anyone, that is, no
que no se los respondió a nadie o sea no
I'm not going away in time, I have many things
no me voy el tiempo tengo muchas cosas
My head is very poorly organized, don't you know?
mi cabeza soy muy mal organizada no les
Cabrales answers about the science that is
contesta cabrales de la ciencia que es
my work that they have to be me
mi trabajo que me tienen que estar
sending messages every day from Ari
mandando mensaje todos los días de ari
You are missing this, I am not answering
te falta esto no contesto
dm
dm
literal
literal
from whatsapp my whatsapp status is
desde whatsapp mi estado de whatsapp es
Do not listen to audios without anything else if
no escuchar audios sin nada más si
If I had heard Dallas, I would have said okay.
hubiera escuchado a dallas diría ok
Maybe I'm exaggerating, but when I hear the
quizás exagero pero al escuchar las
arz's excuses make the ball there is the box
excusas de aríz haz la bola está la caja
is to like the classic because
es que a gustarse con el clásico porque
It's not me, I'm like this and it's too much
no soy yo soy así y es demasiado
immature
inmaduro
Thank you very much from October
muchas gracias de octubre
October 16th when he replied to me
16 de octubre cuando me respondió
I didn't tell anyone, not even
yo no se lo dije a nadie ni siquiera a
My husband himself asked him for it
mi mismo esposo se lo pregunté para
I found out about two days later
saberlo yo a unos dos días después
I was watching Juan's live show and
estaba viendo el directo de juan y
I heard that they donated to him and
escuché que le que le donaron y le
They said hey why did he unfollow you
dijeron oye por qué te dejó de seguir
dallas and his response was not even me
dallas y su respuesta fue ni siquiera me
I had realized I didn't know according to me no
había dado cuenta no sabía según yo no
we are bad like 23 days after
estamos mal como 23 días después de que
I spoke to him and I didn't tell him or her.
yo le hablaba las no se lo conté ni a
Juan
juan
someone else
alguien más
I'm ashamed of her and I feel very sorry for her but
a gonza de ella y me da mucha pena pero
I think it's a shame that the little girl, like
creo mucha pena que la chiquilla como
our mama so much husband telling me
nuestro mama tanto marido diciéndome
or lar and I'm just writing to you to ask you
o lar y sólo te escribo para pedirte
excuse my opinion based on what
disculpas mi opinión la base en lo que
I believed and in some videos that well
yo creía y en algunos vídeos que bien
YouTube we were already
youtube ya estábamos
that he hasn't told Ghosn about it
que no se lo haya contado a ghosn a vela
I believe it and I've been saying it all the time.
me lo creo y lo llevo diciendo toda la
late but that has not only told his
tarde pero que no sólo haya contado a su
I don't believe my husband will take it out for three days.
marido no me lo creo sacar los tres días
I listen to her husband
escucho a su marido
there under wash already there has gone one
ahí debajo lavar ya haya se ha ido un
we have little
poco tenemos
She can say whatever she wants.
ella puede decir lo que quiera se lo
whether or not he has said it and in
haya dicho o no se lo haya dicho y en
This time I didn't tell him because
esta ocasión no se lo dije porque
literally the only messages we have
literal los únicos mensajes que tenemos
hello I was seeing your tweet email and
es hola estaba viendo tu tweet email y
I found you and saw that you were following me just to
te encontré y vi que me seguía solo para
tell you that she is super beautiful and she
decirte que está súper hermosa y ella me
He responded very nicely, I put it after
respondió muy bonito le puse después
like a month later a lie like
como un mes después una mentira como
Ten days later, hello beautiful, how
diez días después hola preciosa cómo
You are here today, I would like to know if you want
estás hoy me gustaría saber si quieres
be part of the PRI to explain yourself in
ser parte del pri para explicarte en
In short, big pays where it counts
resumidas cuentas lo grande paga donde
people want to have more interaction
la gente quiere tener más interacción
with you they can pay the price this is
contigo pueden pagar el precio esto es
what I have said I have been with him
lo que he dicho yo he estado con el
student, what do you have to do to me?
estudiante hay de me tienes que hacer
a thumbnail to upload separately
una miniatura para subir separado la
reaction to Juana and the reaction to
reacción a lo de juana y la reacción a
I'll leave it
lo dejaré
that at the moment he was not interested
que de momento no le interesaba
and there he died and never again to rise and
y ahí murió y ya nunca más al subir y
talking to her I think we bumped into each other and
hablar con ella creo que nos topamos y
I'm not bad and I'm not a [ __ ]
no estoy mal y no una mongas
and that's what
y es lo que
knows the
sabe la
that one day you have a boss outside of networks
que un día tienes un jefe fuera de redes
and you excuse yourself with idle jazz
y te excusas con ocioso jazz al
not to tell anyone but
no contar a nadie pero a
people don't understand
la gente no se entera
I am very closed with my things, I am not going to
soy muy cerrada con mis cosas no voy a
walk around talking to someone who
andar viendo a platicarle a alguien que
someone took my phallus
alguien me quito un falo
I don't give a damn about both poles and the
me vale tanto madre los dos polos y los
two poles
dos polos
and I haven't even stopped following
y yo ni siquiera he dejado de seguir a
a person who came to our house and
una persona que vino a nuestra casa y
A week later he talked [ __ ] about
una semana después habló a de
us live
nosotros en directo
Let's look at the follow and I don't give a damn
miremos el follow y me vale madre
and he won't leave me
y no me va a dejar
sleep nor am I going to sleep badly
dormir ni no voy a dormir mal
but alone and he is in all his right
pero solo y él está en todo su derecho
you are right
tiene razón
We don't answer and you are quite right and
no contestamos y tiene mucha razón y le
I give everything in the reason if it was ours
doy todo todo en la razón si fue nuestra
count because we don't know no
cuenta porque nosotros no sabemos no
We simply answer that we are not given and
contestamos simplemente no se nos da y
also another thing the truth if not to me
también otra cosa la verdad si a mí no
I was interested in being God and I am
me interesó lo de estar dios y yo soy
very embarrassing to say things
muy penosa para decir las cosas
Hey, I'm not interested at the moment.
oye que no me interesa de momento
I prefer not to answer because also the
prefiero no contestar porque también el
silence is an answer for me made
silencio es una respuesta para mí hizo
an answer for not having answered
una respuesta el no haber contestado
These messages about being Osh, why not?
estos mensajes de estar de osh porque no
I was interested because in those months I
me interesaba porque en esos meses yo
There were those who follow me very closely
estaba los que me siguen bien de cerca
had a campaign with real Instagram
tenía campaña con real de instagram
I'm getting real and there are ITVs later
estoy recibiendo reales y hay itvs luego
I had a campaign with YouTube Shorts
tuve campaña con youtube shorts
videos for youtube charts and then
vídeos para youtube charts y luego
This campaign that is going up has ended
terminó esta campaña que va subiendo
videos to facebook yes it is true
vídeos a facebook sí que es verdad lo
what does it say when someone is not with you
que dice cuando alguien no te está
By answering you have to assume
contestando tú tienes que dar por hecho
that the answer is no but man the
que la respuesta no pero hombre la
It is true that due to education it is better to tense and
verdad que por educación mejor tensa y
parade and say the thing must be
desfila y decirlo la cosa hay que
say it clearly, uncle
decirla clara tío
He gave the silent treatment if he stops him
dio la callada por respuesta si le para
things are better if the key but
las cosas es mejores si la clave pero
That's not true either because it's very serious
que tampoco porque está súper grave
without any project and I think even I
sin ningún proyecto y creo que hasta yo
I wrote to him that father project
misma se le escribí que padre proyecto
I'm going to check it out and I didn't tell him anything.
lo voy a revisar y ya no le dije nada
because for me silence is a
porque para mí el silencio es una
people put me in response on twitter who
respuesta me ponen en twitter gente que
Bern, I don't know what she thinks she is.
berna no sé que se cree
careful it was hard for you to say no if that
cuidado te costaba decir que no si ese
It's your way of saying that you're not perfect.
es tu forma de decir que no perfecto te
I respect her now you respect mine
la respeto ahora tú respeta la mía
because that's my way of saying no
porque así es mi forma de decir que no
do not respond
no responder
sometimes the way people have to
a veces la forma la gente tiene que
come to me to tell me what so I don't know
venir a mí a decirme qué así que no sé
They are not my parents, I swear to you.
no son mis papás o sea se los juro por
God, not even my parents send me
dios que ni siquiera mis papás me mandan
to the things I do or don't do, that is, me
a las cosas que hago o no hago o sea yo
I love you very much
quiero mucho
because here it is not a you leave me alone
porque aquí no es un tú me dejas de
follow me I stop following you another one doesn't
seguir yo te dejo de seguir otro no le
I see the importance, that is, I say it
veo la importancia o sea yo lo digo
because he is a person who has affection
porque es una persona que tenga cariño
I knew that I took off the floor days ago and
supe que me quito el suelo hace días y
yesterday or the day before yesterday he agrees he agrees
ayer o antier está de acuerdo está
watching a video of the ISI with the low
viendo un vídeo del isi con el baja
and I'm not tired and it doesn't bother me and
y no estoy cansada y no me molesta y
He says that he said that he was not going to
dice que él dijo ya que él no iba a
say nothing of this, maybe we
decir nada de esto igual nosotros
not even Juan knew it or even
ni siquiera juan lo sabía ni siquiera
Juan knew the answer he gave me
juan sabía la respuesta que me dio él
but because someone had an opinion
pero porque alguien opinó
because someone else had an opinion on things
porque alguien más opinó por las cosas
who watch channels from the CEO and that's why
que ven canales desde el ceo y por eso
He hinted at something and they already threw me the
dio a entender algo ya me echaron la
It's my fault they already scolded me
culpa a mí ya me echaron la bronca a mí
and now I'm sick and now that everyone
y ahora estoy mal yo y ahora que todo el
world finds out about dogs
mundo se entere de los perros
I mean
o sea
and I didn't tell anyone and that's it
y no se lo dije a nadie y eso se
I swear to God
lo juro por dios santo
but I fall like lightning and get broken
sino que me caigo en rayo y me parten
two
dos
with whom to talk about these
con quien estar platicando de estas
meta things I don't talk about my things
cosas meta no platico de mis cosas
personal - I'll be chatting
personales - voy a estar platicando
Javi professionals are not days, they are eggs
profesionales javi no es días son huevos
and pleasant but their professionalism is there
y agradables pero su profesionalidad ahí
is diminished by its immaturity and were
se ve mermada por su inmadurez y fueran
more organized like the flour itself
más organizados como la misma harina
Imagine where they unload bad things
imagina donde descargan cosas que malo
higher up that bothers me the most so that
más arriba que más me molesta para que
They call me bad people when I don't
me pongan de malas personas de cuando no
from the point of view the proposal for rooms is a
de vista la propuesta de salas es una
greater exposure is very nice to answer
mayor exposición es muy lindo responder
messages in truth or that is
mensajes en verdad o sea
we are as we are in the world
estamos como estamos meta en el mundo
He's so stupid because they give him more
está tan ojete porque le dan más
importance of a love rita of 23 years
importancia que un amor rita de 23 años
did not respond to messages that we
no respondió mensajes que nos
survivor who is stealing from us
superviviente que nos está robando un
I have a lot of money
chingo dinero que tengo
to pirate is killing dude that 70
para piratear esté matando wey que el 70
looking
mirando
That is why he is calling in crucifying
o sea por eso llamando en crucificando
That's why they call me a [ __ ] and a fool.
ya por eso me tratan de y pendeja
on Twitter
en twitter
screwed
jodidos
to dinner and the [ __ ] didn't enjoy it at all
a cenar y no se disfrutó nada la
dinner because my twitter was spam llad
cena porque mi twitter estaba spam lladó
black and the bad people are not to be
negro y el que mala gente es que no sea
you are really going to have dinner with your partner and
realmente tú vas a cenar con tu pareja y
you are affected by what is being put into
te afecta lo que esté poniendo en
Twitter
twitter
you are not affected by whatsapp that does not affect them
no te afectan los whatsapp que no los
look and it will affect you tweeting and the
mira y te va a afectar twittear y la
The house is exaggerated, I don't think so.
casa es exagerada tampoco a ver yo creo
What's a nonsense is that he doesn't pay either
que es una chorrada es que tampoco paga
a fart when
un pedo cuándo
When this happened, of those 4 there remains the
cuando pasó esto de esos 4 queda la
raised his opinion
subió su opinión
and Roberto got angry with Juan because he
y roberto se enojaron con juan porque le
They said that the umma is burning because it
dijeron le quema la umma que porque le
I had asked Dallas that there was an extra video
había pedido dallas que sobra un vídeo
Juan didn't ask for anything, that's exactly what he asked for.
juan no pidió nada es exactamente lo
There are also the Traversi Travers tribe
mismo están la tribu traversi travers
fixing I don't know how to say things and
fijando no sé cómo se dice las cosas y
distorting simply because the
tergiversando simplemente porque la
people think it's not that things are
gente piensa no es que las cosas sean
And that doesn't make me a bad person.
así y a mí no me hace mala persona
I do very good things and I can swear to you
hago cosas muy buenas y puedo jurarles
that I am an excellent person for things that
que soy excelente persona por cosas que
I do that it is really worth it that in
hago que en verdad vale la pena que en
I really help people.
verdad ayudo a la gente de verdad me
I take the time to be attentive
tomo el tiempo de ser atenta
and now I'm a bad person simply because
y ahora soy mala persona simplemente por
not knowing how to answer messages for real
no saber contestar mensajes en verdad
I mean
ósea
Friends, this is ridiculous and not even
amigos es que esto es ridículo y ni
This doesn't even seem ridiculous to me.
siquiera me parece ridículo esto me
It seems ridiculous that Gonzalez had
parece ridículo que gonzález haya tenido
to apologize to me for something that
que pedir disculpas a mí por algo que
He said that is, for literal freedom of
dijo o sea por literal libertad de
expression now embitters the new of
expresión ahora se amargue lo nuevo de
KFC tastes great, man, I think.
kfc sabe padrísimo hombre ave yo creo
that they are doing a lot
que están haciendo mucho
It's that in the end this is a nonsense.
es que al final una chorrada ya esto se
would have simply solved
hubiera solucionado simplemente
telling him to give it to me, I'm not interested in it
diciéndole de darla no me interesa la
true to see a lot of luck but I don't
verdad de verse mucha suerte pero no me
I'm interested right now, everyone has
interesa yo ahora mismo cada uno tiene
that managing your business and your work does not
que gestionar su negocio y su trabajo no
mix it with friends and without
mezclarlo con las amistades y sin
commitment dallas does not interest me
compromiso dallas no me interesa de
I'm really glad you're doing one
verdad me alegro que hagas una
platform seems to me a very project
plataforma me parece un proyecto muy
cool but I'm not interested in the guy
chido pero no me interesa el chico en
other things and that does not interest me for
otras cosas y eso no me interesa para
know what would have happened and there I know
saber qué hubiera pasado y ahí sé
tell him hey excuse me it wasn't my
decirle oye discúlpame no era mi
I intend to offend you but friends who
intención ofender te pero amigos que me
blame me for setting it aside is that I
echen en cara que lo aparte es que me
It seems surreal that it's like when
parece surrealista que es como cuando
Little children learn to say
los niños chiquitos aprenden a decir
Mom and Dad, nobody in their [ __ ] life knew
mamá y papá nadie en la vida sabía
that was literally a thing if you
que era goes thing literal si les
I ask, is there the day before yesterday that is casting, right?
pregunto hay antier que es casting no
you have no [ __ ] idea but as already
tienes ni idea pero como ya
you hear someone say it and everyone
escuchas a alguien que lo dice y todos
They are like [ __ ] parakeets that for me
son como pinches periquitos que para mí
the ghost in
el ghost in
For me the casting was someone who
para mí el casting era alguien que te
They totally ignore you, saying it doesn't matter to you
ningunean totalmente en plan no te hace
in no case does he belittle you at all, completely no
caso en nada te ningunea por total no
I don't think he'll answer messages but
teme no creo que responda mensajes sino
that doesn't answer you live acts like
que no te contesta en directos hace como
if it did not exist
si no existiera
because right now I'm not ready to be
porque ahorita no estoy para estar
putting up with nonsense
aguantando tonterías
I have shown you all this week that
se los he mostrado toda esta semana que
I'm going to [ __ ] like that, not even close
me está yendo de la que ni tal no
I feel really good, I'm feeling really good.
me siento bien neta estoy con una bomba
of time in my head because in
de tiempo en mi cabeza porque en
any moment I get sick I am
cualquier momento me pongo mal estoy
I have terribly poor net health.
terriblemente de salud neta no tengo
I'm in no mood, I've been great
ánimos de nada he estado súper
I have been crushed well to whom
apachurrada he estado bien a quienes
They are playing and a minute later they have me
traen jugando y un minuto después me han
I'm seen crying because I'm screwed
visto llorando porque me estoy jodiendo
literally with the [ __ ] hormones and the day
literal con las hormonas y el día
from yesterday reading so many kids
de ayer leyendo tanto chamaco
insulting me just for not knowing
insultándome solamente por no saber
answering messages made me feel worse
contestar mensajes me puso de la peor
way in the world
manera en el mundo
I've never had an attack of
jamás me había dado un ataque de
anxiety like the day we went out in
ansiedad como el día de ella salimos en
the restaurant was talking to
el restaurante estaba hablando con
commands and we were talking about what
comandos y estábamos platicando qué
tortilla things that the people how are you
cosas de tortilla que el pueblo qué tal
What if it also stops everything thrown away?
qué tal que también para todo tirado
Twitter couldn't say any [ __ ] thing
twitter no podía decir ninguna
word in the restaurant about how bad it was
palabra en el restaurante de lo mal que
I felt and we go with Mancho Juanillo
me sentía y vamos con mancho juanillo
We have a party, son, they tell me, do you want to?
tenemos una fiesta hijo me dicen quieres
that we are going to leave with stain and we
que vayamos a dejar a con mancha y nos
we carry out at home because I have very
realizamos a la casa porque tengo muy
badly was shaking brought the
mal estaba temblando traía la
heating brings the heating
calefacción de la trae la calefacción
from the car to 28 because I was
del coche a 28 porque me estaba
rotting from the cold, he couldn't stop shivering
pudriendo de frío no dejaba de temblar
how bad I felt because friends didn't
de lo mal que me sentía porque amigos no
I am a bad person
soy mala persona
a person because my net mistake I don't know
una persona porque mi error neta no sé
answering messages seems to me
contestar mensajes me parece
No kidding, I mean, yesterday I wanted to throw up.
no neta o sea ayer me quería vomitar
yesterday I felt bad I can't stop
ayer me sentía mal no puede dejar de
I saw my parents tremble at night in the
temblar vi a mis papás en la noche en la
same party because they were going to leave me
misma fiesta porque fueron a dejar a mi
sister and my parents had to
hermana y mis papás me tuvieron que
hugging outside the party because
abrazar haga fuera de la fiesta porque
I couldn't do it anymore after an hour, that's true
ya no podía después de una hora que neta
I didn't know how long this was going to last.
no sabía cuánto me iba a durar esta
[ __ ] that I felt so bad dick
que me sentía tan mal se
I swear to God I thought I was leaving
los juro por dios que pensaba que me iba
to die from the games I thought I was playing
a morir de los juegos que pensaba que me
I was going to die because I felt that I was not
iba a morir porque sentía que no
was breathing and was
respiraba y estaba
with everything ready to brown this and
con todo listo cuanto a dorar esto y
until I started talking to Danny
hasta que empecé a hablar con con danny
and other girls who were there in the
y otras chicas que estaban ahí en la
party and they tried to calm me down
fiesta y me intentaron tranquilizar a
breathe and it went down until
respirar y se me fue bajando hasta que
She got off me completely when I saw
ella se me bajó por completo cuando vi a
I love red too much, I'm not a bad person
ama demasiado rojo no soy mala persona
trying to answer messages doesn't work for me
intentando contestar mensajes no me hace
This but Dallas has not put it either
esto pero dallas tampoco la ha puesto de
bad person don't be the one who says that
mala persona no sea la dice que la
It seemed ugly that they had done something ugly to him
pareció feo que le han hecho un feo a él
and that's it, but man, bad person, not her
y ya está pero hombre mala persona no la
has not put the bad person either
ha puesto a la de mala persona tampoco
no if that is my mistake and I have always been
no si ese es mi error y yo siempre lo he
said that he has problems
dicho a que tiene problemas
hormones and it's normal for it to be like that ah
hormonas y es normal que sea así ah
Of course I don't know how to count, I'm very good at it
claro está no sé contar se me dan muy
ill-gotten in the fun, yes man
mal ganado en el cachondeo sí hombre
Of course, if they have hormones and such
claro si tienen con las hormonas y tal
It is normal that you are taking things
es normal que los está tomando las cosas
out of being and
fuera de estar y
be the darling of Dallas
ser ojito dallas
Johnny is bad, I have no courage despite
johnny está mal tengo ni coraje a pesar
that its people because Mexico caused
de que su gente porque méxico ocasionado
It's yesterday
es ayer
We say we get into this and sometimes it can
decimos meternos en esto y a veces puede
Being very good can sometimes be a
ser muy buena a veces puede ser una
[ __ ] and yesterday was [ __ ]
y ayer fue una
affected
afectada
but I have nothing more to say
pero que no tengo más que hablar
You should come and see if you know them better.
debería venir a ver si los conoce más
anxiety which has its problems
ansiedad el cual tiene sus problemas
hormonal are the worst
hormonales son lo peor
need
necesite
Dallas saw a
dallas vi un
clip that I'm going to play for you
clip que se las voy a reproducir para
put them in context
ponerlos en contexto
the complaint or not because they are sent
la denuncia o no porque se mandan
finishing the peeling of the hooves
acabando la pela de los cascos
and the USB doesn't help that's why it was playing
y el usb no ayuda por eso juega estaba
so affected because he saw Arias yes yes yes
tan afectado porque vio a arias sí sí sí
it is likely
es probable
I'm not trying hard now though.
no estoy intentando fuertemente ahora sí
already
ya
One last thing and the topic will appear
una última cosa y aparecerá el tema
is that another production list of my health
es que otra producción lista de salud mi
drink but I feel that everything that is
beba pero siento que todo lo que están
saying it was very bad last night when I saw the
diciendo está muy mal anoche al ver la
Dallas's little face telling everything hurt me
carita de dallas contando todo me dolió
the good choir and if you had seen mine
el coro bueno y si hubieras visto la mía
would have broken your heart too
también te hubiera roto el corazón
honey things very I'm looking for a
cariño cosas muy estoy buscando una
conversation with text
conversación con texto
to see it together
para verlo juntos
the game is also talking about the topic
el juego está hablando también del tema
urban finished already
urbana terminado ya
The lava already changed the razor the other time
la lava ya cambio la otra vez la navaja
I like going out
saliendo me gusta
but it is clear it gets worse not only leave
pero es claro se pone peor no sólo deje
one day juansa with the real one
un día juansa con la verdadera
they decided that he was having
decidieron a que le estaba teniendo
character of the day to the rival by the way ari
carácter del día al rival por cierto ari
hate with all your soul and write to me
odia con toda su alma vale y me escribo
to thank me after doing
para darme las gracias después de hacer
the video about why the disgust
el vídeo sobre el de por qué el asco
would this guy be worth not only not only that
haría este tipo vale no sólo no sólo eso
not only agreed but also having
de acuerdo sino que además de haberle
warned several times I also defended him
avisado varias veces también lo defendí
with the thing about Colombia
con lo de colombia
my mistake according to this
mi error según este
depending on why it didn't go beyond 9 princess
según porque no pasó del 9 princesa
when you have an anxiety attack like this
cuando tengas un ataque de ansiedad así
put an ice pack on your chest near
ponte un pack de hielo en el pecho cerca
From the heart, thank you very much, right?
del corazón muchas gracias derecha no
it was forgotten a lot to know anxiety
era se olvidó mucho saber la ansiedad
widespread and that trick always
generalizada y ese truco siempre me
relax
relaja
He said that my mistake
dijo que mi error
which was not true, so let's see what it is
cosa que no fue verdad pues a ver se lo
I said I do in Seville when in my
he dicho hago en sevilla cuando en mi
[ __ ] life talked to her
vida hablado con ella
something I didn't have to say according to
algo que no tenía que decir según
his thing is
lo de él es
when he forgot those four I did
cuando se olvidó de esos cuatro yo sí le
I spoke
hablé
I'm going to show you the messages
les voy a enseñar los mensajes
in the background
de fondo
and so I spoke to him
y así le hable
and this was the message
y esto fue el mensaje
Hello friend, how are you? I just wanted to
hola amigo cómo estás solo quería
Thank you for giving your point of view
agradecerte por dar tu punto de vista
which by the way and very accurate thanks
que por cierto y muy acertado gracias
to get more people to open their
para hacer que más personas abran los
eyes a hug to you about and alix and with
ojos un abrazo a ti sobre y alix y con
brilliant you are a person who transmits
brillante eres una persona que transmite
I don't know where something is that I told him that
no sé dónde es algo que yo le dije que
I hated proving anything, I don't know now
odiaba el de demostrar nada no sé ahora
He pulled me out and I felt disgusted by his finger
me sacó y me daba asco el dedo
I thanked him because at that moment
yo le agradecí porque en ese momento
They travel very badly when what happened to them happened
viajan muy mal cuando pasó lo de sus
four very very bad and he helped that
cuatro muy muy mal y él ayudó a que
many people if they saw that when you
mucha gente si viera que cuando t
And these people get their ads.
y yo esta gente le salen los anuncios
automatically like this
automáticamente como esto
I try to put it to you guys.
yo lo intenta poner a ustedes salen
also the ads automatically
también los anuncios así automáticamente
is showing conversations with Dallas
está mostrando conversaciones con dallas
is skating
está patinando
and we are going to do a lot that I don't like
y vamos a hacer mucho a mí no me gusta
that the conversations be taken out
que se saquen las conversaciones
private neither on one side nor on the other
privadas ni por un lado ni por el otro
But Dallas just told things yesterday.
pero dallas acaba de contar cosas ayer
in his live performance
en su directo
dallas has literally read the entire
dallas ha leído literalmente toda la
private conversation with her and has
conversación en privado con ella y ha
Having said that he hates the test, I only
dicho lo de que odia al test solo me
It seemed good they are taking out the
pareció bien ellos están sacando las
motherly things for one
cosas de madre por una
something that is not so important
cosa que no tiene tanta importancia
when I reach the point of crying
cuando llegue llorando al extremo cuando
I was driving
estaba manejando
I told him that he had spoken badly of
yo le dije a de que había hablado mal de
He who was obviously angry
él que obviamente por estar enfadada
I said things and he told me not to worry
dije cosas y él me dijo no te preocupes
I too, I too spoke ill of
yo también yo también hablé mal de
you because I was angry
ustedes porque estaba enojado
today
hoy
excuse us, hey, excuse me, you excuse me
disculpa nos oye discúlpame tú a mí
It is also worth it then give it to the client
también vale entonces dale al cliente
with the fact that he hates the destiny that he
con lo de que odia el destino que el
Santera honor on the other hand no
honor santera por otro lado no
in case it had been true and I
en caso que hubiera sido cierto y yo le
I would have said, hey, if you disgust me, this
hubiera dicho oye si me das asco esta
person died of this person
persona falleció de esta persona
because it would have been wrong to do something that was not
porque hubiera estado mal cosa que no
It was true that I had told Gonza
fue cierta que yo le había dicho a gonza
that you stopped following us because of ghosting
que nos dejaste de seguir por ghosting
but because it is then if there were
pero porque es entonces si hubiera
It was good that you said these
estado bien que tú dijeras estas
such strong words of hate and that
palabras tan fuertes de que odio y que
The coach disgusts me to the extreme
me da asco el dt en extremo
Although he told you privately about Italy
aunque te ha dicho por privados italia
It's just that it seems to me
es que es que me parece
uneven is what it seems to me
desnivelado es que es que me parece
uneven or my mistake depending on why
desnivelado o sea mi error según porque
It didn't happen after telling Gonzalez
no paso fue haberle contado a gonzález
since he stopped following us to ask him
ya que nos dejó de seguir para hacerle
ghosting but it was good that there was
ghosting pero sí estuvo bien que hubiera
the ventilated things that maybe I
el ventilado las cosas que tal vez yo
I could have told him what I hated about not
pueda haberle dicho de que odiaba de no
you gave me something that was not easy because 'the
me dabas cosa que no fácil porque 'la
essence' the message and I spoke it to
esencia' el mensaje y lo hablé para
thank you for what you uploaded but I didn't say
agradecerle lo que subió pero no dije
That's right, churra twitch puts more and more
eso sí churra twitch cada vez más pone
increasingly frequent ads and
anuncios cada vez más seguidos y
automatic if you are not a subscriber of the channel
automáticos si no eres subs del canal
education because it was a little help
educación por ser la que iba una ayudita
put the messages children because not
les poner los mensajes niños porque no
let's read other people's
vamos a leer los de los demás personas
is making me have the worst day of my life
me está haciendo tener el peor día de mi
life
vida
and that was before we spoke
y eso fue antes de que habláramos
us
nosotros
something like I'm already with democracy
algo como ya estoy con la democracia
if the street when we were talking
si la calle cuando estábamos hablando
that I was honest but I told you that from there
que fui honesta pero te dije que de ahí
when we spoke it was no longer happening, I put on
cuando hablamos ya no pasaba me puse
Damn, I'm in the worst moment I've ever had.
estoy en el peor momento traigo
so much anxiety that I had to erase
mucha ansiedad cual me tuvo que borrar
twitter because I got really bad I'm doing very
twitter porque me puse bien mal ando muy
bad with the hormones if I catch
mal con lo de las hormonas si me agarro
At the worst moment I am a party well done
en el peor momento soy una fiesta bien a
[ __ ] with a lot of desire to cry
huevada con muchas ganas de llorar
because I feel a lot of pressure and more because
porque siento mucha presión y más porque
Wayne, we never did wrong, Juanillo.
wayne neta no hicimos mal juanillo nunca
We answer to no one whoever you are and no
contestamos a nadie seas quien seas y no
It seems to me that they are against me for
me parece que se pongan en mi contra por
that and then I sent him a photo and I put it
eso y luego le mandé una foto y le puse
I had to bring him a bag hook
tuve que traerle un gancho de bolsa de
potatoes to calm me down because literally everything
papas para calmarme porque literal toda
the [ __ ] party was like this
la fiesta estuve así
and command
y comando
because I felt like [ __ ]
porque me sentía de la
He sent me a very nice audio telling me
me mandó un audio muy bonito diciéndome
that the best cure was to ignore people
que la mejor cura era ignorar a la gente
and I thanked him and said that I loved him very much
y le agradecí dije que le quería mucho
clear to him he can't see Dallas
claro al de él de no puede ver a dallas
and in fact she will have come from a [ __ ]
y al de hecho la habrá venido de
mother cup and
madre copa e
incite or push them not to
incitarlos o empujarlos a que no se
talk more with dallas
hable más con dallas
the test will have put in a bit of persimmon
el test habrá metido un poco de caqui
I also tell you this
está también os digo
will have taken advantage of the topic here
habrá aprovechado aquí para el tema
everyone can take things as they please
cada quien puede tomar las cosas como
wants and for whom he has his duels
quiera y para quien tiene sus duelos
everyone feels as they can
cada quien se siente como se puede
feel clear clear why
sentir claro claro por qué
and maybe I don't give it importance or to me
y tal vez yo no le doy importancia oa mí
I don't mind the fact that someone
no me cuesta el hecho de que alguien me
I let you answer because I am like that but
deje contestar porque yo soy así pero
maybe to dallas and it affects him a lot
tal vez a dallas y le afecta mucho el
that we will not answer you and that is why I
que no le contestaremos y por eso me
I apologize because my intention and that of
disculpo porque mi intención y la de
Juan never wanted to make them feel bad.
juan jamás fue hacerles sentir mal
and that or continue to be taken away from us
y eso o seguir que nos haya quitado el
Folio is not going to change things, it's not going to
folio no va a cambiar las cosas no va a
take away that we are grateful to him
quitar que estamos agradecidos con él
Many people yesterday telling me why you
mucha gente ayer diciéndome porque te
sorry because you don't apologize to him
disculpas porque no te disculpas con el
why do you apologize on twitter and between
por qué te disculpas en twitter y entre
nothing more because sorry because you don't know
nada más porque perdón porque no sabe
answering messages I didn't apologize to him
contestar mensajes no me disculpé con él
there is healthy on twitter he is he is
hay en twitter saludable a él es él es
privately a week ago
en privado hace una semana antes
let's really learn to give it importance
en verdad aprendamos a darle importancia
guys to the things you should put in when
chicos a las cosas que deben meta cuando
they want to cancel and in one or when not
quieren cancelar y en unl o cuando no
have a good reason when this is
tengan un motivo bien cuando ésta esté
screwing someone when they're not there
jodiendo a alguien cuando no está
doing something horrible for the world
haciendo algo para el mundo horrible
sangonera that you stealing from you 16 no
sangonera que ustedes robando a ti 16 no
to a person who metal us
a una persona que metal nosotros
answer messages for real
contestar mensajes en verdad
dallas no
dallas no
thanks to the
gracias a la
great beautiful gonza because
grandísima gonza bella porque
It is probably also falling
seguramente es que también está cayendo
[ __ ] and what horror what horror that we
y qué horror qué horror que nos
[ __ ] falls
caiga
efe
efe
I dropped the live stream, it's not going to happen for sure.
se me cayó el directo seguro no se va a
fall directly no
caer directo no
I'm going to fall, director, it wasn't anymore, it was already
se me va a caer director ya no ya era ya
we were here too long
estaba estábamos demasiado tiempo aquí
without a host
sin una
the person responsible for two awaiting arrest
la responsable dos a vela por detención
of the flame another but because it may
de la de la llama otra pero porque podrá
the girl will be able to say what she has
podrá opinar la muchacha lo que ha
past
pasado
How disgusting my house is
qué asco de mi casa
It's going to fall straight for sure, look, I don't know.
se va a caer directo seguro mira no se
it fell on her
la cayó a ella
he dropped it on her
se la cayó a ella
Juan, we need to know something.
juan necesitamos saber algo
by leaving minecraft as important as
al dejar minecraft tan importante como
my name
mi nombre
the way calls the most current way
la vía llama la vía más actual
the beautiful one
la bella
Well, I can call her if she lives in Mexico.
bueno la puedo llamar si vive en méxico
I don't have it on the phone, call me
por teléfono no la tengo llama por
WhatsApp
whatsapp
[Music]
[Música]
ah already comes back to comes back to comes back
ah ya vuelve a vuelve la vuelve
would not be worried arica
no sería preocupado arica
I had no worries
no tenía preocupado
is not heard now
no se escucha ahora
cannot be heard
no se escucha
or is it me
o soy yo
it is not heard no
no se escucha no
let's listen, listen, it's not me
vamos a escuchar se escucha no soy yo
It's not that
no es que
don't call her that you like her
no la llame que te guste
restart I can't imagine what it's going to do
reinicia no me imagino que va a
restart no
reiniciar no
now now it's coming
ahora ahora ya viene
but we can't stay like this all afternoon
pero no podemos estar toda la tarde así
We've been here for almost four hours now
llevamos casi cuatro horas en el momento
to finish and I'm going to take out
de terminar y ya me voy a sacar
He already made me 15 ar and if you see that your direct
ya me hizo 15 ar y si ves que tu directo
you're not going well, come here
no te vas bien vente para acá
ar and if you see that your live is not going well
ar y si ves que no te va bien tu directo
through the internet or whatever 20 to here
por el internet o lo que sea 20 para acá
don't get worried
no te rayes
I did have to have a bad mindset here
yo sí tuve que tema mal mente para acá
they no longer saw that
ya no vieron que
is that here they come out directly
es que aquí salen directo
now now
ahora ahora
literally the greatest test
literal la mayor prueba
He is a very cute boy who warns me of
es un chico muy lindo que me avisa de
everything in general but goatherd and
todo sea en general pero cabrero y
entering into little things when they talk about me
entrando de cositas cuando hablan de mí
That's how the guy sends links and he's gay.
así cabrón manda links y es un gay
So he is super good, he is a sweetheart.
entonces él es súper bueno es un amor yo
I love it, cameo fits or not, send a video
lo amo cameo cabe o no manda un vídeo
What Gonzalez says, I have an opinion about him.
que dice gonzález yo opino sobre él un
dallas phallus
falo de dallas
I call her boss gossip, I called her
me pone patrona chisme a ella le puse a
see in short is because
ver en resumidas cuentas es porque
You did not answer them when they
ustedes no le contestaron cuando los
invited his project to his platform
invitó a su proyecto de su plataforma
reflected now but I say it
reflexionado ahora pero yo lo dice
defending Dallas or us because
defendiendo a dallas o a nosotros porque
I had no [ __ ] idea
yo no tenía idea
where it says you and I put right now
donde pone a ustedes y le puse a ahorita
I see it
lo veo
I mean
o sea
If I had had any idea I wouldn't have
si hubiera tenido idea no hubiera
asked that
preguntado eso
But how can't you see Javier Canijo?
pero como no puedes ver a javier canijo
are they seeing me there or not
me están viendo ahí o no
but what's going on
pero qué está pasando
since small sticks
desde chicos palos
Javier can't do anything now.
javier lo no puede hacer nada ahora
same
mismo
Yeah
si
You know that I asked who they were defending.
sabéis que yo pregunté a quien defendían
This art is ending and again there they are
va acabando este arte y otra vez ahí los
times of
tiempos de
ultimate proof that I didn't even have a [ __ ]
máxima prueba de que yo no tenía ni
idea
idea
Closing the topic, oh, of course that shows
cierre de tema ah claro eso demuestra
that he had not spoken with does not think
que no había hablado con no piensa
talk more about this
hablar más de esto
I hope they buy a good big buck
espero que se compren una buena big buck
quarter pounder
cuarto de libra
the people who were watching videos of this I don't
la gente que estaba vídeos de esto yo no
I plan to talk more about the topic but why?
pienso hablar más del tema pero por qué
it doesn't say that
no dice eso
it is enough
es suficiente
because prayer is [ __ ]
porque la oración una
answering is not something new and so
contestando no es algo nuevo y así que
It's a problem that I'm always going to have and
es un problema que siempre voy a tener y
that everyone is going to complain to me but
que todo mundo se me va a quejar pero
I never imagined it would get to this point
nunca me imaginé que fuera a este punto
where
donde
people on twitter who don't even know me
gente de twitter que ni siquiera me
meet people on twitter who never met me
conoce gente de twitter que jamás me
had made the interaction and then that
había hecho la interacción y luego que
I put myself I am very disappointed in
me ponga me estoy muy decepcionado de
throw and
tirar y
Honestly, I don't care if you're here.
honestamente no me interesa que estés
disappointed in me I don't know you
decepcionado de mí no te conozco
and disappoint people who do things
y decepcionar a la gente que haga cosas
bad not of a love that is going to us
malas no de un amor que nos va a
Reply to messages, end of tortilla topic
contestar mensajes fin del tema tortilla
and here I don't want bad comments towards
y aquí no quiero comentarios malos hacia
dallas please
dallas por favor
what I say I'm going to leave there having
lo que digo yo voy a dejar ahí teniendo
the follow because it doesn't seem bad to me
el follow porque no me parece mala
person on the contrary is grateful with
persona al contrario se agradecida con
He and I don't have any money with
él y yo no tengo ninguna blanca con
nobody
nadie
literally with no one and I'm sick of it
literal con nadie y estoy harta de que
get into controversies when metal doesn't
se meta en polémicas cuando metal no las
I'm looking for
estoy buscando
enough is worth it is worth it
suficiente vale vale
and get well soon, beautiful
y te mejores de ánimas bonita
Well, let's see what Dallas says it has done.
bueno a ver qué dice dallas ha hecho las
thanks for the sub welcome are
gracias por las sub bienvenidos están
the favorites out thank you very much
los favoritos a cabo muchísimas gracias
To all who sent beats
a todos los que mandaron beats las
tablets that subscribed to this in the
tablets que se suscribieron a esto en el
title that the alerts were going to be
título que las alertas iban a estar
mounted because otherwise it wouldn't be going to happen
montadas porque si no luego no iba a
being able to speak now, the alerts are already there
poder hablar ahora sí las alertas ya
It's perfect, okay.
está perfecto ok
that's it
ya está
tortilla was not finished they did not complain about
tortilla no se acabó no se quejaban de
which are previously given in controversies in
que antes están dadas en polémicas en
Those who avoid them get into places they don't belong.
las que las evita se meten en donde no
Navigon knows he spoke in his live I
navigon sabe él habló en su directo yo
I can't call, life can't go down
no puedo llamar no puede bajar la vida
I'm going to write to Dallas
le voy a escribir a dallas
the title is going to be changed if we are going to
el título se va a cambiar si vamos a
put to
poner a
They in tortilla, well, nothing family
ellos en tortilla pues nada familia
I think a little too
yo creo que también un poco
[Music]
[Música]
I think a little bit too
yo creo que un poco también tampoco
has so many so many
tiene tantas tantas
live
en directo
Now I think it doesn't have either
ahora yo creo que tampoco tiene
so much so much so much
tantísima tantísima tantísima
importance
importancia
as if it were happening in such a way
como para que se está dando en plan
he's asleep okay if dallas is
está dormido vale si dallas estar
lying down probably because writing
acostado seguramente porque escribiendo
the note with this flour or is it me
la nota con esta harina o me está
boxing the writing did not write
haciendo boxing el escrito no escribía
I imagine Dallas tonight
yo me imagino que dallas esta noche
now a direct something
ahora un directo algo
let's see, I'll take a look
a ver echo un vistazo
let me look
dejadme que mire
It's a direct goal
es un directo en el tanto
all night has connected to no one
toda la noche ha conectado a ninguna
part to the same
parte a la misma
but it won't be better anywhere
pero no estará mejor está en ninguna
part
parte
then I think that
entonces yo creo que